to the
al
he p p p p p
lui p p p p p
p
p
[Music]
[Música]
p p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
p
p
p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p
[Music]
[Música]
pom pom pom pom pom pom pom pom pom
pom pom pom pom pom pom pom pom pom
pom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam pam
pam pam pam
Pam Yosi
pam yosi
p
p
p p p p p p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p p p p p p
[Music]
[Música]
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p pom pom pom
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p pom pom pom
pom
pom
pom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
pam pam
pam pam
p
p
Yi ah
Yi ah
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Sparkle Oh
Sparkle Oh
[Music]
[Música]
wow
wow
ye
ye
I said
di
[Music]
[Música]
I have
he
yes ah
ye ah
[Music]
[Música]
P
P
w
w
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Go
Go
here we
here we
Go here we
Go here we
[Music]
[Música]
Go here we go
Go here we Go
ye
ye
[Music]
[Música]
Here we go, yeah
here we Go yeah
I love Wario I'm gna win
amo wario I'm gna win
[Music]
[Música]
Oh Oh
Ay Ay
Oh Oh a
Ay Ay a
a Oh a
a Ay a
to Ay
a Ay
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
come
venga
[Music]
[Música]
I have
he
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
pod he Hey he Hey Hey hey he
pod he Hey he Hey Hey hey he
[Music]
[Música]
heo
heo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
fierce Oregon
fero Oregon
you
you
[Music]
[Música]
short
corta
Come on then why are we going to talk
Dale Entonces por qué vamos qué hablamos
So things between them are already
Enton las cosas entre ellos ya
well spun with the condemnation Of course
bien hilado con la condena Claro que
plan a trip to your city eh I am
premeditar un viaje a tu ciudad eh Yo es
that I want to mark a day for me if I
que yo me quiero marcado un d a mí si me
condemned for something I want to say no
condenan por algo Yo quiero decir no
I pay and get [ __ ]. Of course, clo. Yes.
pago y que le follen Pues claro clo Si
you not if you lose and don't pay you
tú no si tú pierdes y no pagas te
They seize things and if you don't have them
embargan las cosas y si no tienes
nothing well spun well spun with the
nada bien hilado bien hilado con la
Good night family
condena Buenas noches familia
That
Qué
Come on, let's start strong. It's not that they have me
pasa empezamos fuerte No es que me han
warned while I had the music on
avisado mientras que tenía la música
since they were mentioning the thing about
puesta que estaban mencionando lo de
Ricky wanted
Ricky quería
listen to them clearly clearly only midón yes
escucharlos Claro claro camente midón si
Well, if you want, I wanted to ask you something.
Bueno si queréis os quería preguntar una
Something has passed me by. As you have seen.
cosa Se me ha pasado Cómo habéis visto
the theme of the ruine And Javi and Ricky because
el tema del ruine Y Javi y Ricky porque
There were sticks a couple of days ago I think
hubo palos hace un par de días creo que
It was or so, I don't ask you for good blows
fue o así palos buenas no te pido
kindly acknowledge the supremacy
amablemente que reconozcas la supremacía
and independence of the youth over
e independencia de la chavaleria sobre
your honor or we will do
la señoria o haremos
union union I would say that
sindicato sindicato Yo diría que
I would like the union to be the
quisiera sindicato sea la
fat gentlemen to the box
señoreros gordo a la caja
3600 the box already I mean I've already said it eh
3600 la caja ya O sea ya lo he dicho eh
Already Practically the answer to the
Ya Prácticamente la contestación a la
This type of demand is made
demanda del tipo este está hecha
I don't know how much the attorney will cost
la no sé Cuánto costará el procurador
but I think it's approximately 1,100 or so.
pero creo que aproxim m unos 1 100 o por
there okay then I understand that when
ahí vale entonces entiendo que cuando
let's have less than 1000 euros more now
tengamos menos de 1000 eur más ya
We pay the attorney and the next thing is
pagamos el procurador y ya lo siguiente
we started to demand from the list what
es empezamos a demandar a la lista lo
next is we start to demand the
siguiente ya es empezamos a demandar la
list okay we have this
lista vale esto lo hemos
spoken among the gossip I'm not going to do it
hablado entreel salseo no lo voy a
talk again here But well I don't know
volver hablar aquí Pero bueno no sé
earn it Cat Thank you very much for the super
gánatelo Cat Muchas gracias por el super
chat but eh
chat pero eh
a little no also I tell you no good
un poco no también te digo no bueno
win the kids not a little bit
ganel ganarlo la chavalería no un poco
No, because they are humiliating you there.
no porque es que os están humillando ahí
Hey, good night, Javi, kids.
eh buenas noches chavaleria Javi tú
work I work okay Okay then okay
trabaja yo trabajo vale Ya pues Vale
Come on, I'll get to work here. Also
venga yo me pongo aquí a trabajar Además
Today I have to do a live show here.
hoy tengo que hacer aquí un directo que
we have a few things a little
tenemos unas cositas un poco
interesting gossip to comment on and
interesantes de chisme que comentar y
Then I have to record a video.
después me tengo que grabar un videito
on the main channel that you
en el canal principal que os
What do you think of the videos?
están que os están pareciendo los vídeos
of the Channel
del Canal
main thing that you are thinking about
principal que os están pareciendo los
videos from the main Channel that you
vídeos del Canal principal que le
We're kicking butt again. Hey.
estamos dando cañita de nuevo Oye
we are almost almost almost
estamos ya casi casi casi
The New York blog is almost done
casi está andado con el blog de Nueva
York that we haven't uploaded yet because it is
York que no lo subimos todavía porque es
that has cost more work than I expected
que ha costado más trabajo de lo que me
I expected a lot of clips, a lot of clips
esperaba o sea muchos clips muchas
recordings look that was the only thing that
grabaciones mira que fue lo único que
I recorded that I later regretted, I say I had
grabé que luego me arrepentí digo tenía
that having released much more content
que haber sacado mucho más contenido por
Here I came up with ideas and so on but
aquí se me ocurrieron ideas y demás pero
as I was with the family and such neither
como estaba con la familia y tal tampoco
I was barely aware of the Internet
estuve apenas pendiente del Internet
But well, I think that for Sunday or
pero bueno creo que para el domingo o el
Monday you will have it uploaded to the Channel
lunes lo tendréis subido al Canal
main yes
principal sí
and nothing The truth is that it has happened to me
y y nada La verdad es que a mí me ha
It seemed excessive to download the video myself.
parecido excesivo bajarle el vídeo yo yo
I already said it if Javi doesn't put one
lo dije ya yo si Javi no pongo una
Rick's song edit less Knowing how
canción de Rick edit menos Sabiendo cómo
Things were already between them but
estaban las cosas entre ellos ya pero
Uncle, the one who gives himself monetization Ricky
tío la que darse la monetización Ricky
I would have said what a son of a [ __ ] no but because
hubiese dicho qué hijo [__] no pero por
another part says
otra parte dice
I don't know why the T says this because I
no sé por qu el T dice esto porque yo
For me it's almost the same. Well, it's not the same.
para mí es lo mismo casi Bueno no es lo
same but not good either
mismo pero bueno tampoco
don't put him to stay
no ponerle a quedarte la
monetization Well but the strike and
monetización Bueno pero ya el strike y
download the video especially a video that
bajar el vídeo sobre todo un vídeo que
There are like 30 or 40 collaborations
hay como 30 o 40 colaboraciones
different No no, I already stopped going down
distintas No no ya lo deaj lo de bajar
the video Ah salu I really say let's go
el vídeo Ah salu yo de verdad Digo vamos
Let's see how far it goes, let's go.
a poner a ver hasta dónde llega eh vamos
Let's see how far it goes, eh? And it has gone.
a ver hasta dónde llega eh Y ha llegado
the guy to throw the video to read on top
el tío a tirar el vídeo a lear encima
then he with you know or has been
luego él con sabes o sea ha sido
tremendous
tremendo
hey there's Auron there's Alfa there's Marta there
eh está auron está Alfa está Marta está
I don't know, man, a lot of people, man, it seemed
yo que sé tío mucha gente tío pareció
ugly anyway Sure but I just put by
feo igual Claro pero acab de poner por
The chat is missing now We close the topic
el chat que falta ya Cerramos el tema lo
of the sentence already
de la condena ya
finished a kiss veracity Many
finalizada un beso veracity Muchísimas
Thank you Welcome to the family don't you
gracias Bienvenido a la familia no te
we knew welcome I hope you
conocíamos bienvenido espero que te
you are forever from Dallas before
quedes para siempre de Dallas antes de
this
esto
He and I were going to subdivide that.
el y yo eso lo iba como a subdividir
for later
para luego
as it is another topic it is true
per claro como es otro tema es verdad
another one, let's go, damn it, Junior eats [ __ ]
otro vamos [__] el Junior come [__]
short short
corta corta
Come on then, let's talk. Then
Dale Enton por vamos hablamos Entonces
by poro then daddy welcome Hey
por poro entonces papi bienvenido Oye
but there are new people today
pero que hay gente nueva hoy no
Ricky who misses us
Ricky que nos extraña
being in the head of my friend Milhaus
estando en la cabeza de mi amigo milhaus
editions I can come to understand that
ediciones puedo llegar a entender que
want to [ __ ] a person with whom
quiera [__] a una persona con la que
has Big or with whom he doesn't get along at all
tiene Big o con la que no se lleva nada
I can understand that too, it is in
bien puedo entender eso también es en
war mode with that person you know is
modo guerra con esa persona sabes está
everything is bad and you will understand what is also
todo mal y vais aender lo que también
you have to see the perspective of what action
hay que ver la perspectiva de Qué acción
took, that is, he didn't hit him with a strek
tomó es decir no le metio un strek
direct Like for example Pablo Franco to
directo Como por ejemplo Pablo Franco a
me or what he's trying to do put a
mí o lo que intenta hacer le metió una
sanction that remained in the
sanción que se quedaba en la
monetization can be correct and that
monetización puede ser de correcto y que
if he cut or removed the song
si él recortaba o quitaba la canción
I think they didn't show him the video.
Creo que quedaba no le tiraban el vídeo
Neither the strike nor anything. We would have to see how.
ni el strike ni nada Habría que ver cómo
I would modify that because Javi did it
quedaría modificando eso porque Javi lo
It could have been modified too, but it was expected.
pudo modificar también pero se esperó eh
I think that spending that time is a
A que pasar ese tiempo creo que es una
week I think more or less what it
semana creo que más o menos lo que lo
What does Wismichu say to Tomy?
que dice wismichu a tomy no una
a week's warning didn't happen to him
advertencia de una semana no sí le pasó
What happened to me first jumped out at him
lo que me pasó a mí primero le le saltó
a claim of content ID that is
una reclamación de conten ID que eso es
automatic uncle the chat of c eh or that is me
automático tío el chat de c eh o sea me
they hate to the point of this
odian al punto de esto
Look, Javi couldn't help it when he was
Mira no ha podido evitarlo Javi al ser
That strike is legitimate, Javi deserves that.
legítimo ese strike Javi se merece ese
strike to go around insulting and
strike para andar insultando y
bothering others there if they don't cry
molestando a los demás ahí si no lloran
I mean, imagine when we have another one.
O sea imagínate cuando tengamos otra
strike controversy
polémica de strike
eh Imagine when we have another one
eh Imagínate cuando tengamos otra
controversy related to strike vale
polémica relacionada con los strike vale
It's that I would love to put you to
es que encantaría te va a poner a
save random usernames
guardar los nombres de usuarios Random
but they are going to put they are going to put it
pero van a poner van a poner lo
contrary to the song he put on
contrario por la canción que puso él
I had three options: mute Javi.
tenía tres opciones eh mutear lo Javi
Why are you doing this but change it
Por qué eres t va esto pero cambia de
music Face smiling with eyes
música Cara sonriendo con los ojos
closed the intro music
cerrados la música de la intro te
you mean or what the music of the
refieres o qué la música de la
intro I don't know but well that one doesn't play
intro yo que sé pero bueno esa no salta
nolo or
nolo o
with why And I guess he appealed I guess
con para que Y supongo que apeló Supongo
who did that I guess he sent the
que hizo eso Supongo que mandó la
appeal to YouTube
apelación a YouTube
and and then
y y después
eh they sent him the warning that that is
eh le mandaron la advertencia que esa se
puts it manually Well, the managers in
la pone manualmente Pues los managers en
Ricky didn't put your agency's shift
turno de su agencia no no lo puso Ricky
That is to say, we are going to talk about the managers
o sea lo de los managers vamos a
Let's see, let's see, we've already seen, yes, I do.
ver vamos a ver ya hemos visto yo sí me
I thought they were the managers but now
creía que eran los managers pero ya
we have seen from the screenshots
hemos visto por las capturas de pantalla
that Ricky taught is worth it for him
que enseñó Ricky vale que a él le
the accept appeal button appears or
aparece el botón de aceptar apelación o
reject appeal for Tommy's case
rechazar apelación por tanto lo de Tommy
It has been wismichu by hand
ha sido wismichu a mano
Ok, this warning gives you 7 days to
vale esta advertencia te da 7 días para
that you do the following or delete the
que tú hagas lo siguiente o borres el
video or communicate with the person
video o te comuniques con la persona
so that this can be resolved between both of us
para que se solucione esto entre ambas
parts does not give you the option to cut
partes no te da la opción de que cortes
eh but if you for example Javi spoke
eh pero si tú por ejemplo Javi hablaba
with Ricky edit and I told him, well, cut the
con Ricky edit y le decía pues cortas el
video and I'll remove the warning from you
video y yo te yo te quito la advertencia
It could be done and it is supposed to have happened in
se podía hacer y supone que pasó en
change in change he I think he waited for the
cambio en cambio él Creo que esperó los
7 days and well there it tells you 7 days and
7 días y Bueno ahí te lo dice 7 días y
strike but also, that is, there are like two
strike pero también o sea hay como dos
phases the first in which they give you a
fases la primera en la que te dan un
time in which you can modify the
tiempo en el que tú puedes Modificar el
Grandpa video I was going to tell you off, I thought that
vídeo abuelo Ya te iba a funar pensé que
you hadn't done direct jsj yes well
no habías hecho directo jsj si bueno
Since I have no context and I don't know what
como no tengo contexto y no sé qué
comment, spam, become a member
comentar hago spam háganse miembros
guys give the live show a like and donate
chavales denle like al directo donen en
the little box for grandpa to make the
la cajita para que el abuelo haga el
extendable from 24 hours and
extensible de 24 horas y
Garfield to see on Sunday not tomorrow
Garfield a ver el el domingo no mañana
Pablo Fran tomorrow is going to be a live broadcast
Pablo Fran mañana va a ser un directo a
the
las
12 announcing the game and premiering
12 anunciando el juego y estrenándose
because I'm not going to work tomorrow
porque yo mañana no voy a trabajar
absolutely nothing
absolutamente nada
in me tomorrow Well today I'm going to leave
em yo mañana Bueno hoy voy a dejar
recorded a video for the main thing
grabado un vídeo para el principal lo
You will have tomorrow, Sunday there will be
tendréis ustedes mañana el domingo habrá
video on the main channel surely
vídeo en el canal principal seguramente
which will be the New York blog
que será el blog de Nueva York
but I'm not going to work tomorrow
pero yo no no voy a trabajar mañana
because tomorrow I will be full with the family
porque mañana estaré full con la familia
It's also my mother's birthday
también es el cumpleaños de mi madre
Tomorrow I will go see her Also apart from
mañana iré a verla También aparte de
be with the family then we'll see
estar t con la familia entonces ya verem
but you guys really want to
pero ustedes tenéis realmente ganas de
an extensible You are going to contribute in the
un extensible Vais a aportar en el
extensible or are you going to make me start
extensible o me vais a hacer que empiece
at 12 noon
a las 12 del mediodía
eh And at 2 in the afternoon you
eh Y a las 2 de la tarde te
cut heats with a 12 hours but it is
cortar calienta con un 12 horas pero es
It is not a 12-hour period, it is a
que no se trata de un 12 horas se trata
that the extensible You start with a
de que el extensible Tú empiezas con una
hour and from there you start to
hora y a partir de ahí empiezas a
add without a limit no B without a limit I cannot
sumar sin tope no B sin tope no puedo
The children have school, my wife
los niños tienen colegio mi mujer
also studies
también estudia
is that if you really want a
es que si realmente tenéis ganas de un
extensible and you think we can hit it
extensible y creéis que le podemos pegar
a push to that, well maybe yes but
un empujón a eso pues tal vez sí pero
We don't care if we do the live shows
nos da lo mismo que hagamos los directos
Normally on Sunday I also have with
normales el domingo también tengo con
Marina edit it No that's when there is the
Marina editarlo No eso es cuando está el
content that is not when it is something manual
content eso no es cuando es algo manual
but when it is a claim of
sino cuando es una reclamación de
content ID the B this one that detects those
content ID el B este que detecta esas
[ __ ] there you can cut mute
[__] ahí puede cortar mutear
o o Apple is that I do not understand why
o o Apple es que yo no entiendo por qué
People, Eh, they start to see the shuffle
la gente Eh se ponen a ver a barajar las
options that if you can cut here if
opciones de que si puedes cortar aquí si
You can cut there, eh, let's see, Ricky.
puedes cortar allá eh vamos a ver Ricky
has gone to put a strike by hand both
ha ido a poner un strike a mano tanto
first the monetization and then
primero lo de la monetización como luego
the strike is worth it, he went to put it by hand
el strike vale lo ha ido a poner a mano
and that's it, you understand me. I mean, there's no more.
y punto me entiendes O sea no hay más no
let's turn it around so it could have been cut
le demos vuelta de podía haber cortado
yes yes yes yes of course and all the strikes
sí sí sí sí claro y y todos los strike
that Dallas has also put then
que ha puesto Dallas también pues
they might not have been put on as well and
podrían no haberse puesto también y y
all the strikes he's put in, eh? Who?
todos los strikes que ha puesto eh Quién
It was Sel who also put a strike on me
fue sel también puso strike quién me ha
strike put who gave me strike
puesto strike quién me puso strike
Gref also gave me a strike
también gref me puso un strike
Gre also gave me a strike shokas.
también gre me puso un strike shokas me
he put a strike
puso un strike
also the issue is that Ricky Also already
también el tema es que Ricky Además ya
whether it was part of Shas and Gref's thing
ya fuera parte de lo de shas y gref el
The thing is that windy windy it's true that I
tema es que windy windy es verdad que me
He wanted to put a strike, no no, he put it
quiso poner un strike no no que lo puso
that he put it is true I didn't remember anymore
que lo puso es verdad no me acordaba ya
eh it's true it's true But It's that the
eh es verdad es verdad Pero Es que la
move is the following the subject of the
movida es la siguiente el tema de el
The same old topic is a dirty trick, isn't it?
tema de siempre es una guarrada no el
strike theme but Ricky's theme
tema de los strike pero el tema de Ricky
specifically that it is a person who has
en concreto que es una persona que ha
criticized the whole strike thing and
criticado todo el rollo de los strike y
especially the nonsense he's said
sobre todo las payasadas que ha dicho
which is what I suppose it is And that can make you
que es lo que Supongo es Y eso te puede
jump as soon as you get the best of the day
saltar nada más subir el mejor al día
The next clear thing is that it is what he said
siguiente claro es que es eso según dijo
Javier jumped the next day But
Javier saltó el día siguiente Pero
Normally I like songs with
normalmente a mí las canciones con
Copyright was released after two days or so.
copyright saltó a los dos días o por ahí
but because it was manual at two TR days
pero porque fue manual a los dos TR días
They usually jump at the beginning or at the
me suelen saltar al principio o a la
hour quickly jumps very quickly because it
hora rápido salta muy rápido porque lo
He put the manual in two or three days
puso manual a los dos o tres días
moment It depends it depends usually
momento Depende depende por lo general
your video has to have a certain amount
tu video tiene que tener cierta cantidad
impactful so they see it and say Ah
de impacto para que lo vean y digan Ah
Well, I'll stick with my monetization.
pues me quedo con la monetización mis
Videos of Professor Jirafales Kiko
videos de el profesor Jirafales Kiko
and how much Well it was almost a minute I will play
y cuánto Pues fue casi un minuto tocaré
I think the total of everything I have not looked at it
creo el total de todo no lo he mirado la
truth and another but for him for what
verdad y otro pero por el por lo que
Ricky said, he doesn't care what he says.
dijo Ricky Lo pasa claro de lo que diga
Ricky, you have to see him.
Ricky hay que verlo
Always good night Javi Greetings and yes
siempre buenas noches Javi Saludos y si
You go up to the gathering, there is no one there
subes a la tertulia no hay nadie en
Twitch and at the beginning they said they wanted
Twitch y al inicio dijeron que querían
invite someone since not everyone is there
invitar a alguien ya que no están todos
Well, let's see, they haven't invited me and
Eh bueno a ver no me han invitado y
point I'm not going to get more encal or there was
punto tampoco me voy encal más o se haby
has divided this piece because it is about
a raccionado este trozo porque es sobre
I'm already there, we now have little things that
mí ya está tenemos ahora cosillas que
see we now have little things that
ver tenemos ahora cosillas que
see but you know that I don't understand the
ver pero eso sabes que no entiendo el
turn it around so it could have been cut off
darle vuerta de podría haber cortado no
I know what we're going to see, man, so how am I going?
sé qué vamos a ver tío o sea cómo me voy
to put to cut a rewind that is already
a poner a cortar un rewind que ya está
finished it's done it's done it's fine
terminado ya está hecho ya está bien sea
It just doesn't make sense, that's it.
es que no tiene sentido ya está
finished it's cool it's edited how
terminado está chulo está editado cómo
I'm going to [ __ ] a video So it doesn't have
voy a putear un vídeo Así que no tiene
sense none other characters more than the
sentido ninguno otos personajes más del
Chavo del Ocho They were claimed by
Chavo del Ocho Fueron reclamados por
Televisa even months later because
Televisa incluso meses después porque
they were getting 100,000 200,000 views
estaban pillando 100000 200000 vistas
clear and clear they saw it is Dijon Ah for
claro y claro ellos vi es dijon Ah para
m
m
what a bad thing, let's see what I want
ya qué mal a ver yo mira que quiera
to [ __ ] about the monetization issue
putear con el tema de la monetización
keep the money and all that
quedarse con el dinero y todo eso lo
I can understand from the B that you have and so on
puedo entender por el B que tien y demás
if I saw a route above in the video like
si visto una vía encima en el vídeo como
what B throws at him
que le tira B
no to
no al
[Music]
[Música]
glasses like you're going to throw me too
gafa como que en plan me tiras t también
here or whatever Well look I give you for
aquí o lo que sea Pues mira te doy por
there but now move on to a strike and that
ahí pero ya pasar a un strike y que le
can screw up the channel And that's what I think
pueda [__] el canal Y eso yo creo que
Nobody agrees with that.
nadie está de acuerdo con eso no
obviously not but already screwed because
obviamente no pero ya [__] porque
you enter into an ugly situation because
entras en una tesitura fea Porque
Surely Javi also has content
seguramente Javi también tenga content
From this the content ID will surely
de esto el content ID seguro que le
skip some Ricky video because Ricky
salte algún vídeo de Ricky porque Ricky
have you ever done things with Javi or
alguna vez ha hecho cosas de Javi o con
Javi ent you are now entering into a dirty war
Javi ent ya entras en una guerra [__]
that it be without quarter But Javi
que qu o sea sin cuartelillo Pero Javi
He's not going to do that, no Javi, he's not going to do that.
eso no lo va a hacer no Javi eso no lo
is going to do or is
va a hacer o sea
do all we have the option to
hacer todos loses tenemos la opción de
do it man Of course yes by power by
hacerlo hombre Claro sí por poder por
we can do it Yes but the issue is
poder podemos hacerlo Sí pero el tema es
What has to happen because Ricky
que qué tiene que pasar porque Ricky
has always criticized the strikes always
siempre ha criticado los strikes siempre
has been against it when it
ha estado en contra de eso cuando lo
made daras and other creators and this
hizo daras y otros creadores y esto le
he remains as a hypocrite, he remains as
queda como hipócrita queda como
hypocrite that you
hipócrita de que tú
Bravo criticism there Bravo I liked it
criticas Bravo ahí Bravo me ha gustado
I liked it, I liked it. Hey, he ...
me ha gustado me ha gustado Oye me oye
what is what it is and how much they know
lo que es lo que es y tanto que saben
that I don't do it is that I'm not going to do it
que no lo hago es que no lo voy a hacer
and the and very bu c also very good c that
y la y muy bu c también muy buen c que
who is saying things clearly and
que está diciendo las cosas claramente y
sincere and without hesitation from the
sinceras y sin titubeo desde desde el
first moment of the strike that but
primer momento de del strike eso pero
Then Claro says in the statement that
luego a dice Claro en el comunicado que
He put it on Twitter as if it was
puso por Twitter como que lo
I don't have the theory that
no tiene yo tengo la teoría de que
linking to the following
enlazando con el siguiente
point that Ricky believes that Javi has
punto de que Ricky cree que Javi tiene
quite like it's quite
bastante como que está bastante
involved in the complaint against him
involucrado en la denuncia que le está
putting Lali with Pablo Franco you me
poniendo Lali con Pablo Franco tú yo
exactly but yes yes he actually believes it
exactamente pero sí sí lo cree de hecho
They told me that he believes it, yes.
me lo han dicho que lo cree que sí que
I'll probably think about it, let's see this.
seguramente lo piense vamos a ver esto
Look, utbh hit him the other day with a sac ler
Mira utbh le pegó el otro día un sac ler
Len, we are not going to see that it does not matter that Lali
len no vamos a ver que da igual que Lali
I would have reported it if it weren't for Pablo
lo hubiera denunciado si no es con Pablo
It's with Pepito, okay, so it doesn't matter.
es con Pepito vale o sea que da igual
I already said it in 2022 that neither
que yo ya lo dije en 2022 que ni
It was estimated that Lali would end up reporting
cotizaba que Lali acabaría denunciando a
Ricky okay let's see you're not the best
Ricky vale vamos a ver no eres el más
Aunt Lali is smart, you are
espabilado una tía Lali le estás
saying in a viral video what he
diciendo en un vídeo viral lo que le
you're saying and then you've had enough
estás diciendo y luego te has hartado
insulting her in other podcasts was not even worth it
insultarla en otros podcast ni cotizaba
Okay, I personally have a personal opinion.
vale yo personalmente opinión personal
Super personal, very
Super personalísima muy
staff without blaming anyone, respecting
personal sin culpar a nadie respetando
the presumption of innocence is valid But
la presunción de inocencia vale Pero
giving our opinion because we are in things that are
opinando porque estamos en cosas que est
They are happening in public okay Yes they are
están pasando en público vale Sí que se
some private things too
algunas cosas de las privadas también
Ok, but well, regarding the public, yeah.
vale Pero bueno respecto a lo público Ya
I'm the only one who thinks Ricky has to
solo yo pienso que Ricky tiene que
defend himself very well from that Complaint
defenderse muy bien de esa Denuncia lo
It's [ __ ] up seeing how things are going And
tiene [__] viendo cómo va la movida Y
how things are going Of course he has recognized
cómo va la cosa Claro que ha reconocido
already one of the crimes has
ya una uno de los delitos la ha
recognized okay but I don't give a damn about anything
reconocido vale pero que me suda todos
balls what he thinks of Ricky or whatever
los [__] lo que piensa de Ricky o sea
Ricky is very short and very stupid.
Ricky es m muy corto es muy tonto aparte
The bad thing is that it is very short and very silly. Okay.
de malo es muy corto y muy tonto Vale
then I don't give a damn that
entonces a mí me suda los [__] que
Ricky thinks that I have put the o on him
Ricky se piense que yo le he puesto la o
that I have incited Lali or that I myself
que yo he incitado a Lali o que yo yo ni
I have introduced Pablo Franco to Lali
le he presentado a Pablo Franco ni Lali
has contacted Pablo Franco next to me
ha contactado a Pablo Franco al lado mía
and no one will ever be able to say it
y jamás nadie va a poder decir lo
The opposite is true if I say something with such
contrario vale si yo digo algo con tanta
rotundity and with such certainty it is
rotundidad y con tanta seguridad es
because it is like that, period, without more, I do not know if
porque es así punto sin más yo no sé si
to other youtubers or whoever there will be
a otros youtubers o quien sea le habrá
asked me of course Lali no and I
preguntado a mí desde luego Lali no y yo
I never lie, okay, because they could
no miento nunca vale porque me podrían
tomorrow I'll fight with Lali
sacar el día de mañana me peleo con Lali
and he shows me the screenshots or with Pablo it's okay
y me saca Las capturas o con Pablo vale
They will never be able to say otherwise.
jamás van a poder decir lo contrario yo
I have absolutely nothing to do with
no tengo absolutamente nada que ver con
that Ricky has been reported for eh
que a Ricky lo hayan denunciado por eh
Well, they have filed a complaint against him.
Bueno le han puesto una denuncia de
gender violence is worth the only one that
violencia de género vale el único que
It has to do with that complaint, it's him and
tiene que ver con esa denuncia es él y
If something happens to him, the one who has to see it is
si le pasa algo El que tiene que ver es
I have nothing to do with him. I have
él yo no tengo nada que ver Yo he
spoken to Lali five times four
hablado con Lali cinco veces cuatro
very few times is worth very few times
veces contadisimas vale contadisimas que
so from memory it was an eh about the
así de memoria fue una eh sobre el
theme When I don't know if She is there
tema Cuando no sé si estando Ella
We still talk a bit with Ricky
todavía con Ricky algo hablamos
Okay, you shouldn't have found out about that.
vale No debiste enterarte de lo de
Dallas you seem very quiet But
Dallas que se te ve muy calladito Pero
has lost the lawsuit against Miare you are going to
ha perdido el juicio contra miare vas a
make a video about anything for nothing
hacer vídeo al respecto de nada por
inform you, you don't do your job very well
informarte no haces muy bien tu trabajo
But the journalist is already here to
pero ya está aquí la periodista para
help, well look, no, I didn't know that.
ayudar pues mira no no lo sabía la
I really didn't know, I really didn't know
verdad no lo sabía la verdad no lo sabía
the truth is I just
la verdad me acabo de
find out But well I said it, it's worth it
enterar Pero bueno lo he dicho vale lo
saying
dicho
[Music]
[Música]
that they can never tell me
que que me que no me pueden decir nunca
They will never be able to tell me otherwise
nunca me van a poder decir lo contrario
I never have absolutely nothing to do
jamás yo no tengo absolutamente nada que
see but if I had to see if I had
ver pero si tuviera que ver si tuviera
what to see either, so you have to find your way
que ver tampoco o sea te buscas la vida
and you give it back to me in another way
y me la devuelves de otra forma a lo
throughout life
largo de la vida
Okay, you make a living and you give it to me.
vale Te buscas la vida y y me la
you will return in another way in life, okay?
devolverás de otra forma en la vida vale
but I have nothing to ask you to do
pero yo no tengo nada que que que tú me
you put a strike is not what we are going to see the
pongas un strike no es lo vamos a ver el
strike is for copyright the strike is for
strike es por copyright el strike es por
copyright is not for that is the report the
copyright no es por o sea el reporte el
reporting system what it says is that
sistema de reporte lo que dice es e que
the strike is for copyright not for
el strike es por copyright no es por
and because I'm stung with
e porque estoy picado con
Javi was funny in my mind, sorry.
Javi en mi mente daba risa perdón
Shut the [ __ ] up, but whatever.
Cállate la [__] boca pero bueno que da
it doesn't matter what
igual qu da
I think so and that's why it goes
igual yo creo y por eso va
[ __ ] yeah I think so
[__] Sí yo creo que
I would believe it if it were such a [ __ ] thing
lo lo cree si fuera [__] de forma tan
directly I would not have given him the strike
directa no le hubiera metido el strike
directly instead of a warning
directamente en vez de una advertencia
clear is the topic you know what I think happened
claro es el tema sabes que creo que pasó
Here the desire to [ __ ] came together
aquí Se juntaron las ganas de [__] de
Ricky's eh with
de Ricky eh con
Well, Javi's ego is not for my balls
Pues el ego de Javi de no por mis huevos
that I'm not going to delete that part and how
que no voy a borrar esa parte y como
They have that Where is that going to go?
tienen ese A dónde va a llegar esa
conversation because both could
conversación ya porque ambos podían
inhabited the strike both Javi editing
habitado el strike tanto Javi editando
that part as he not having put it and
esa parte como él no habiéndolo puesto y
No, because Ricky doesn't really win.
no porque es que Ricky realmente no gana
nothing about Javi taking a strike
nada de que Javi se llev un strike de
that other thing is still in fashion
eso del otro Aún se lleva la
modeling And he says Well look 300
modelización Y dice Pues mira 300
euros then I pay for dinner and what about me?
eurillos pues me pago la cena y yo que
I know even badly clear it is clear
sé incluso mal claro queda claro se
the p was left and he called it strike, that is, it was
quedó la p y le puso strike o sea fue
full, that is, we have not done that
full o sea es que eso no lo hemos hecho
never uncle no We have never come to that
nunca tío no Hemos llegado nunca a eso
Imagine, man, you're left with the
Imagínate tío le o sea te queda la
monetization and then you take it and put it in
monetización y luego coges y le metes
he is too much of a guy for me
est que es demasiado tío para mí es
a lot
mucho
Uncle, many people are behind the
tío mucho gente est detrás de la
complaint of the
denuncia del
Ali, let's see, Lerl said that to Delox that Delo
Ali a ver lerl dijo que a delox que delo
Aerl took the lawsuit away from Delo, I don't know if
le quitó la demanda aerl a delo no sé si
It was Javi, well I don't know which of them
era Javi bueno no sé quién de ellos que
They had told Delox when Delox was
le habían dicho a delox cuando delox era
part of your group of friends or whatever
parte de su grupo de amigos o lo que sea
that practically delox I don't know if it
que prácticamente delox yo no sé si lo
Delox said: Hello, but what about Delox?
contó delox Hola pero que a delox le
They had said, Look, we almost prepared you
habían dicho Mira casi que te preparamos
all the laser demand you just pum You have
todo la demanda laser tú solo pum Tienes
Just press a button and you have everything.
que apretar un botón y ya lo tienes todo
fact That is so and it is not so let's see
hecho Eso es así y no es así vamos a ver
that's what he said
es lo ha dicho
I had a very good laser with Delo
laser yo con delo tenía una muy buena
clear relationship So if suddenly
relación claro Entonces si de repente
to join us of those who had not
por juntarse con nosotros delos no había
never put a demand of this kind
puesto nunca una demanda de estas no
then I don't know if at some point I
entonces no sé si en algún momento Yo le
I would say, Hey, well this works like this or
diría Oye pues esto funciona así o
it works like this
funciona asá
And yes, I introduced him to Pablo A delo yes.
e Pues sí le presenté a Pablo A delo sí
I introduced him to Pablo, okay, I don't know.
le presenté yo a Pablo vale Yo no sé
how it was or how it wasn't I don't know if it's that
cómo fue o cómo No fue no sé si es que
talking when everyone was talking to him
hablando cuando todo el mundo le estaba
saying scam I don't know if I would tell him
diciendo estafa do no sé si yo le diría
Hey, look, this is how you do it.
eh Oye pues mira esto se hace así tú
You can file a claim like this:
puedes poner una demanda de estas como
the civilians who are putting us to
las civiles que nos están poniendo a
we that I discovered them by by
nosotros que yo las descubrí por por
it
ello
or or he would ask me do you know any
o o él me preguntaría tú conoces algún
lawyer I don't know I don't remember But what
abogado No lo sé no me acuerdo Pero que
it doesn't matter that it doesn't matter or rather that it doesn't matter
da igual que da igual o sea que da igual
that I am suing you for delox
que que yo que te está demandando delox
So it remains the same but let's see
O sea que queda igual pero vamos a ver
just like just like if I were to join together
igual que igual que como si me juntase
with any of them and such and all the
con cualquiera de ellos y tal y todo el
That roll is worth it. You know, yes.
rollo ese vale Sabes sí
So maybe this man thinks that
Entonces igual este hombre piensa que
Ricky thinks they've done something to him
Ricky piensa que le han hecho Algo
similar to
similar que
By association you may think so
por asociación lo puede llegar a pensar
In fact, a white guy threw [ __ ] at him.
de hecho un tío blancoo le tiró [__]
to Pablo Branco for in
al a Pablo branco por en
I saw it on Twitter, they saw the photo.
Twitter lo vi vieron la foto
they didn't see the epic photo
no vieron la épica foto
It is true
verdad es
epic I don't understand what sense it has
épica no entiendo qué sentido tiene que
I call you a puny nauter. But the truth is,
llame nauter canijo Pero bueno la verdad
I don't know, I don't think so. Met 55 and hidden
no sé no creo que Met 55 y escondido
behind me bad there no
detrás mía mal ahí no
I didn't expect that from you nter Play but
no esperaba eso de ti nter Play pero
Now being honest nauter is neither
ahora siendo honesto nauter no es ni
short or anything nauter is Met photo Pao
bajito ni nada nauter es Met foto Pao
Franco and the other girl Ricky standing up because
Franco y la otra ch Ricky de pie porque
It's clear that I haven't seen photos of
es que claro Yo no he visto fotos de
They both standing but come on Pao
ellos dos de pie pero vamos que Pao
Franco go around eh Because according to me
Franco ir por ahí eh Porque según estoy
watching with ricked he takes half of it
viendo con ricked está le saca media
head I think but 40 kilos doesn't weigh eh
cabeza yo creo pero 40 kil no pesa eh
That's what you see here 40
eso S que lo ves aquí 40
how funny
que muy gracioso
uncle you like that is as if the
tío que te gusta eso es como si la
have
tienes
that's always banking bro amazing dude
así siempre es banca bro increíble tío
60 out of 20 no but I'll tell you now yes
60 de 20 no pero ya ya os digo a mí si
I receive the demand directly
me llega la demanda yo directamente
I obey what they tell me. I don't even know what they tell me.
acato lo que me digan Yo es que ni lo
I fight because it is already lost, that is
peleo porque ya está perdido o sea
possible not
posible no
It's already [ __ ] up and Ricky's cones edit what
[__] ya está y conos de Ricky edit qué
You think it's going to happen because it's [ __ ] up
creéis que va a pasar porque está [__]
the topic eh Oh important thing that is
el tema eh Ay cosa importante que es
say from here eh one of the things that
decir de aquí eh una de las cosas que
Andorra has that if you have any
tiene andorra es que si tienes alguna
legal move and such I think you're going to
movida legal y tal creo que te vas a
[ __ ] the country
tomar por culo del país
eh There are quite a few, there is a lot of gossip
eh Son bastante es que hay mucho chisme
Well let's talk about things, let's go.
Bueno vamos a comentar cosas vamos Les
I send a kiss I send a kiss to you
mando un beso Les mando un beso a los
four and thank you for being with me
cuatro y gracias por por estar conmigo
in this Eh well family
en esta Eh bueno familia
that we have something we have
que tenemos cosita tenemos
little thing today the truth is almost a day of
cosita hoy la verdad es casi un día de
the most
los más
calm down, okay today has been a day of
tranquilos vale hoy ha sido un día de
the quietest today of those of the
los más tranquilos hoy de los de los del
little soccer team today have been more or
equipito de fútbol hoy han estado más o
less good except one thing I saw of
menos bueno menos una cosa que vi de
[Music]
[Música]
Karime, what a percilla, what a percilla, she tells me
Karime qué percilla qué percilla me dice
Karime look what I put in your
Karime mira lo que te he puesto en
Twitter and it makes me la la la again
Twitter y me pone otra vez la la la
Gorgon the Patri Okay what
gorgona la patri Vale qué
heavy noes
pesada noes
about the exens that I don't know Juan how
acerca el exens que no lo sé Juan cómo
how we decided on the extensible thing, that is
cómo decidimos lo del extensible o sea
we do
hacemos
a or rather how how we decide about the
un o sea cómo cómo decidimos lo del
extensible I set a goal I set a
extensible pongo una meta pongo un
objective and and and then it's that I don't know
objetivo y y y entonces es que no sé
because of course I don't know, I don't have a [ __ ]
porque claro No lo sé no tengo ni [__]
idea But I don't know if really
idea Pero es que yo no sé si realmente
you are, I mean, I don't know if you really want
estáis o sea no sé si realmente deseáis
that is, I don't know if because you know Then yes
eso o sea no sé si porque sabes Luego si
Are you going to leave me stranded or what? How annoying?
me vais a dejar tirado o qué Qué pesada
How annoying is Antonia's friend, Mrs.
Qué pesada la amiga de la Antonia señora
Leave me alone, you've been insulting me for 6 years now.
déjeme ya 6 años llevas insultándome
from this account and from the other
desde esta cuenta y desde la otra
Let me know how heavy you live in the year
déjame qué pesada tío viven en el año
That and they are discussing things like that, man.
ese y están discutie cosas de esas tío
They haven't won, these people haven't won
no han ganado no han ganado esta gente
Well, it seems that they are more burned
pueso si parece que están más ardidas
those who have won than those who have
las que han ganado que las que han
lost happens to me like with those who
perdido me pasa como con los que me
They beat me, damn it seems like they are
ganan a mí que están [__] parece que
They are more burned than I am than the one who has
están más ardidos que yo que el que ha
lost you understand me but you know why
perdido me entiendes pero sabes por qué
Because they do not cause the effect that
Porque no causan el efecto que que
They want to believe that because they
quieren ellos se creen que porque se
lose a lawsuit or because one is won
pierda un demanda o porque se gane una
demand is already decided the whole debate that
demanda ya se decide todo el debate que
there was and the whole story the story is
había y toda la historia la historia es
the same applies if a person has
la misma vale Si una persona ha
used insulting expressions because
utilizado expresiones insultantes pues
They are going to give you a fine, okay, but the
le van a poner una multa vale pero la
history and reality and the debate
historia y la realidad y el debate lo
People know and that's it, there's no more
sabe la gente y ya está que no hay más
If you see what I tell you, okay what?
si es que verás tú qué te digo Vale qué
Are you going to come and call me a gorgon, Karime?
Me vas a venir a decir gorgona Karime
do your job and pass the capture that says
haz tu trabajo y pasa captura que dice
a certain gentleman with a curious addiction, that is
cierto señor con curiosa adicción O sea
already getting into my addiction I
ya metiéndose con la adicción mía yo me
I'll mess with you, pat
meto contigo pat
I mess with you, you mess with me
yo me meto contigo te has metido conmigo
You messed with my daughter, you said.
te has metido con mi hija has dicho
very serious things about my daughter that you
cosas muy graves de mi hija que te
should even put a penalty but no
debería poner hasta una penal pero no
I can waste time on so much equipment
puedo perder el tiempo en tanto equipo
little soccer team as I call it Vale
equipito de fútbol como yo lo llamo Vale
I know that the addiction is but it is that
yo te yo que la adicción sea pero es que
Comment on every single thing that happens to me
Comenta cada cosa me pasan a cada
moment
momento
lady, what worries you most in life
señora lo que más le preocupa en la vida
and what is most pending is in the
y de lo que más pendiente Está en la
life is one of the things that are of the
vida es de las cosas que son de la
other people's family of mine and that of
familia de otra gente de la mía y la de
your friends that is your your biggest priority
tus amigos eso es tu tu mayor prioridad
in life, that is, with a curious addiction
en la vida o sea con curiosa adicción
Why doesn't Javi Oliveira put everything now?
por qué no pone Javi oliveira ya todo el
world knows how I pronounce that I am
mundo sabe cómo pronuncio que yo estoy
I reported you to him, I filed a complaint against you
denunciada por él te puse una denuncia
for putting my address on that page
por poner mi dirección en la página esa
of [ __ ] from the jurisdiction trying to say a kiss
de [__] del fuero tiando decir un beso
Okay, it's not even a few years old yet.
vale que no te ha llegado casi se añitos
Repeating the same thing, justice is slow
repitiendo lo mismo la justicia es lenta
so much so that this complaint has not yet been filed against me
tanto que esa denuncia todavía no me ha
been notified nor have I been notified either
sido notificada ni a mí tampoco me ha
yours has arrived this capture of that
llegado la tuya esta captura de que
You went to the police station and asked how
fuiste a la comisaría y a decir que cómo
was what you said in the
fue lo que dijiste en la
I don't remember the police station, but it's nonsense.
comisaría no me acuerdo pero t chorrada
of your history Because everything you do
de tu histori Porque todo lo que hacéis
It's the same, okay, I haven't received it either. What
es igual vale tampoco me ha llegado Qué
It also happens, have you lied or have we
pasa también has mentido tú o hemos
we both lied or we both said it
mentido los dos o los dos hemos dicho la
true But they have not taken it into account
verdad Pero no lo han tenido en cuenta
No. Ah, well, that's it, not each to his own.
no Ah pues ya está no cada uno por su
side but what are you going to be arguing about
lado pero qué vas a estar discutiéndose
with me that if I took a photo of your son
conmigo que si saqué una foto de tu hijo
I this I this this is from you know okay
yo esto yo este esto es de you know vale
If I start to see what it is that has happened to me
si yo me pongo a ver que es que me ha
taken out the la la with the [ __ ] nonsense
sacado la la la con la [__] tontería
This has already been told to me 800 times, okay?
esta me le ha dicho ya 800 veces vale y
I have answered you here, okay, continue.
le he contestado aquí vale sigue
living in the same thing I haven't either
viviendo en lo mismo A mí tampoco me ha
your complaint arrived XD and about it
llegado su denuncia XD y sobre la
nonsense that the piece of [ __ ] mentions
mamarrachada que menciona la pedazo de
obsessed, you have to see Game Over
obsesa vale que tenéis que ver Game Over
gossiping and it was a photo that she
cotilleando e fue una foto que ella
same
misma
published in the same capture that she
publicó en la misma captura Que ella
The same publication mentions that he wanted him to
misma publica menciona que quería que El
kid was a youtuber or Patrick
chiquillo fuese youtuber o sea Patrick
This photograph came to tell the
esta fotografía sin venía cuento la
You upload tags to your Twitter
subes tú a tu Twitter etiquetas a una
YouTuber with a million followers
youtuber de un millón de Seguidores la
youtuber answers you because you are a
youtuber te responde porque eres una
friend fan friend of these who approach
amiga fan amiga de estas que se acercan
to feel something is worth it and and and and the
para sentirse algo vale y y y y la
youtuber gives a lot of exposure to
youtuber le da un montón de difusión a
your photo when he is answering you if you
tu foto cuando te está contestando si tú
You upload a photo of your child tagging
subes una foto de tu hijo etiquetando a
a famous youtuber and the famous youtuber
una youtuber famosa y la youtuber famosa
who is spreading the word answers you
te responde quién le está dando difusión
the photo is fine if I'm looking at it
a la foto vale si yo estoy viendo
Twitter and I find the photo that
Twitter y me encuentro con la foto que
What do I do in a live show the most that I can do?
qué hago en un directo yo lo máximo que
I can do is not upload it pixelated or
puedo hacer es no subirlo pixelar o lo
that you want to leave me alone okay
que sea me quieres dejar en paz vale que
you here in the capture itself that you are
tú aquí en la propia captura que estás
telling me you're telling me that you want
diciendo me estás diciendo que quieres
that the child is a YouTuber and that you are going to help him
que el niño sea youtuber y que tú le vas
to support him to be a youtuber and that you
a apoyar a que sea youtuber y que tú me
you sent me a video here that you
mandabas vídeo a mí aquí que tú me
You sent a video here congratulating me.
mandabas aquí vídeo felicitándome el
your son's birthday so that I
cumpleaños de tu hijo para que yo
I put videos of your son here
pusiera aquí vídeos de tu hijo me
Do you want to let go of your arm now, Patricia?
quieres soltar ya el brazo Patricia que
To you, the only thing we have done is
a ti Lo único que hemos hecho ha sido
help you who have put yourself here above
ayudarte que te has puesto aquí encima
with all the shamelessness to say in your
con toda la poca vergüenza decir en tu
Twitter that you have to see that we
Twitter que hay que ver que nosotros
We have given you where you worked what you
teemos doados donde tú trabajabas lo que
you have to get into other things
tienes que hacer meterte en en otras
things that are not yours
cosas que no sean las que no son tuyas
that this has nothing to do with you
que esto no tiene nada que ver contigo
you are not even part of it, let's see how you find out that
ni eres parte a ver como te enteras que
I don't know how to tell you anymore if Anica that
ya no sé cómo decírtelo si Anica que
We put where she works, not pretty
nosotros pusimos donde trabaja no guapa
You came to ask for help because you had
viniste tú a pedir ayuda porque tenías
economic problems and I the teteg and
problemas económicos y yo el teteg y
a few of us helped you and I have here
unos cuantos te ayudamos y y tengo aquí
the certified t of ukum saying
los t certificados de ukum diciendo
buy at my friend's store
comprar en la tienda esta de mi amiga
Patricia Shut up Shut up now because I
Patricia Cállate Ya cllate ya que yo a
I haven't told you anything for 6 years.
ti no te digo nada desde hace 6 años
Shut up, I've done too many things.
Cállate Ya que demasiadas cosas he hecho
Damn, do what you have to do.
[__] dedícate a lo que te tengas que
dedicate and focus on whoever you have
dedicar y céntrate en quien te tengas
that focus seems to be a topic
que centrar que parece que es un tema
yours aunt that does not go with you that I know that
tuyo tía que contigo no va que yo sé que
I've already read you, I've known you for 6 years.
yo ya te he leído ya te conozco hace 6
years has been a friend of mine or a colleague of mine or
años ha sido amiga mía o colega mía o
You've already told me something, I need to be
algo ya me lo has dicho necesito ser
part of something feel part of something that
parte de algo sentirme parte de algo que
Listen to me, I've already listened to you today
me hagan caso ya te he hecho caso hoy
Patricia, leave me for another 6 years.
Patricia déjame hasta dentro de 6 años
Okay, next month you're going to be a witness.
vale el mes que viene vas de testigo a
about miar tell the truth about what you
lo de miar di la verdad de lo que te
go interrogate is the only thing that you
vayan a interrogar es lo único que te
I ask you, okay, don't do the same thing as
pido vale no vayas a hacer lo mismo que
he made the mess of cowards that he invented
hizo la lía de cobardes que se inventó
8000 videos and now that trial is over
8000 vídeos y ahora ese juicio se
will take much longer because what has
alargará muchísimo más porque lo que ha
that guy is a false witness
hecho ese tío es un falso testimonio lo
The only thing I ask of you is that of all that you
único que te pido de todo lo que te
Go ask them and they will tell you
vayan a preguntar que te van a di la
It's true, okay, but I don't even know
verdad vale sin más es que yo no sé ni
Why do they put you as a witness? It's because I
para qué te ponen de testigo es que yo
I don't even know why they put you as a witness
no sé ni para qué te ponen de testigo
Okay, but what always goes, what always goes
vale Pero bueno lo de siempre vale lo de
always with these people the same as always
siempre con esta gente lo de siempre
All things are equal Hey but what
Todas las cosas son iguales Oye pero que
the colleague is wearing eh, the colleague is wearing 6
lleva la colega eh que lleva la colega 6
years that if my son you put a photo no
años que si mi hijo pusiste una foto no
I know what, hey lady, let me go now it seems
sé qué Oye señora suéltame ya que parece
that you are part when when the one
que eres parte cuando cuando el que
I would have to be with you behind
tendría que estar con usted detrás de
you and I say you because I think that
usted y digo yo de usted porque creo que
This lady will have something like that and both
ya esta señora tendrá como ent y tanto
sticks too, let me go now, let me go now
palos también suéltame ya suéltame ya
[ __ ] Haven't you had enough with the
[__] No has tenido suficiente con las
things you said about my daughter that you don't
cosas que dijiste de mi hija eso no te
It has been enough for you Patrick that
ha sido suficiente a ti Patrick que
you want to distort I don't know what I don't know
quieres tergiversar no sé qué no sé
how much of me taking a photo for
cuánto de que yo saque una foto para que
I took a picture as if I were him
saque una foto como que yo le estoy me
I'm messing with your son, I'm going to
estoy metiendo con tu hijo yo me voy a
I'm messing with a kid
meter con un chiquillo me estoy metiendo
with you
contigo
Ladies learn to live in the
señoras aprendan a es que viven en el
2019 live in 2000 I don't know where
2019 viven en el 2000 yo no sé dónde
They live, but what do they want?
viven pero es que qué es lo que quiere
discuss Patrick if I took the photo if not
discutir Patrick si saqué la foto si no
I took the photo, the photo is on the channel
saqu la foto está la foto en el canal
So what are you asking me?
Entonces qué es lo que me estás
discussing what you're going to be like in 2027
discutiendo qu vas a estar en el 2027
arguing
discutiéndose
a little boy here but if you are
un chiquillo aquí pero si tú estás
looking at Twitter and the photo appears or it
viendo Twitter y te sale la foto o lo
what the hell am I doing, you know what I mean?
que sea yo qué [__] hago me entiendes
a photo that is being answered by a
una foto a la que está contestando una
super famous youtuber and then the mother
youtuber superfamosa y luego la madre
sending me video here so I can put The
mandándome vídeo aquí para que ponga El
Boy, what the hell am I going to have?
chiquillo yo qué [__] voy a tener la
bad intention but let's go anyway
mala intención pero vamos de todas
ways even if I had messed up
maneras aunque yo hubiera metido la pata
lady who 6 years ago says no more what
señora que hace 6 años suelta ya no qué
you are discussing what he wants you to do
estás discutiendo qué quiere que te qué
What Patrick wants is that I don't understand it anymore
quiere Patrick es que no lo entiendo ya
no, it's enough. No, you don't give yourself.
no ya es suficiente No tú no te das
tell what you do Patrick in
cuenta de lo que tú haces Patrick en
internet and what it dedicates to you And that when
internet y lo que te dedica Y que cuando
then you go to gorgon to insult me
luego te vas a gorgona a insultarme a ti
That seems normal to you that you have
eso te parece normal que te has
wrong several times
equivocado varias
sometimes Hey but I do it I do it
veces Oye pero que yo lo lo yo lo de
have a little soccer team that they put on
tener un equipito de fútbol que se ponen
to discuss with me each one his topic The plan
a discutir me cada uno su tema El plan
It's the fight we had in 2020
es la pelea que tuvimos en el 2020
He is still turning it over to see if he
todavía está dándole vuelta a ver si le
The other lady agrees that the years
da la razón la otra señora que Los años
What happens is that I don't know what the objective is
pasan es que no sé cuál es el objetivo
Tell me the objective what is it you have my
Dime el objetivo cuál es tienes mi
phone Tell me the goal and and and and and it
teléfono Dime el objetivo y y y y y lo
we'll fix it quickly but don't be too hard on me.
arreglamos rápido pero no me estés 6
years discussing whether a photo that
años discutiéndose que si una foto que
if I don't know what what
si no sé qué qué
you want me to not know what it is
quieres que no sé qué es lo que
wants No no it's not that these people are not that
quiere No no es que esta gente no es que
They are debating with you, no, no, it is not
estén debatiendo contigo no no esta
people stay in the year where they have been
gente se quedan en el año donde se han
stayed and they stay to fight
quedado y se quedan a pelearse a
discuss things that have happened
discutir de cosas de lo que se han
She was left with her theme The Joan plan
quedado ella con su tema El Joan plan
with his theme the other with his theme all
con su tema el otro con su tema todos
each one with his own story
cada uno con Los cada uno con su cuento
but come on, he has balls, he has balls
pero vamos que tiene huevo tiene huevo
that you have gone to that Forum and you have
que te has puesto al Foro ese y te has
put to say the things that you have said and
puesto a decir las cosas que has dicho y
the insults you have made to my wife
los insultos que le has hecho a mi mujer
and he also gives me the face that he knows
y me va echado también cara que que se
I saw a photo there when it is censored
vio Ahí una foto cuando está censurado
really let go, don't turn the page, no no
suelta de verdad no pasan página no no
They turn the page, Nica, but you still say you
pasan página Nica pero todavía dices tú
the protagonists of the story are worth it
los protagonistas de la historia vale
But you are nobody You are a
Pero tú no eres nadie Tú eres una
person from a forum who approached that
persona de un foro que se acercó a esa
lady took the friendship because the lady
señora cogió la amistad porque la señora
is recruiting okay And then you believe
va reclutando vale Y entonces te crees
that you are a friend okay But you are a
que eres a una amiga vale Pero eres una
person who says that you are a tool
persona que que que eres una herramienta
a weapon to say this kind of things
un arma para decir este tipo de cosas
but it's like
pero es como de
true This is forever good This
verdad Esto es para siempre bueno Esto
It will be forever or not. We'll see if
será para siempre o no Ya lo veremos si
will it be forever or
será para siempre o
No, well I don't know Karime but I don't even know
no pues no lo sé Karime pero ni me
It matters that I am when I talk about this
importa o sea yo cuando hablo de esta
people when trials come out when they come out
gente cuando salen juicios cuando salen
more or less things I would still like
cosas más menos todavía me gustaría
talk but judgments come out things come out
hablar pero salen juicios salen cosas
That's when these people come to light.
que es cuando salen esta gente a la luz
me
me
you understand but it's like no longer I mean already already
entiendes pero es como ya no O sea ya ya
One day they will have to stop, I say.
para algún día tendrán que parar digo yo
What's up? You realize that now only
qué va Tú date cuenta que ya solamente a
the fist procedures you what you
los procedimientos fist tú lo que le
They are left with what they extend and the
quedan con con lo que lo alargan y las
things that they are doing, preventing and
cosas que van haciendo impidiendo y
all the things but the worst is that she
todas las cosas pero lo peor es que ella
She knows what she said to me
sabe ella sabe lo que le ha dicho a mi
daughter knows what he said to my wife
hija sabe lo que le ha dicho a mi mujer
she knows perfectly well this and that
sabe ella sabe perfectamente ente y lo
worse is that ena is trying to you
peor es que ena te está intentando
to refute with their lies and with their
rebatir con sus mentiras y con sus
movies you know well if you say Well
películas sabes pues si tú dices Bueno
[ __ ] and he's refuting something that
[__] y te está rebatiendo una cosa que
She is convinced that but if it is that
ella está convencida que pero si es que
on top of that you are refuting me When you
encima me estás rebatiendo Cuando tú
you know what you've done in
sabes lo que has hecho en
internet Javi throws all the [ __ ] and
internet Javi tira toda la [__] y
marry
cásate con
Marifer Bueno let's start with this one
Marifer Bueno vamos a empezar con este
family extract but well how were you doing
extracto familia pero bueno como os iba
saying today has been a day
diciendo hoy ha sido un día
Today has been a quiet day
tranquilito hoy ha sido un día
calm down taking off this that he put on me
tranquilito quitando esto que me puso
Karime, the truth is that today I have had little
Karime la verdad que hoy he tenido poca
little news about the football team
poca noticia de del equipillo de fútbol
Okay
vale
eh today practically what I
eh hoy prácticamente pues lo que yo
When I wake up in the morning I feel
cuando me despierto por la mañana me me
I sometimes meet with Well I I me
encuentro a veces con Bueno yo Yo me
I wake up and turn off airplane mode. No. And
despierto quito el modo avión no Y
then the WhatsApp Pin Pin Pin begins
entonces empieza el WhatsApp Pin Pin Pin
Pin that I was talking about with Luare today
Pin que hoy lo estaba hablando con luare
I say precisely that I have fixed it because
precisamente digo lo he fijado porque a
the best places have written me something and
lo mejor lugares me ha escrito algo y a
I read it best in the afternoon when
lo mejor lo leo ya por la tarde cuando
talk to me again or whatever and I say
me vuelva a hablar o lo que sea y digo
I'm going to pin you up because if not it's
te voy a fijar arriba porque si no es
that I'm not going to leave, in the end, between all of us
que se me va no e Total que entre todos
those messages that come to me when I
esos mensajes que me llegan cuando me
I wake up suddenly in the morning
despierto por la mañana de repente
I check Twitter and I have notifications
reviso Twitter tengo notificaciones
I have this and I look better. I like them a lot.
tengo esto y me veo mds Me gustan mucho
the Twitter md because
los md de Twitter porque
Clear Greetings Grandpa breathes everything Pura
claro Saludos abuelo respira todo Pura
Victor's life is that they are more burned
vida Víctor es que están más ardidos los
who win lawsuits than those who do
que ganan demandas que los que las
you lose you know listen to me
pierden sabes escúchame
Well, anyway, Twitter DMs are awesome to me.
Eh bueno total a mí los md de Twitter me
They are more exciting because they are usually
hacen más ilusión porque suelen ser
people that you Well a youtuber no
gente que que tú Bueno un youtuber no
someone who doesn't have me on WhatsApp
alguien que no me tenga en WhatsApp
obviously not and when I see m
evidentemente no y cuando veo m
skylar and when I see m skylar and attentive
skylar y cuando veo m skylar y atentos
to the message You shouldn't have found out about
al mensaje No debiste enterarte de lo de
Dallas you seem very quiet But
Dallas que se te ve muy calladito Pero
has lost the lawsuit against Miare you are going to
ha perdido el juicio contra miare vas a
make a video about anything for nothing
hacer vídeo al respecto de nada por
inform you, you don't do your job very well
informarte no haces muy bien tu trabajo
But the journalist is already here to
pero ya está aquí la periodista para
help because the journalist has had to
ayudar pues la periodista se ha tenido
to smoke a log but a big one
que fumar un tronco pero de los gordos
Because all direct from me yesterday deal
Porque todos directo mío de ayer trato
About that I'll tell you anyway, that is,
sobre eso Igualmente ya te digo o sea el
this issue of the conviction of Dallas in the
tema este de la condena a Dallas en el
supreme I understand that they love him
supremo Yo entiendo que ellos le quieren
give a lot of hype because it is his and a man
dar mucho bombo porque es suyo y hombre
When you win something, you are not going to win everything.
cuando tú ganas algo no sobre todo vas a
receive a little bit more of that is you are going to
recibir un poquito más de o sea vas a
receive a little of everything you have
recibir un poco de todo lo que te has
spent no and when you have that
gastado no y cuando tienes esa
motivation in life that
motivación en la vida que al
end in the end these people the center of
final al final esta gente el centro de
Your life is the demands you have placed
su vida son las demandas que han puesto
not because they see it as
no porque ellas ellos lo ven como
the burning nail that is left is not
el la el clavo Ardiendo que le quedan no
No, no, this is the opportunity.
no no esta es la Esta es la oportunidad
With this one they really do denounce Dallas with
con esta sí que sí funan al Dallas con
This is the one that everyone is going to do.
esta sí que sí todo el mundo va va a
hating Dallas is nothing, it's a sentence
odiar a Dallas no nada es una sentencia
and it is a sentence for some insults eh
e es una sentencia por unos insultos eh
it is applauded, it is justified, not sincerely
se aplaude se justifica no sinceramente
No, let's see, I think, I'm not going to
no yo a ver yo pienso yo yo no voy a
to give an in-depth opinion on that ruling
opinar sobre esa sentencia a fondo
because I have problems with this
porque como tengo los problemas con esta
people I have I prefer not to do it okay
gente que tengo prefiero no hacerlo vale
I prefer not to do it. I understand.
Yo prefiero no hacerlo Yo entiendo
I understand the parts
entiendo las partes yo
Personally, I have seen myself in the
personalmente yo me he visto en la
situation that my family has been
situación de que a mi familia le han
I did something and I got really pissed off
hecho algo y yo me he [__] muchísimo
and I have been able to tell him a lot of
y he podido decirle un montón de
atrocities have happened and they have happened to me
barbaridades ha pasado y me han
also sued
demandado también
Not me personally. How do I explain it to you?
No yo personalmente Cómo os explico
What the [ __ ] is this Javi, time without
esto Qué pedo [__] Javi tiempo sin
see your face blowing a kiss face
verte cara lanzando un beso cara
blowing a kiss face blowing a kiss
lanzando un beso cara lanzando un beso
face blowing a kiss me personally
cara lanzando un beso yo personalmente
If someone is telling me
si alguien me se está me está diciendo
something strong is worth it
algo fuerte vale
and because this man has put things on him
e porque este hombre le ha puesto cosas
strong to Dallas on Twitter since its
fuertes a Dallas en Twitter desde su
account is not multi-account or anything this
cuenta no es multicuenta ni nada este
man had put things in Dalas
hombre le había puesto cosas a Dalas las
I have here stored safe in
tengo yo aquí guardadas fuertes en
Twitter happens that they have not been taken into account
Twitter pasa que no se han tenido en
account because Bueno is a man without
cuenta porque Bueno es un hombre sin
impact is not understood anonymous good
repercusión no se entiende anónimo bueno
I'm not going to give much of an opinion on
Yo es que no voy a opinar mucho en
depth of this sentence because it
profundidad de esta sentencia pues lo
to avoid nonsense but I
para evitar tontería pero yo
personally
personalmente
And look, one thing is that I sue the
e Mira una cosa es que yo demande a la
Lolly Huerta is worth it. I think that what the
Lolly Huerta vale Yo creo que lo que la
Lolly Huerta has made us and told us
Lolly Huerta nos ha hecho y nos ha dicho
It is one thing, it is already a strong car that does not
es una cosa ya es un carro fuerte que no
for a person who doesn't stop
para una persona que no para
eh a laser is worth it But when you
eh un láser len vale Pero cuando tú
you already have a conflict of this type
tienes un conflicto ya así de este tipo
What you can't do is that I don't know
lo que tú no puedes hacer es que no sé
how to get into this, really
cómo meterme en esto la verdad
Miare's father had gotten into trouble with
el padre de miare se había metido con
Dallas online and had told him
Dallas por internet y le había dicho
things I can say with
cosas que lo puedo decir con
peace of mind because he has put it there
tranquilidad porque lo ha puesto el
man from his account hints of
hombre desde su cuenta insinuaciones de
You're the same as always and things like that.
estas de Las de siempre y cosas así que
They are on their public Twitter you know
están en su Twitter público sabes
[Music]
[Música]
eh me for me me
eh yo para mí yo
and if someone messes with me
e si conmigo alguien se mete con mi
family or does something serious to me or
familia o me hace algo grave a mí o
someone in my environment whom I love
alguien de mi entorno a quien yo quiera
a lot eh
mucho eh
I can, I can warm up and I can
se me puede me puedo calentar y puedo
to put my foot in it too, that is, I think that
meter la pata también o sea yo creo que
all of us here in the chat in
todos los que estamos aquí en el chat en
sometime if they touch us
algún momento si nos tocan a los
ours or we already have something after
nuestros o tenemos ya una cosa después
you know about the other
de la otra sabes
eh there comes a time when you
eh llega un momento en el que tú
you explode and and Hey, well it could be
explotas y y Oye pues puede ser
disproportionate, you understand me
desproporcionado me entiendes
mm then Well, I don't know
mm entonces Bueno pues yo es que no sé
how to tell you This is fine but basically
cómo deciros Esto vale pero básicamente
I don't know if I would have insulted too
yo yo no sé si hubiera insultado también
In the Dallas situation you understand me
en la situación del Dallas me entiendes
That is, what I don't see as normal
o sea lo que lo que lo que no veo normal
is that this is celebrated as if it were the
es que esto se celebre como si fuera el
end of giving the review no hostia This time
fin de dar la review no [__] Esta vez
Yes, yes, they have convicted him for
sí que sí eh que lo han condenado por
insult and all the people who are
insulto y toda la gente que está
celebrating this sentence as if it were
celebrando eh esta condena como si fuera
a sentence that would turn it around
una condena que le diera la vuelta a
everything is the same as always. In the end,
todo son los de siempre Al final el
little team, the little team is worth it, that is, the people
equipito el equipito vale o sea la gente
with two in front For nothing it is one it is one
con dos de frente Por nada es una es una
condemnation for insult and out but that's not it
condena por insulto y fuera pero eso no
remove the rest of the topic, the dog topic
quita el resto de tema el tema del perro
all the fights they have all
todas las las peleas que tienen todas
the complaints that have been
las denuncias que se han
crossed what can I tell you for me of all the
cruzado qué te digo para mí de todos los
lawsuits that these people have had for
pleitos que han tenido esta gente para
There are others who are more important to me.
mí hay otros que son más importantes el
the minors' lawsuit the lawsuit of the
pleito de las menores el pleito de las
minors are reported by my mother
menores lo denuncia la la madre de mi
Father, that lawsuit is the mother of my father
adre ese pleito es la madre de mi adre
The one who starts it goes to the police station
la que lo inicia ella va a la comisaría
and says no, I found out that this
y dice no que me he enterado que esta
girl and this girl is worth that much, that's it
niña y esta niña vale eso ya está por
There counted ok Dalas loose okay eh
ahí contado vale Dalas a suelto okay eh
the accusations that Miare makes against him do not
las denuncias que le pone miare a él no
They don't even go to trial, okay, what about the dog?
llegan ni a juicio vale eh lo del perro
First civilian wins Dallas these people
primero civil lo gana Dallas esta gente
He breaks the sentence and is not given the
incumple la sentencia y no le dan el
dog and then a penalty wins Dallas
perro y luego un penal lo gana Dallas
misappropriation forgery
apropiación indebida falsificación
documentary I don't know what then That is
documental no sé qué entonces Ese es
the whole background of the real story that in
todo el fondo de la historia real que en
all these moves and in all these
todas estas movidas y en todos estos
conflicts that Dallas has had
conflictos que han tenido Dallas ha
insulted this man man to me
insultado a este hombre hombre a mí me
It is very striking that the
llama mucho la atención que que que el
that the demand is the father and not the no them
que demanda es el padre y no la no los
two not the whole family no Why Well
dos no toda la familia no Por qué Pues
because the
porque el
father is
padre es
Anonymous Why the mother does not put the
anónimo Por qué la madre no pone la
same demand if in those videos also
misma demanda si en esos vídeos también
messes with
se mete con
her because she also tells him little things
ella porque ella también le dice cositas
to Dallas, do you understand me? That's what they are.
al Dallas me entiendes o sea eso son eso
That's what a journalist of mine would do
eso es lo que haría un periodista mía
analyze the topic a little more deeply
analizar el tema un poco más a fondo
Ok, but anyway,
vale Pero bueno de todas maneras que
come to me to remind me of this you are
vengas a mí a recordarme esto tú eres
my silly one, I mean you are silly right?
tontísima mía o sea eres tontísima no
Mine yes there is a video in your imagination
mía sí hay un vídeo en tu imaginación En
which
cuál
fay In which In which imagination which video
fay En cuál En qué imaginación qué vídeo
What do you mean by that if the
a qué te refieres a que a que si la
mother messes with him
madre se mete con el
Dallas, I'll take it from you, I'll take it from you, I'll list it for you.
Dallas te saco te lo saco te lo enumero
because what I don't understand is how not to
porque lo que yo no entiendo cómo no la
demand because the lady comments
demanda porque es que la señora comenta
everything ah The
todo ah El
what the what What's happening in the chat that
qué el qué Qué pasa en el chat que
you are with another
estáis con otro
topic they are discussing is that the
tema están discutiendo lo de que el
father Ah no no no no I'm not there
padre Ah no no no no yo ahí no me
I don't get involved there
meto yo ahí no me meto
Okay, me with the dog thing with the issue
vale Yo con lo del perro con lo del tema
of the dog but but what is it that
del perro pero pero si que qué es lo que
We are discussing the dog thing.
estamos discutiendo lo del perro lo del
mobile phone theme that takes away the mobile phone that
tema del móvil que le quita el móvil que
so with the mobile phone of course because they had
le así con el móvil claro porque tenían
to the dog no Or the bottom at the end Which
al perro no O sea el fondo al final Cuál
It was either they had the dog or they didn't have the dog.
es que tenían al perro o no tenían al
dog you are with a lot of subject better do it
perro estás con mucho tema mejor hacerte
the crazy one, I'm going to the gathering
el loco me voy a la tertulia
guys well everyone interprets that
chicos bueno cada uno interpreta ese
video as you want listen to me eh But this
vídeo como quiere escúchame eh Pero esto
it's not pathetic
no es pateti
dude, this gives us the creeps
quillo esto nos da cosilla
says Hey Cinti says Hey how nice Come in
dice Oye cinti dice Oye qué bien Entre
She and Ret you have them working for you
ella y ret los tienes trabajando para ti
without pay everything that has to do with
sin paga todo lo que tenga que ver con
Dallas will already be covered because you
Dallas ya estará cubierto porque te
They will report everything, not some cram and here
informarán de todo no unos cram y aquí
I tell him, well, but it's to be
le digo yo Bueno pero esta para ser
journalist is a little late
periodista va con un poquillo de retraso
The other is more instantaneous and accompanies it
El otro es más instantáneo y lo acompaña
with a drawing No no it's not that this one has me
con dibujito No no es que esta me ha
come by the
venido por la
Tomorrow at 10 in the morning I have
mañana a las 10 de la mañana me ha
mandate
mandado
This makes me feel tender, says Karim.
esto a mí a mí me da ternura dice Karim
But what are you arguing about in the
pero de qué estáis discutiendo en el
chat you are with something else in the
chat estáis con otra cosa en el
chat good morning message What else
chat mensaje de buenos días Qué más
do you want grandpa
quieres abuelo
Well guys you've distracted me a bit.
Bueno chicos me habéis distraído un
little uncle I'm going to start the tract of
poquito tío voy a empezar el tracto de
new
nuevo
Okay, but I don't know what you're with.
vale pero es que no sé es que estáis con
another topic in the
otro tema en el
chat a question had already condemned the
chat una pregunta ya habían condenado al
Miare's father for hitting Li Yo
padre de miare Por pegarle a Li yo
I remember that yes, greetings, you're handsome, kiss
recuerdo que sí saludos estás guapo beso
If I'm not mistaken, those are complaints.
eso si no me equivoco son denuncias
Crossed Hol old tasty 10 years of yes
cruzadas Hol viejo sabroso 10 años de si
I'm not mistaken, the issue is complaints
no me equivoco tema son denuncias
crusades that I don't know how they are, I mean I think
cruzadas que no sé cómo están O sea creo
that Dallas has put something today but I don't know
que Dallas ha puesto algo hoy pero no sé
How are you? I think both of you are accused.
yo cómo están yo creo que ambos acusan
mutually
mutuamente
and and that it is stopped I don't know why
y y que eso está parado no sé el Por
I don't know why the
qué no sé el Por qué la
true sure that well it doesn't matter deal with it
verdad seguro que bueno da igual dealo
okay okay
vale vale
Karime anonymous children
Karime chavalería anónima
No, well, guys, let's start again.
no Bueno chicos vamos a empezar otra vez
to comment on this okay let's see
a comentar esto okay a ver
Hey this one
eh esta
tomorrow I
mañana me
I lift up that bonny boxing coat, don't you
levanto ese abrigo de box bonny no te
You look better without expensive clothes
queda mejor estás sin ropa cara
smirking, drooling
sonriendo con superioridad car babeando
A kiss friend A kiss friend Many
un beso amigo Un beso amigo Muchas
thank you
gracias
eh Let's see kiss paim monkey How
eh A ver beso paim monito Cómo
It was hot here a while ago
estás estuvo caluroso aquí hace
It's a little cool here, it's a little cool, good
fresquete aquí hace fresquete bueno
Come on family, let's get to it.
venga familia vamos al lío no
hon modo subs you are It's that I'm going to
hon modo subs os estáis Es que voy a
having to put two members on this topic
tener que ponerme dos miembros este tema
because you are going to say barbaric things eh or
porque vais a decir barbaridades eh o
I understand that this topic puts the
sea yo entiendo que este tema pone a la
people on the surface and it is a
gente a flor de piel y es un
A topic that generates a strong debate is worth it
tema que genera un debate fuerte vale
but try not to say nonsense
pero intentar no decir barbaridad
Please try not to distract yourselves and
porfa sea intentar no distraer os y
let's take things easy
vamos a tomarnos las cosas con el cachon
crime
deito
there aren't many haters lost around here
no hay mucho hater perdido por aquí
Well I understand the debate but let's
Bueno yo entiendo el debate pero vamos a
comment everything with respect Karime Pon
comentar todo con respeto Karime Pon
order by
orden por
There we can't say man, well yes
ahí qué no podemos decir hombre pues si
You cannot, if you can, not charge him with crimes
no podéis si podéis no imputarle delitos
it would be great for no one
a nadie estaría genial
Okay, if you can avoid charging crimes to
vale si podéis no imputar delitos a
no one or anything like that would be
nadie ni nada por el estilo estaría
brilliant
genial
Okay, there's my uncle who doesn't
vale está mi luare tío que no me
answer ok Anica Karime I leave it in
contesta vale Anica Karime lo dejo en
your hand Ah copy copy now I
vuestras mano Ah copi copi ya me
answer Well let's see family let's go
contesta Bueno a ver familia vamos a
start here it turns out that as you were doing
empezar por aquí resulta que como os iba
saying before I in the mornings when
diciendo antes yo por las mañan cuando
I wake up because the first thing I do is
me despierto pues lo primero que hago es
I put it on airplane mode and they start arriving.
pongo el modo avión empiezan a llegar
the WhatsApp
los WhatsApp
pi but they all start to arrive too
pi pero también empiezan a llegar todas
notifications of all the
las notificaciones de todas las
platforms no So when I see that
plataformas no Entonces cuando veo que
I have a Twitter DM, and Skylar is mine.
tengo md de Twitter eh Y es mía skylar
Well, I was very surprised by the message.
pues me ha sorprendido mucho el mensaje
so nice with which he gave me the
tan bonito con el que me ha dado los
Good morning, wouldn't you like it?
buenos días a ustedes no os gustaría
dawn with a message from
amanecer con un mensaje de
m you wouldn't love it or so
m a ustedes no os encantaría o sea se
You can have a more beautiful awakening No
puede tener un despertar más bonito No
You should have heard about what happened in Dallas.
debiste enterarte de lo de Dallas que se
you look very
te ve muy
quiet But he has lost his mind
calladito Pero ha perdido el juicio
against miare you are going to make a video
contra miare vas a hacer vídeo al
You do nothing to inform yourself about anything
respecto de nada por informarte no haces
very good your work but here it is
muy bien tu trabajo pero ya está aquí la
journalist to help besit
periodista para ayudar besit
kiss this has been my good morning
besito esto han sido mis buenos días est
It has been my awakening I have been watching the
ha sido mi despertar he estado viendo el
Mia Kylar's Twitter has given me the creeps.
Twitter de mia kylar me ha dado cosilla
It has given me a little bit of a creep seeing it
me ha dado cosilla un poquito de verlo
no but I mean I put the capture when I
no pero o sea pongo la captura cuando me
I wake up Good morning and such no And to her
despierto Buenos días y tal no Y a ella
He loved it eh Here it is again
le ha encantado eh Ya está otra vez la
app sher la aplo
app sher la aplo
chaffer the aplo chaffer
chaffer la aplo chaffer
Why the aplo chaffer m dat
Por qué las aplo chaffer m dat
nillan I don't know, it's very romantic
nillan yo a m no sé es muy romántica la
mine with you Javi Yes but this kind of
mía contigo Javi Sí pero este tipo de
attitudes I see her a little attention
actitudes yo la veo un poco attention
World sea is that no what explanation
World sea es que no qué explicación le
gives
da
without what explanation he gives you if not, that is
sin qué explicación le da sin no O sea
The girl comes as if because of course we are going to
la tipa viene como porque claro vamos a
see you can like a person better or worse
ver a ti te puede caer mejor o Peor un
character here we are already talking about the
personaje aquí ya estamos hablando de la
former forum member, okay, here we are
forera de antes vale aquí estamos
talking about a person who I think is not
hablando de una persona que creo que no
knows the others no I mean neither nor nor nor
conoce a los otros no O sea ni ni ni ni
with Dalas or with Miar he has had nothing no
con Dalas ni con miar ha tenido nada no
but is more of a fan of one than the other
sino que es más fan de uno que del otro
either by ideology or by what
o bien por ideología o bien por lo que
be it no eh or by factions no and by mob or
sea no eh o por bandos no y por turba o
for whatever reason no but of course from there to
por lo que sea no pero claro de ahí a
that you take a gossip creator and
que tú cojas a un creador de salseo y le
open by md for
abras por md para
tell him because here I really don't
decirle porque aquí en realidad no me
is remembering if he is reminding me of what
está recordando si me está recordando lo
if you are informing me about a topic
de la si me está informando un tema
because he thinks I haven't mentioned it.
porque cree que yo no lo he comentado Es
that is missing an nb because it is no longer that
que le falta un nb porque ya no es que
Well, you haven't seen the live broadcast of the
bueno pues no ha visto el directo de la
night no no it's not that you haven't seen my
noche no no es que no ha visto mi
Twitter because I was on Twitter
Twitter porque yo en Twitter estaba
commenting on this
comentando este
topic you know men hates you a lot and sends you
tema sabes men te odia mucho y te manda
kiss no I don't know think about it Well from Love to
beso no no sé piénsalo Bueno del Amor al
I hate there is a step But what is it that you
odio hay un paso Pero qué es lo que te
I say that is a person who is not
digo o sea una persona que no esté
involved going to send me a
involucrada ir a mandarme a mí un
message I don't understand Or how do you
mensaje Es que no entiendo O sea cómo lo
How do you interpret this? How not?
interpreta ustedes esto Cómo no
only how it
solamente cómo lo
I got married because it gave me eclipse
ha me caso es que me ha puesto eclipse
which means Ah yes Ah well, well, I'm going
que significa Ah sí Ah pues bueno me van
to funar maybe [ __ ] my mother
a funar tal vez [__] madre mía
we start again the tractor doesn't come
empezamos otra vez el tractor no venga
Come on, we'll put up with this, it doesn't matter, they're going to go to me
va este lo aguantamos da igual me van a
They are going to denounce me just like La Movida that
me van a funar Igualmente La Movida que
I don't understand it, but let them do it.
no lo entiendo o sea pero que lo hagan
Ricky's little kids who tell you
los niños pequeñitos de Ricky que te lo
make people who still believe people
hagan la gente que todavía cree a gente
like delox Okay, so you still say you
como a delox Vale pues todavía dices tú
Well they are special but let them do it for you
Bueno son especiales pero que te lo haga
an aunt of How much does this aunt TR have
una tía de Cuánto tiene Esta tía TR
so many sticks or lack of Nervo or
tantos palos o sea falto Nervo o sea
because you come to me because you come to me
porque vienes a mí porque vienes a mí
How to tell me that Haha your friend has
Cómo decirme que Jaja tu amigo ha
lost one or so that's what you come to
perdido un o sea eso es lo que vienes a
tell me point number one And what do I care?
decirme punto número uno Y a mí qué O
I don't have to pay for it, that's enough.
sea yo no lo tengo que pagar yo Bastante
I have with mine
tengo con los míos me
You personally understand what I think
entiendes yo personalmente lo que pienso
This is a demand I have already said before.
es esta demanda ya lo he dicho antes no
I'm going to go into depth, I prefer
voy a entrar en profundidad prefiero
avoid it But not for nothing but for the
evitarlo Pero no por nada sino por los
problems I already have with these people
problemas que ya tengo con esta gente
Hey, if I really have an opinion on this, I'll go.
Eh si yo opino realmente de esto los voy
to have been hooked for three or four weeks
a tener enganchado tres o cuatro semanas
insulting me on Twitter to all of them
insultándome en Twitter a todos ellos me
You understand, I personally have already done it.
entiendes yo personalmente ya lo he
I have said many times
dicho muchas veces yo
mm a people who have had so many
mm una gente que ha tenido tantas
problems with the
problemas con la
another Ana a kiss some people who have
otra Ana un beso una gente que le ha
made so many moves to
hecho tantas movidas al
Dallas me for me Well then you have
Dallas yo para mí Bueno pues te ha
insulted what do I say, or rather me too
insultado que te digo o sea yo también
I would insult people who have done things to me
insultaría a gente que me ha hecho cosas
surely
seguramente
Javi You shouldn't have found out about that
Javi No debiste enterarte de lo de
Dallas you seem quiet, or so I think.
Dallas se te ve calladito o sea yo lo
What I think is that basically clear the
que pienso es que básicamente claro los
Insults cannot be justified by
insultos no se pueden justificar por
supposed when we are in a non-medium
supuesto cuando estamos en un medio no
we can say everything that
podemos decir todo lo que
we think when we are in public and more
pensamos cuando estamos en público y más
With so many repercussions we cannot
con tantas repercusión no podemos
say it I have made that mistake too
decirlo Yo también he cometido ese error
On several occasions you already know it and I
en varias ocasiones ya lo sabéis y me
They have sued but let's see. It's that the
han demandado pero a ver Es que la las
people have feelings
personas tenemos sentimiento las
people when we get hot and we
personas cuando nos calentamos y nos
They do certain things because they do them because you
hacen ciertas cosas pues pues te
turn it on they do it to you or someone else
enciende te lo hacen a ti o a alguien de
your environment, someone you love,
tu entorno alguien a quien quieres pues
It turns you on and without further ado, then it's fine.
te enciende y sin más vale entonces pues
What do you want me to tell you if I
yo Qué quieres que te diga si a mí me
They condemn me because I have insulted them
condenan porque he insultado se me ha
gone crazy one day when you made it or me
ido la olla un día que la has hecho o me
you have said something to me or to my partner or to
has dicho a mí algo o a mi pareja o a
Whoever is around me understands me.
quien sea de mi entorno me entiendes son
many things are many things that
muchas cosas son muchas cosas las que
they have to be the conflict then
tienen que est el conflicto entonces
For me, the whole background is what you
para mí de todo el fondo es lo que te
I mean, eh, what they report with what
digo o sea eh lo de lo denuncian con lo
of the minors report him for abuse
de las menores lo denuncian por maltrato
Hey Dallas has to report it because it doesn't
eh Dallas tiene que denunciar porque no
They give it back to the dog and he wins it and still
le devuelven al perro lo gana y todavía
They don't give the dog back either and it has
tampoco le devuelven al perro y tiene
that they have put a penalty on the penalty
que poner una penal en la penal han
I still have Don Quixote wrapped up, I still have it wrapped up
liado El Quijote todavía me todavía me
You are going to come to report or sue for
vas a venir a denunciar a demandar por
civil because I have insulted you, you know
lo civil porque te he insultado sabes
but no, it's not that, but it's very
pero no no es que eso sino que es muy
It is obvious that if you have insulted
evidente no que si tú has insultado a
someone strongly are not expressions
alguien fuertemente no son expresiones
strong ones will condemn you okay it's very
fuertes te van a condenar vale es muy
obvious but to me specialist people
evidente pero a mí gente especialita
how is this that these are very people
como esta es que esto como son gente muy
special, that is, the people who are
especial o sea la gente que Está
celebrating this the people who support
celebrando esto la gente que apoya a
These people are very special people for
esta gente son gente muy especial para
Let's see what the whole conflict is about
mí vamos a ver de todo el conflicto es
like Anaya's demand, Naya's demand
como la demanda de Anaya la demanda naya
Of course I win. Of course I win.
Claro que la Claro que la gana yo me
I expected that he was going to win, of course, that is
esperaba que le iba a ganar claro o sea
If it is true that it has been proven that
si es verdad que se ha podido probar que
Naya went and posted That Call When I Didn't
naya fue y publicó Esa llamada cuando no
I was a participant or anything like that. Well
era participe ni nada por el estilo Pues
Of course they are going to condemn her but for me
claro que la van a condenar pero para mí
the point is what was being demonstrated
el punto es lo que se estaba demostrando
no That is what was being discussed in
no O sea lo que se estaba discutiendo en
that
esa
called Well, people say Ah well
llamada Bueno pues la gente dice Ah pues
hag won has won she was right
hag ganado ha ganado tenía ella razón
Claro was right that it was not
sbre Claro tenía la razón en que no se
you can publish that no but but that is
puede publicar eso no pero pero eso es
as if I now sue Win michu No
como si yo ahora demando a Win michu No
because he published the es that he does not have
porque él publicó las es que no tiene
meaning are hypocrisies at every moment
sentido son hipocresías a cada momento
No, but well, you pay and what is the
no pero bueno pues pagas y ya cuál es el
problem exactly then you take charge
problema exactamente pues te haces cargo
of what you have done and just like that no O
de lo que hayas hecho y y sin más no O
I imagine that Dalas, eh, I don't know.
sea yo me imagino que Dalas eh No sé
Now then we will see what he said
ahora luego vamos a ver lo que ha dicho
Dala but I think she won't regret it
dala pero yo creo que no se arrepentirá
From what he said you understand what I mean
de lo que ha dicho me entiendes lo que
It happens that you can't say everything that
pasa que tú no puedes decir todo lo que
you think and such And and you already know No no no
piensas y tal Y y ya lo sabes No no lo
you say again and and without more but for
vuelves a decir y y sin más pero para
these special people So of all the
esta gente especial O sea que de todo el
lawsuit of the whole lawsuit of the
pleito de todo el pleito lo de las
minors are released from the dog's case
menores sale de suelto lo del perro le
condemns that they return the dog
condena a que devuelvan al perro no lo
returns has to p a criminal complaint
devuelve tiene que p una denuncia penal
Hey, they say the dog has a brother.
eh el perro dicen que tiene un hermano
twin I don't know what I don't know how much all the
gemelo no sé qué no sé cuánto todas la
who messed with the dog are sentenced for
que liaron con el perro les condenan por
the dog because of misappropriation
el perro porque apropiación indebida
Document forgery, eh Emilio, that is.
falsificación documental eh Emilio o sea
Okay, but eh eh eh eh the end of Dallas
Bueno pero Eh Eh Eh Eh el fin de Dallas
who has insulted someone man
que ha insultado a alguien hombre
Forgive me Mika a kiss forgive me
Perdóname Mika un beso perdóname
forgive me
perdóname
Forgive me, I have a tweet from that man.
perdóname yo tengo tweet de ese hombre
It happens that of course it has no impact
lo pasa que claro no tiene repercusión
but that man has also put things
pero ese hombre también ha puesto cosas
on Dallas Twitter that they are not that they are not
en Twitter del Dallas que no son que no
It's nonsense, eh? And not from a multi-account.
son tonterías eh Y no desde multicuenta
from yours I'm not going to say your name
desde la suya no voy a decir su nombre
but from your account with your
pero desde su desde su cuenta con su
name Because I knew the man
nombre Porque yo lo conocía al hombre
from his account he has posted Pin Pin things
desde su cuenta ha puesto cosas Pin Pin
clicking clicking clicking you know
pinchando pinchando pinchando sabes
So of course here what we have in mind
entonces claro aquí lo que se tiene en
The thing is that one is famous and the other is not.
cuenta es que uno es famoso y el otro no
one has repercussions and the other does not
uno tiene repercusión y el otro no por
that's what I was telling you
eso lo que os estaba diciendo
eh I think this complaint is in fact
eh yo creo que esta denuncia de hecho
First I would have to check this, right?
primero esto lo tendría que comprobar no
I'm sure it's okay but I think this one
estoy seguro vale pero yo creo que esta
complaint first they put it as criminal and
denuncia primero la pusieron penal Y
Since it didn't work out for the criminal case, I think
como por lo penal no funcionó creo que
So they went civilly but not
entonces Fueron por lo civil pero no
I'm sure, eh, that's maybe I'm
estoy seguro eh eso a lo mejor me estoy
making a mistake but if you realize it in
equivocando pero si os dais cuenta el en
those videos are saying family of
esos vídeos está diciendo familia de
criminal the mother this I don't know and only
delincuente la madre esto no sé y solo
The father asks why. Well, because
demanda el padre por qué Pues porque
They have a very good lawyer who gives very good
tienen muy buen abogado que da muy
good steps, the truth is things have to be done
buenos pasos la verdad las cosas hay que
recognize them and knows them very well
reconocerlas y sabe muy bien las
Strategies How to play them for later
estrategias Cómo jugarlas para luego
Call all the press and play with them
Llamar a toda la prensa y juga con los
headlines okay but you have to
titulares vale pero usted tiene que
notice the details or that is
daros cuenta de los detalles o sea el
Dallas talks about the Father And the mother
Dallas habla del Padre Y de la madre la
Mother, why don't you sue as well as you have?
madre por qué no demanda también como ha
made in mine in the first mine because
hecho en la mía en la primera mía porque
already in the second one I don't know anymore
ya en la segunda ya no se
put in Well because the mother is also there
metió Pues porque la madre también está
insulting him all day on Twitter is
todo el día insultándolo en Twitter es
public and all that stuff But oh well
pública y y toda esa movida Pero bueno
There are already special people like me, okay?
ya está gente especial como mía vale que
is not part of the conflict and you come to
no forma parte del conflicto y vienes a
me but apart This is not like
mí pero aparte Esto no es como
reminding me of content that I have
recordándome un contenido que a mí se me
forgot to comment this is like
ha olvidado comentar esto es como
challenging me as if I were
retándome a mí como si a mí me
messed up something this you know as if it were
fastidiara algo esto sabes como si fuera
One thing about me is that you are pathetic, right?
una cosa mía y es como eres patético no
and now take and quote the
y ahora coge y cita el
tweet it
tweet lo
retweet pic
retuitea pic
And I don't understand how people have Gan
u yo no entiendo la gente cómo tiene Gan
to ruin Sela the Javi of the past yes
de arruinar Sela el Javi del pasado si
I would give attention to my man if I did.
le daría atención a mía hombre yo si le
I give attention if I am giving attention to him
doy atención si le estoy dando atención
like no I invite her here to come up
como que no Yo la invito aquí a que suba
If you want me, I'd like to ruin your
si quieres yo Qué ganas de arruinarte la
life colleague I mean you are criticizing you are
vida colega O sea estás criticando estás
rejoicing that they condemn a
alegrándose de que condenen a una
person for insults and you are there
persona por por insultos y estás tú ahí
Pin Pin Pin with the demands he has
Pin Pin Pin con las demandas que tiene
sorry, I mean he quotes it again because he doesn't
perdón O sea lo vuelve a citar porque no
they have paid attention to him, they have not paid attention to him
le han hecho caso no le han hecho
enough case before and does it again
suficiente caso antes y lo vuelve a
quote Sorry I didn't see that you had already spoken
citar Perdón no vi que ya habías hablado
of the subject because your channel seems to me a
del tema porque tu canal me parece una
damn [ __ ] and I preferred to cut myself
reverenda [__] y prefería cortarme
I would rather cut my little chorizo
preferiría cortarme el choricito de
new Before watching a video of yourself alone
nuevo Antes que ver un vídeo tuyo solo
I wanted to remind you that the court
quería recordarte que el tribunal
Supreme Court has condemned Dallas alone
supremo de ha condenado a Dallas solo
that's it. Sorry, what did I put there?
eso ji Perdona eh qué le he puesto yo
Here and what the hell do you remember me for?
aquí y a mí para qué [__] me recuerdas
that [ __ ], I mean it's like as if
eso [__] o sea es como como si
as if I had lost something but it is
como si yo hubiera perdido algo pero es
that not even Dallas, or rather Dallas lives
que ni siquiera Dallas o sea Dallas vive
his chill life calmly if it is true
su vida chill tranquilo si que es verdad
that this does not have with this family that
que tiene esto no con esta familia que
you're going to have it for life, or so it is.
lo va a tener para toda la vida o sea lo
we have those who speak to him
tenemos los que nos hablamos con él
imagine imagine he's worth this is going to
imagínate imagínate él vale Esto va a
to be for life, it will have it all
ser para toda la vida lo va a tener toda
life and it has to go eh
la vida y tiene que ir eh
You know, but it's like you're from Sevilla
sabes pero es como si fueras del Sevilla
and from the beti And you come and you rejoice because
y del beti Y vienes y te alegras porque
has won the beti you know droll the no
ha ganado el beti sabes droll la no
I droll the pape a lot but it is that it is
droll la pape mucho pero es que es
ridiculous or rather it is that it is
ridículo o sea es que es
pathetic or so Dallas has lost one
patético o sea Dallas ha perdido una
sentence for insults Ah
sentencia por insultos Ah
and how many youtubers are there? Since they have
y cuántos youtubers van Ya que han
lost sentence for
perdido sentencia por
insult
insulto
And that takes away everything else, of course.
Y eso eso quita todo el resto claro
then they burn for example the part that
luego se arden por ejemplo la parte que
wins the lawsuits is more bitter than the
gana las demandas está más ardida que la
that I lost it and that also happened to me with
que la perdido y eso también me pasó con
another lawsuit that I lost Damn they are more
otra demanda que perdí [__] están más
Those who lose are more bitter than those who lose
ardidos los que pierden que los que
They win Why Because the result is not no
ganan Por qué Porque el resultado no no
so in the end who celebrates this? Well, the
tal al final quién celebra esto Pues el
I equip mine kyar the Johan flat the
equipito la mía kyar el Johan plana la
Tania, you know, normal people say
Tania sabes o sea la gente normal dice
Well, they condemned him for insulting.
Bueno puesan condenado por insultar no
you can use those expressions no
puedes utilizar esas expresiones no
You can say those things, okay, I don't know.
puedes decir esas cosas vale eso no se
can do in a medium ok you could
puede hacer en un medio vale podías
having said the same thing with others
haber dicho lo mismo con otras
expressions in another way but they are good
expresiones de otra forma pero bueno son
things about the heat are also valid. Good
cosas del calentón también vale Bueno
from the heat and conflict they have
del calentón y del conflicto que tienen
measured in time because the lawyer of
medido en el tiempo porque el abogado de
They claim that it was not a
ellos alegan no es que no fue un
hot because it was in another video a year later
calentón porque fue en otro vídeo al año
next also said it and it's like
siguiente también lo dijo y es como
Ah But this is not everyday life because
Ah Pero esto no es el día a día porque
I have here all of them all of them
yo tengo aquí la todos lo todas las
things that this lady tells us and it's every
cosas que nos dice esta señora y es cada
day is every day is every day
día es cada día es cada día
every day when he is not abusive they are
cada día cuando no es maltratador son
insults that we are [ __ ] that we are not
insultos que somos unas [__] que no
We have dignity that I don't know what all of us have.
tenemos dignidad que no sé qué todos los
days that's why she doesn't demand she puts in
días por eso ella no demanda ella mete a
the
los
But anyway, a very cool kiss from me
demás Pero bueno un beso mía muy chuli
the truth you
la verdad tu
message there you don't have Ricky's
mensaje por ahí no tienes lo del Ricky
but that's what I'm telling you, I mean, eh
pero es que es lo que te digo o sea eh
In short, nothing is nonsense, just give it to him
en fin nada son tonterías son darle
back to nonsense let's see what it is
vuelta a tontería vamos a ver qué es lo
what he said
que ha dicho el
D let's see what he said
D vamos a ver qué es lo que ha dicho el
dala based mine based mine good
dala basada mía basada mía buena
journalist if so why don't you sue
periodista si es así por qué no demandas
July
Julio
because good question why not
porque buena pregunta por qué no
demands Well I have already passed it on to the
demandas Pues yo ya se lo he pasado al
lawyer who is handling the case with her already
abogado que lleva el tema con ella ya se
I've been through it several times and it has to
lo he pasado varias veces y tiene que
make the decision himself in the end, that is
tomar la la decisión él al final o sea
He is the one who decides, okay, what do I do?
él es el que decide vale Yo qué
I would rather not know anything about them at all
preferiría no sabe nada de ellas en toda
Life, if I tell you the truth, what I want
la vida si te digo la verdad qué quiero
Give me how much 2000 in 6 years
que me dé cuánto 2000 dentro de 6 años
Why don't you sue? Well, maybe the
por qué no demandas Pues a lo mejor La
The answer is because I am not
respuesta es pues porque no estoy
obsessed you understand me that maybe
obsesionado me entiendes que a lo mejor
There comes a time when I say, look, lady.
llega un momento que ya digo mira señora
That's it, you're going to pay me, well, maybe
ya está me vas a pagar tú pues puede ser
You know why I don't insult people?
Sabes porque es que yo no insulto a la
Lady, I won't even say anything good to you, mentioning her.
señora ni le digo nada bueno mencionarla
Yes, we mention it, it is obviously there
sí la mencionamos evidentemente está
saying things about me I can
diciendo cosas sobre m Yo puedo
respond to the fact that I put myself
responderle el hecho de que me pusiera
a lawsuit in 2019 doesn't make me no
una demanda en 2019 no me hace no
answer him and I think it's a desire to
responderle y yo creo que son ganas de
that he answers you because look now at the
que te responda porque mira ahora el
dasas is answering him and says the
dasas le está respondiendo y dice el
dasas that will make a series of
dasas que le va a haer una serie de
videos are wanting you to come now and you
vídeos son ganas de que ahora venga y te
respond today You were complacent with
respondan hoy Estuviste complaciente con
your haters making him write Karim January
tus hater haciéndole escito Karim enero
It is a very month
es un mes muy
Bad but maybe the answer is that
malo pero tal vez la respuesta es esa
but it's not like I don't demand it
pero no es como por no demando yoo el
Dallas and then the issue of the
Dallas y además luego el tema de las
demands are also very subjective uncle
demandas también es muy subjetivo tío
Look
Mira
Hey, I was watching the sentence.
eh estuve viendo la sentencia
from Roma Gallardo who sued him
de de Roma Gallardo que lo demandó
Cristina keep going, okay, they had it.
Cristina a seguir vale eh ellos tuvieron
as
como
[Music]
[Música]
a a move also is is a is a
una una movida también sea es un es un
very similar lawsuit very similar to the
pleito muy similar muy similar al
first mine with miare okay But well no
primero mío con miare vale Pero bueno no
very similar to the expressions of Rome
muy similar las expresiones de Roma
toward
hacia
Cristina, for my taste they are worse than
Cristina yo para mi gusto son peores que
Mine towards Meades, okay?
las mías hacia meades vale
eh And Cristina did say something to Roma
eh Y y Cristina sí le dijo algo a Roma
what if
como que ay
how was it that happened to him
que cómo fue lo que le
He said, I don't know if he called him sexist or something.
dijo No sé si le dijo machista o algo
I don't remember anything like that, but something
por el estilo no me acuerdo pero algo
not like that but it was not proportional
así no pero no era proporcional la
true okay or so and basically it is very
verdad vale o sea y básicamente es muy
the claim is similar to mine in the lawsuit
parecida la demanda a la mía al pleito
It is very similar to mine Because e
es muy parecido al mío Porque e
There is a kind of previous contest
hay como una contienda previa una
non-animistic prior are found and there are
animista no previa se encuentran y hay
a previous dispute that ties And such But
una contienda previa que ata Y tal Pero
then there are the expressions of Rome, well
luego ya eh las expresiones de Roma pues
They are expressions a little more not for for
son expresiones un poco más no para para
I have to admit that for my taste
mi tengo que reconocer que para mi gusto
They are not proportional, let's say not.
No son no son proporcionales digamos no
and and there are a few tweets and some
y y son unos cuantos de tweet y unos
How many videos is it worth? And in a program
cuantos de vídeos vale Y en un programa
I don't know if it will be in such a way, Cristina already
no sé si será en tal pues Cristina ya
after all the videos it does say
después de todos los vídeos sí que dice
some comment of the stick Oh well look
algún comentario del palo Ay Pues mira
how sexist I don't know I don't have it I would have it
que machista No sé no lo teng lo tendría
that I don't have it by heart, it's worth it
que ver no lo tengo de memoria vale la
I was reading today
estuve leyendo hoy
In La Movida there is a very beach
em La Movida es que un playo muy
similar to mine for my taste with
parecido al mío para mi gusto con
The most insulting expressions are fine and without
expresiones más insultantes vale y sin
However, the claim is dismissed in
embargo eh la desestiman la demanda en
two instances you know So in the end
dos instancias sabes Entonces al final
the issue of lawsuits you have to
el tema de las demandas tienes que
have it very clear very clear very clear
tenerlo muy claro muy claro muy claro
And you know how you ended up with Rome well or
sabes Y tú cómo quedaste con Roma bien o
bad No, I'm good I'm good in that fight
mal No yo bien Yo bien yo en ese pleito
I have not made any video or commented or anything.
yo no no vídeo ni he comentado ni nada
because I get along with both of them
porque yo me llevo con los dos yo me
I've been with Cristina for a while now, I have a thing for her.
llevo con Cristina que le tengo un
special affection also because I have lived
cariño especial también porque he vivido
with her a series of things I have not been
con ella una serie de cosas no he estado
with her in Thailand and all that stuff
con ella en Tailandia y todo el rollo
We have also been to Madrid.
ese no también hemos estado en Madrid
we have been to a few places
hemos estado en unos cuantos de sitios
No, and I get along with Rome because it is a
no y yo me llevo con Roma porque es una
person who is a colleague with whom you
persona que que es un colega con el que
I have affection not for many years
tengo cariño no de hace muchos de hace
many years and I the lawsuits that
muchísimos años y yo los pleitos que
they have both and the moves that
tengan ellos dos y las movidas que
They have them both, I don't put it in me.
tengan ellos dos yo no me no me meto la
true I mean I can comment on it like
verdad O sea la puedo comentar como
It's news, but objectively it's like this.
noticia vale pero objetivamente es así
It is a very similar pl to mine, there are two
es es un pl muy parecido al mío son dos
people who have a previous dispute
personas que tienen una contienda previa
No, there's a move, no, I had the
no eh Hay una movida no Yo tuve la
thing that happened to me, no
movida de que a mí me me pasó aquello no
that they threatened me with things
que me amenazaron cosas con las
conversations that they later took out and there are
conversaciones que luego sacaron y y hay
a series of expressions that can
una serie de expresiones que pueden
being more unfortunate, let's say it
estar más desafortunadas vamos a decirlo
not like that
así no
and then they dismiss it and
em y entonces pues lo desestiman y
we are talking about something that happened
estamos hablando de una de algo que pasó
in
en
So why don't I sue?
entonces que por qué no demando pues
because I'm not obsessed, that is, me
porque no estoy obsesionado o sea yo
I think that's the one
creo que esa es la
answer that is not a thing either You know
respuesta que tampoco es una cosa Sabes
less when viral topics go like this
menos cuando salen así los temas virales
Let this be of judgment, for this is already today
sea esto del juicio pues esto ya hoy
We talked about Dallas, I think Dallas has
comentamos lo del Dallas yo el Dallas ha
said that it's going to be a series of videos
dicho que va a ser una serie de vídeos
but I think it is the result of
pero yo pienso que es fruto del
hot I think that that is not it
calentón Yo pienso que que que no lo
will do because it is that
hará porque es que
You really know I don't know the truth
realmente sabes No sé la verdad yo
I think he won't do it but if he does
pienso que no lo hará pero si lo hace
We may react if it doesn't end.
posible reaccionaremos si no se acaba el
topic also the other people uncle are desire
tema también la otra gente tío son ganas
that this one answers you and I hit you a
de que este te responda y os pegué un
I walk everyone, eh, I think he will.
paseo a todos eh yo s creo que lo hará
I don't think so Karime but let's get to it
yo creo que no Karime pero vamos a lo
that the one who was going to question that was not
que iba el que de la cuestión que no
They stop, they don't stop, they live in 2018 16 no
paran no paran viven en el 2018 16 no
they stop, they don't stop and apart from that, it's that you
paran no paran y aparte es que te
They argue and throw things in your face
discuten y te echan en cara cosas de
2016 as if it were things from now to me
2016 como si fueran cosas de ahora a mí
Suddenly Karim sends me a tweet that
De repente me manda Karim un twet que
The lady says: Yes, yes, the one who told me
dice la señora Sí sí el que me decía
Mom on WhatsApp, lady, we are friends
mamá en WhatsApp señora erramos amigos
Madam, we are in 2025, that is, I think
señora estamos en 2025 o sea creo que
makes a
hace una
decade you know what a is
década sabes lo que es una
decade, that is, do you know what a decade is?
década o sea sabéis lo que es una década
dude, I mean, I start to think about what it is
tío o sea yo me pongo a pensar lo que es
a decade
una década
eh what a decade is eh And they throw me out
eh lo que es una década eh Y me echan
face because I told him a decade ago
cara porque yo le dije hace una década
No man, it's a decade, there are two years left.
no tío es una década falta dos años para
a decade or
una década o
less you know what that is and they are
menos sabes lo que es eso y te están
discussing that uncle what do I tell you if I don't
discutiendo eso tío que te digo si yo no
Uncle, I have been able to change my mind
tío que yo he podido cambiar de opinión
of things from a month ago that is that I
de cosas de Hace un mes que es que me
you said I don't know
dijiste no sé
What then? Okay, what do you
qué pues Vale qué te
I say a decade is a decade because a
digo una década es una década pues una
decade are the conversations that I
década son las conversaciones que me
Win michu took out, they are from a decade, you know, and
sacó Win michu son de una década sabes y
It's like what you
es como qué te
I say you know life but they are there
digo sabes la vida pero es que están ahí
They are there, they have stayed there.
están ahí ellos se han quedado ahí ellos
not super but apart from that they are things that eh
no super pero aparte son cosas que eh
for my taste Also another opinion that
para mi gusto También otra opinión que
I have that sentence
tengo de esa sentencia
eh for my taste these people what they are
eh para mi gusto esta gente lo que van
looking for is
buscando es
humiliate not to compensate his honor for me
humillar no resarcir su honor para mí el
the issue of lawsuits, that is one of
tema de las demandas que eso es una de
the things that I am going to discuss until the
las cosas que yo voy a discutir hasta el
supreme also if that is necessary
supremo también si hace falta eso de
order four
pedir cuatro
videos well it depends it doesn't depend
vídeos bueno es que depende no depende
of the case for the diffusion and such yes it can
del caso por la difusión y tal sí puede
be justified but of course if you have
estar justificado pero claro si tú has
gone
ido
In my case, it is true that I do not have the
en el caso mío vale que yo no tengo la
diffusion that Dallas has
difusión que tiene Dallas
eh they go to all the newspapers and put
eh se van a todos los periódicos y ponen
not only the headline that I have
no solamente el titular de que me han
convicted of insulting her
condenado por insultarla
but they take an extract taken from the
sino sacan un extracto sacado del
context of the trial with arguing
contexto del juicio con discutiendo
on a subject that is not part of the lawsuit
sobre un tema que no es parte del pleito
Also, I'll tell you about that later.
además O sea que eso ya os comentaré
Well, the context is fine, they bring it up on TikTok.
bien el contexto vale lo sacan en tiktok
on Instagram and
en en instagram e
They took me out of my trial and began to
a sacaron del juicio mío se pusieron a
her boyfriend and her laughing at each other
reírse el novio y ella de hasta de la
clothes I was wearing were taken as a meme
ropa que llevaba sacaron como un meme
with Mira the sheep cowboy a pair of pants
con Mira el borrego vaquero un pantalón
of I don't know what a pair of pants of I don't know
de no sé qué un pantalón de no sé
how much or what they are looking for is not
cuánto o sea lo que buscan no es
to restore your honor I think that the
resarcir tu honor Yo pienso que las
lawsuits are to restore your honor not
demandas son para resarcir tu honor no
to humiliate the other party you what
para humillar a la otra parte tú lo que
you have revenge because in the debate
tienes es venganza porque en el debate
media you have not been able to you have not been able to
mediático no has podido de no has podido
with your arguments with your facts you know O
con tus argumentos con tus hecho sabes O
be that I read and also they if you give yourselves
sea que lea y además ellos si os dais
The lawyer also tells in a podcast
cuenta el abogado también en un podcast
He said the thing about No, it's not that he reads it.
dijo lo del No no es que la lo de leer
The failure is the most humiliating thing about
el fallo es lo más humillante con lo de
nauter I think he said it and it's like for
nauter creo que lo dijo y es como para
My demands are to compensate the
mí las las demandas son para resarcir el
honor does not stop, does not stop
honor no para no para
humiliating is not about humiliating either
humillar no se trata de humillar tampoco
the other part is not about doing
la otra parte no se trata de hacer
Justice is not good because they ask you for it.
justicia no bueno porque te pidan bueno
is that Sorry they can't force you to
es que Perdón no te pueden obligar a
ask no but the issue of them going for
pedir no pero el tema de que vayan por
all the media laughing at you eh
todos los medios riéndose de ti eh
stains Why don't you take the piece out of the
manchás Por qué no saca el trozo del
trial where he asks my lawyer
juicio donde le pregunta a mi abogado
for the interview he did on 20 And her
por la entrevista que hizo en 20 Y ella
says no no I've never done one
dice no no Yo nunca he hecho una
interview in 20 or a thousand things like that
entrevista en 20 o mil cosas así que
There was, you know, well, we'll talk about that later.
hubo sabes Bueno ya hablaremos de eso
we'll talk about that eh we'll talk about that
eso hablaremos eh eso hablaremos os
I promise we'll talk about that.
prometo que eso hablaremos
deeply
profundamente
but I don't know, so why do you want me to?
pero no sé o sea para qué quieres que
upload 10 videos and ask me to upload them
suba eh 10 vídeos a mí me pide que suban
eight videos eh. It asks me to upload
ocho vídeos eh A mí me pide que suba
eight videos that are like what do you want
ocho vídeos que es como para qué quieres
that I upload eight videos with the error if
que yo suba ocho vídeos con el fallo si
you have gone to 28
habéis ido a 28
newspapers will destroy the judges
periódicos se va a cargar los jueces
boredom no but this of the
aburrimiento no pero esto de las
demands Although her lawyer tells you
demandas Aunque el abogado de ella te
Say pioneering demand that is not pioneering OR
diga demanda pionera eso no es pionero O
There are already a lot of convictions
sea hay un montón de condenas ya de
youtuber in the supreme is that of the
youtuber en el supremo es que lo de lo
of the lawyer promoting himself too It is
del abogado promocionándose también Es
a joke, eh, or rather, the pioneer sentence
un chiste eh o sea lo sentencia pionera
and it is like a pioneering sentence But why
y es como sentencia pionera Pero por qué
It is a pioneer no no because it is the first
es pionera no no porque es el primer
youtuber There are a lot of sentences of
youtuber Hay un montón de sentencias de
youtuber already already but it is the first
youtuber ya ya pero es el primer
There aren't a lot of YouTubers in the Supreme Court.
youtuber en el supremo no hay un montón
from youtube in the supreme the speak by
de de youtub en el supremo el spean por
example He was also in the Supreme Court O
ejemplo También estuvo en el supremo O
sea ​​there are a lot of sea is that I don't know in
sea hay un montón de sea es que no sé en
what a good pioneer in What is
qué pionero bueno en Qué es
canary
canario
You know the worst thing is that justice gives them the
sabes lo peor que la justicia les da la
Gaston is not right, they don't agree with him.
razón Gastón no es que le den la razón
Let's see when you, eh, let's see, man.
vamos a ver cuando tú eh vamos a ver tío
look at Nauter's, that is, when you
mirar la de nauter o sea cuando tú
If you insult a person, they will insult you.
insultas a una persona a ti te van a
They will fine you if you are not sentenced outside
multar te van a condenar fuera no has
tarnished a person's image outside
manchado la imagen de una persona fuera
there is no
no hay
But then it depends on the context of the
más ya luego depende del contexto del
rest of the context Well, well, you're done.
resto del contexto Pues bueno pues ya tú
you value from whom
valoras de parte de quién
you are there but not
estás pero no
necessarily the fact that you give it to him
necesariamente el hecho tú tú le das la
reason to Juan Planas because I
razón a la a Juan planas porque a mí me
condemned for
condenaron por
insult him you agree with him in the
insultarle tú le das la razón a en el
debate that
debate que
We have Well let's read what has
tenemos Bueno vamos a leer lo que ha
saying
dicho
Dalx my ex and his entire family condemned to
dalx mi ex y toda su familia condenada a
prison twice already and soon
prisión dos veces ya y pronto la
third well This refers to that there was
tercera bueno Esto se refiere a que hubo
one there are two first instances because
una hay dos primeras instancias porque
There was a first instance of a trial
hubo una primera instancia de un juicio
that they managed to cancel the voucher. It was repeated.
que consiguieron anular vale Se repitió
the judgment is worth, that is, the judgment of something
el juicio vale o sea el juicio de algo
It has been the penalty twice, eh, that is to say,
ha sido dos veces el penal eh o sea el
judgment of something has been twice the
juicio de algo ha sido dos veces el
penalty you know Ah They are extending it for the
penal sabes Ah Lo van alargando para el
dog but good
perro pero bueno
and now they appealed it. Hey, well, the
e y ahora lo recurrieron Oye pues la el
topic of the provincial court of something
tema de la audiencia provincial de algo
It has to be on the way out too
tiene que estar al salir también
eh Wi mocho makes me feel sorry Well lo Win
eh Wi mocho me da pena Bueno lo Win
Michu also had a trial with
michu también tiene tuvo un juicio con
Dallas that has to be out
Dallas que tiene que estar salir la
sentence in any
sentencia en cualquier
moment notice that many times the
momento fijaros que muchas veces el
destiny is capricious, eh, I mean, it is, it is
destino es caprichoso eh o sea está está
eh waiting for the sentence eh Win's
eh a la espera de Sentencia eh la de Win
michu
michu
and the dog's resource the dog's resource
y y la del perro el recurso del perro
And there is something else about Win Michu too.
que y de Win michu otra cosa también hay
Hey, there's another little thing about Wi Michu.
eh de Wi michu hay otra cosilla que
It must be said that we have
tiene que comentarse que nos ha
commented
comentado
Anika the dog realizes that now I
anika el perro date cuenta que ahora yo
I don't know if they can appeal a penalty
no sé si pueden un penal recurrir al
Supreme I don't know if they can penalize it
supremo no sé si el penal lo pueden
to resort to the supreme truth There is no more
recurrir al supremo la verdad Ahí ya no
I know how
sé cómo
In addition to having lost more than 10 cases
va además de haber perdido más 10 casos
against me and having to pay me in
contra mí y haber tenido que pagarme en
my judgment
mi juicio
Previously in the civil case he paid money, I didn't
anterior en el civil pagó dinero no me
I agree, well I don't remember, I don't know what
acuerdo bueno no me acuerdo no lo sé que
plus 10 cases against me or how many
más 10 casos contra mí o sea Cuántos
These people have put in more than 10 cases.
casos han puesto esta gente tío más 10
more than 10, my goodness, the money they carry
más de 10 madre mía la pasta que llevan
These people are lawyers and lawsuits, eh, and
esta gente en abogados y y pleitos eh y
and and and the
y y y el
wear and tear. Well, it's normal that they celebrate it.
desgaste Pues normal que lo celebren
as a pleasure to win some let's see if not
como un placer ganar alguno a ver si no
I'm wrong
me equivoco de
memory is the lawsuit, that is, my complaint
memoria está el pleito o sea mi denuncia
dala for gender violence no
dala por violencia de género no
He tries to reopen that same complaint.
de esa misma denuncia la intenta reabrir
try to reopen Well I don't know if
intenta la reapertura Pues no sé si
There were two three times because one did it
fueron dos tres veces porque una lo hizo
as
como
with one if I'm not mistaken he did it with a
con una si no me equivoco lo hizo con un
topic of saying that they had
tema de de diciendo que se habían
leaked photos of
filtrado las fotos de
She claiming that the information had been leaked
ella alegando que se habían filtrado las
sexy pictures of her out there I think it was
fotos de ella sexy por ahí Creo que fue
and then the other time he tried to reopen
y luego la otra vez que intentó reabrir
He was accusing Dala of revealing
fue acusando a dala de revelación de
Secret because of that issue of the
Secreto por por el tema ese de las
talk that or uncle about the subject of
conversa que o sea tío lo del tema de
the conversations is also that it is the
las conversaciones también es que es la
host in the lawsuit with
[__] en el pleito con
Naya, well there is one thing that you don't know.
naya bueno es que hay una cosa que no os
I can say clearly that there is one thing
puedo decir claro es que hay una cosa
that I can't tell you but well,
que no os puedo decir pero bueno lo de
gender violence is worth it, he put it later
violencia de género vale la puso luego
He tried to reopen that one, I don't know if two or three
esa la intentó reabrir no sé si dos tres
four times I don't know how many times it's worth it later
cuatro veces no sé las veces vale luego
the dog's civilian where the condemned one
el civil del perro donde la la condenada
that the dog that does not have to return
que tiene que devolver el perro que no
He served that sentence, I don't know if he paid.
cumplió esa sentencia no sé si pagó
money paid thing I don't know what I would pay
dinero pagó cosa no sé lo que pagaría
there okay I know the dog doesn't
ahí vale sé que el perro no lo
He brought back the topic of the minors. That was it.
devolvió el tema de las menores Ese fue
the mother who went to the police station
la madre la que fue a la comisaría a
putting it on is worth it to Dalas It's not that I have
ponérsela vale al Dalas No es que me he
I found out that they are minors, I don't know what
enterado que están menores no sé qué
Okay
vale
mm this is from the father if I'm not mistaken, man
mm esta del padre si no me equivoco tío
If I'm not mistaken, this is from my father, uncle.
si no me equivoco esta del padre tío yo
I would swear that first they gave her a penalty
juraría que primero la pusieron penal
But maybe I'm getting confused
pero es que a lo mejor me estoy liando
with something else eh Because there are so many but
con otra cosa eh Porque son tantas pero
I would swear that this one was put first
yo juraría que esta primero la pusieron
penalty and then then they went for the
penal y luego entonces Fueron por los
civil I think eh But I don't remember well
civil creo eh Pero no me acuerdo bien
because if I'm not mistaken the mother put
porque si no me equivoco la madre puso
one by
uno por
harassment
acoso
when what happened in a Dallas video
cuando cuando pasó lo de un vídeo Dallas
He made a video and the mother put one
le hizo un vídeo y la madre puso una
complaint for harassment and had to go to that
denuncia por acoso Y tuvo que ir d que
I think it was the time when
me parece que era la época en la que
Dallas was I don't know if in Ireland or or
Dallas estaba no sé si en Irlanda o o
be that
sea esa
also the problem with Dallas is that I
también el problema con Dallas es que yo
I don't know why he doesn't do it but he doesn't advertise
no sé por qué no lo hace pero no anuncia
every time the others lose I don't know
cada vez que que pierden los otros no sé
Why don't you do that? You don't know how to sell that.
por qué no hace eso no sabe vender eso
really eh or already forget about the subject is
en verdad eh o pasa ya del tema está
But all these when they are gone
teado Pero todas estas cuando se han ido
losing or whatever it is not
perdiendo o lo que sea no lo
says what else What else Javi Bueno then
dice qué más Qué más Javi Bueno luego
They have the issue of the clash in the
tienen el tema del encontronazo en la
street that these are cross-accusations that
calle que eso son denuncias cruzadas que
I think they stood still until
creo que se quedaron paradas hasta que
the dog's problem will be solved
se solucionara lo del perro del
All yes but the one of an rebun is not with
todo Sí pero la de an rebun no es con
they, that is, we are talking about them
ellos o sea estamos hablando de los
cases with them well a lot a
casos con ellos bueno un montón un
lots of stories should be
montón de historias dasas debería
show the videos of their trials as
enseñar los vídeos de sus juicios como
they did to you Javi But then you are
hicieron contigo Javi Pero entonces eres
just like them
igual que ellos
No, I don't think that when they take out the
no yo creo que cuando ellos sacan los
videos and things from the trial no I mean
vídeos y las cosas del juicio no O sea
I think that when for example the
yo creo que cuando por ejemplo salió el
video of my trial on knife, the one from knife
vídeo del juicio mío en faca el de faca
who has the same lawyer as her and
que tiene el mismo abogado que ella y
who shares and who is a friend You know that you
que comparte y que es amigo Sabes que te
I say the funny thing is that he is still happy
digo lo divertido es que aún y se alegra
that his father won a case for
de que su padre ganara un caso por
insults not defamation Because everything
insultos no difamación Porque todo lo
what I said was true and it was proven before
que dije era cierto y se demostró ante
many
muchos
judges good He affirms in his move
jueces bueno Afirma en su en su movida
Okay, that's why she's sentenced to prison for two
vale por eso está condenada a cárcel dos
times Ah okay here what is here what is
veces Ah vale aquí lo que está aquí lo
what Dallas is saying is
que está diciendo el Dallas es
basically that this does not remove the
básicamente que que esto no quita el
case of the bottom of the whole case of
caso de el fondo de todo el caso de
they are worth it And now the list tries
ellos vale Y ahora la lista intenta
divert tension by pretending it is
desviar la tensión fingiendo que es
defamation Yes yes we already saw you and also
difamación Sí sí ya te vimos y además
insults I said for hitting someone
insultos que dije por haber pegado a una
woman my girlfriend who is recording
mujer mi novia la cual está grabando
recorded on video and was even convicted
grabado en vídeo y encima fue condenado
His father has already been to jail twice.
ya dos veces a cárcel su padre anda que
Then she goes around being a feminist, but
luego va de feminista ella eh pero
Don't worry, soon you will be condemned
tranqui que pronto será condenado una
third time and his brother also takes a hit
tercera vez y su hermano también [__]
the thing about the brother, the thing about the brother, I don't
lo del hermano lo del hermano no me
I agree how it was, or rather, because yes,
acuerdo cómo era o sea porque sí que
there was part of the first sentence of the
hubo parte de la primera sentencia de lo
of the dog of the first criminal sentence
del perro de la primera sentencia penal
that there was part of the first sentence
que hubo parte de la primera sentencia
dog penalty in which they appear
penal de lo del perro en la que salen
They are now in the second best position
ellos ahora en la segunda mejor parado
no because in this second one the mother
no porque en esta segunda a la madre la
release the mother they put something like that on her
suelva a la madre le ponen algo así como
that obviously
que evidentemente
How do you say the word that
Cómo se dice la palabra que
evidently she was sure to be knowledgeable
evidentemente seguro que era conocedora
of the acts that were
de los de los actos que estaban
committing her daughter and her husband but at
cometiendo su hija y su marido pero al
being the mother or being the wife
ser al ser la madre o al ser la esposa
Well no, they don't condemn you, I don't know how
pues no no te condenan no sé cómo se
call that I don't know if it's in coverage or
llama eso no sé si es en cubrimiento o
I don't know the truth but they don't condemn you
no sé la verdad pero que no te condenan
because he is your husband and she is your daughter no
porque es tu marido y es tu hija no
You know what I'm telling you, I mean it can't be in
sabes lo que te digo O sea no puede e en
Spain you yes yes
España tú si si
He covered up nothing and they won't condemn you, okay? And
encubría nada que no te condenan vale Y
I think the sentences were lesser
creo que las condenas eran menores las
of miar and that of the father I think they were
de miar y la del padre creo que eran
lower than those of the first sentence
menores que las de la primera sentencia
Okay, but what
vale Pero lo que
Yes, but what really turned out worse for him
sí pero lo que sí que que le salió peor
is that in the sentence there is a pronounci
es que en la sentencia hay un pronunci
at the end of that
al final de que se
chase a possible fake
persiga un posible falso
testimony from this Emilio and
testimonio por parte de El tal Emilio y
the brother who is like an uncle you have brought in
el hermano que es como tío habéis metido
The son also goes as far as this goes.
también al hijo en esto hasta ahí llega
your
vuestro
conflict be
conflicto sea
why have you brought the
porque haber metido aquí al
son you know And then I think if
hijo sabes Y entonces creo si
I think that if they ratify the sentence of the
creo que si ratifican la sentencia de la
Provincial Court Now when it comes out
audiencia provincial Ahora cuando salga
the resource would then be initiated
el recurso Entonces se iniciaría un
procedure to check for false
procedimiento para ver si hay falso
testimony or not is that I do not remember what
testimonio o no es que no recuerdo lo
that the brother testified but it sounds familiar to me
que testificó el hermano pero me suena
No, it didn't turn out very well either.
que no a que no salió muy bien tampoco
that testifies what happens that that click does not happen
esa testifica lo pasa que ese clck no lo
I think they have put that click on Facua, I don't think so.
han puesto creo en facua ese click no lo
have put
han puesto
I think this is the whole life.
creo Total que esto es toda la vida
arguing, eh, man, my goodness
pleiteando eh tío madre mía
Ask yourself, my dear, why they only make you
plantéate querida Por qué solo te hacen
case in networks If you talk about me while
caso en redes Si hablas de mí mientras
that nobody cares about your life You continue
que a nadie le importa tu vida Tú sigues
in the same situation as 10 years ago or
en la misma situación que hace 10 años o
worse I am a thousand times better than when
peor yo estoy mil veces mejor que cuando
tea
te
I knew envy is very bad but it is
conocí la envidia es muy mala pero es
It is not about being better or worse.
que no se trata de estar mejor o peor se
It's about turning the page
trata de que hay que pasar página
no, I don't know, that's what I'm telling you.
no no sé es que yo es lo que te digo O
be it to me tell me and these people send me
sea a m dime y esta gente me mandan
the mother's tweet, that is, not a month has passed
tweet de la madre o sea no pasa un mes
They send me tweets from the mother
que me mandan tweet de la madre
seriously insulted by one of the
insultándolo gravemente alguno de los
two and and he doesn't he doesn't mention them or rather
dos y y él no él no las menciona o sea
He only comes out to talk about them
él solamente sale a hablar de ellas
when they are and there are many things that are not
cuando son y hay muchas cosas que no
mentions what I'm telling you, man
menciona es lo que os estoy diciendo tío
either
o
be Dallas and I think that's a
sea el Dallas y yo creo que eso es un
error because playing as they play the
error porque jugando como juegan el
Dallas doesn't announce every complaint.
Dallas no va anunciando cada denuncia
that they put on you and they don't accept them or they don't
que le ponen y y no se las admiten o no
They win, they don't announce all of them, I think.
las ganan no las anuncia todas yo creo
that will now say a few
que ahora irá diciendo unas cuantas
because there have been procedures that have
porque ha habido procedimientos que han
set against him and and they
puesto contra él y y se los
they have
han
It's good that he tells it, okay? But he has
e bueno que lo cuente él vale Pero ha
there have been a few things that
habido habido unas cuantas de cosas que
He hasn't told, I don't know why he's not going to.
él no ha contado no sé por qué no lo va
counting uncle every time they put one on you
contando tío cada vez que te pongan una
report and you lose it Put a tit
denuncia y te la pierdan Pon un tet
even if you know
aunque sea sabes
Yes Bruno I think he will.
sí Bruno Yo creo que él sí lo va a
making envy is very bad but hey
hacer la envidia es muy mala pero Oye
that if you have had to resort to the
que si has tenido que recurrir a la
justice so that it has to go up more
justicia para que tenga que subir más
videos about you, then don't worry, with
vídeos sobre ti pues tranquila que con
I will gladly do it and I will continue watching my
gusto lo haré y seguiré viendo mi
living my life right after
viviendo mi vida justo después a
difference from you who have been here for 10 years
diferencia de ti que llevas 10 años
Living only for me, you never get tired, uncle
viviendo solo para mí no te cansas tío
that a decade eh with this topic eh
que una década eh con este tema eh
It's a decade, man, do you know what a decade is?
es una década tío sabéis lo que es una
decade is a decade
década es una década
man and now this occurs to me and now
tío y ahora se me ocurre esto y ahora
I talk to this journalist and now I
hablo con este periodista y ahora me
I speak with the accounts of Javier Canino and
hablo con las cuentas de javiel canino y
I don't know who and I don't know how much and now I
no sé quién y no sé cuánto y ahora me
I talk to the delox and now I talk to myself
hablo con el delox y ahora me hablo con
Ricky and now I talk to her
el Ricky y ahora me hablo con la
Tania Bueno no
Tania Bueno no
I know deep down you know that that money is not
sé en el fondo sabes que ese dinero no
It doesn't cover you, it's not that they are already topics
te cubre ni es que ya ya son temas
even from the beginning I mean how do you
incluso de principios no O sea cómo te
you are going to talk to a Tania that Tania
vas a hablar con una Tania que la Tania
that they have met in person
úa que han quedado en persona
eh And with a delo or with a
eh Y con un delo o con un
Ricky So it's already clear, so it's not anymore.
Ricky O sea ya es eh claro o sea ya no
you don't have you don't keep your your
no tienes tu no mantienes tu tu
ideology or your feelings your
ideología o tus sentimientos tus
thoughts your principles are already yours
pensamientos tus principios ya es tu
Dallas base If a person gets along with
base Dallas Si una persona se lleva con
I hate Dallas because of Antonia
Dallas lo odio porque a delos la Antonia
He put t on him, messing with him too
le puso t metiéndose con él también
Who is this character I don't know how much
Quién es este personaje no sé cuánto
messing with him, what a person and
metiéndose con él no vaya persona y
Now at the moment when Delox fights
ahora en el momento que delox se pelea
with Dallas follows him, of course, and the people
con Dallas lo sigue tío claro y la gente
who supports this what he thinks is
que apoya esto qué es lo que piensa es
that I would love
que me encantaría
knowing it is that I don't understand it, these are things
saberlo es que no lo entiendo son cosas
that I'm leaving Well, it's that I fight
que yo se me va Pues es que yo me peleo
with so many people along for this no
con tanta gente a lo largo de de esto no
of the gossip and suddenly Maybe With
del salseo y de repente A lo mejor Con
How many people have we fought with in a year?
cuánta gente nos hemos peleado en un año
maybe after two months you will
a lo mejor luego a los dos meses se te
forget it and go on to something else, even do it
olvida y aí a otra cosa incluso haces la
passes no I mean fate you me with drone me
pases no O sea fate tú yo con dron me
I said everything, eh, with the drone we said to each other
dije de todo eh con dron nos dijimos de
You all liked how well I get along
todo fiste tú lo bien que yo me llevo
with
con
drone I'm not there I'm not going to stop until
dron no estoy ahí no voy a parar hasta
that you don't get
que no te te
sink deep into the bottom you know that money
hunda en el fondo sabes que ese dinero
It doesn't even cover what you spent on it
no te cubre ni lo que te gastaste en el
bald, trembling man with a Smurf voice who
calvo tembloroso con voz de pitufo que
He is your lawyer but I hope that at least
es tu abogado pero espero que al menos
use it to hire a good psychologist
lo uses para contratar un buen psicólogo
Let's see if this allows you to live your life a little bit longer.
a ver si así te permite Vivir tu vida un
day and calm down, there are four more coming
día y tranquila que se vienen cuatro
documentaries sorry for not responding
documentales siento no haber respondido
before but I was busy enjoying my
antes pero estaba ocupado disfrutando mi
life something that you unfortunately cannot
vida algo que tú por desgracia no puedes
do Aha soon don't worry it's already done
hacer Ajá prontito no te preocupes ya ha
been condemned many times to
sido condenada muchas veces a
see okay This is the topic
ver vale Esto es lo del tema
of incredible amount of lies that
de increíble cantidad de mentiras que
They say the case of the aggression look here
dicen el caso de la agresión mira aquí
there is that thing about that subject
está lo del tema ese
the case of the assault has not yet
el caso de la agresión aún no ha
finished In fact it was on pause until
terminado De hecho estaba en pausa hasta
that you just sentenced them in the case
que terminas de condenar les en el caso
The dog will soon condemn this guy
del perro pronto condenarán a este tipo
also for aggression which is also
también por agresión que además está
recorded on video, so I think that the thing about
grabado en vídeo o sea creo que lo del
the topic of aggression is that of the conflict of the
tema de agresión ese del conflicto de la
street I think they were put
calle creo que fueron se pusieron
cross-complaints I think they went to the
denuncias cruzadas creo que fueron a la
police station And both accused each other, that is
comisaría Y ambos se acusaron o sea
both sides accused each other
ambas partes se acusaron mutuamente el
one to the other I think it was something like that
uno al otro creo que fue algo así
some enjoy and others are condemned
algunos disfruta y otros son condenados
to
a
prison But Andorra and the United States
cárcel Pero andorra y a Estados Unidos
They no longer enter
ya no entran
eh all with criminal records since
eh todos con antecedentes penales desde
the groom until the
el novio hasta el
Father, the way life takes you, eh, since
padre la vuelta que da la vida eh desde
2016 trying my ex's obsession
2016 intentando la obsesionada de mi ex
destroy my career and in the end it ends
destruirme la carrera y al final termina
She and her family were sentenced to prison and
ella y su familia condenadas a prisión y
Now they only pay attention to him when they talk.
ahora solo le hacen casito para hablar
from Dallas so much that they tried to get me in
de Dallas tanto que intentaron meterme
in prison and in the end he was given the
en la cárcel y al final se le dio la
back and they ended up in jail and
vuelta y en la cárcel acabaron ellos y
now he starts to rejoice for having
ahora se pone a alegrarse por haber
won a case of insults to the father
ganado un caso de insultos al padre
just after he assaulted a
justo después de que agrediera a una
woman and it's all recorded that copy what
mujer y está todo grabado que copi qué
that you have told me
que me habéis
sent Yes, I already saw this about the
mandado Sí esto ya lo vi lo del
journalist I've already seen this one, José
periodista Este sí ya lo vi José
It was yesterday
está Ayer fue
mood they are all condemned several times
nimo están todos ellos condenados varias
sometimes soon the brother's thing
veces prontito lo del hermano
I have also been your whole life
también llevo siendo su vida entera los
last 10 years he only surrounds himself with people
últimos 10 años solo se rodea de gente
who speaks of me for me and through me
que habla de mí para mí y por mí su
session level knows no limit and also
nivel sesión no conoce límite y además
They only pay attention to him if he talks about
solo le dan atención si habla de
This video has to be me
mí Este vídeo lo tiene que
erase we are all
borrar estamos todos
Calm down. Look, it's the one in blue, right now.
tranquilos Mirad es el de azul eh ahora
comes from the side Look
viene por el lado Mirad
Look what a move that was.
Mirad qué movida fue esa
eh What a midot it was
eh Qué midot fue es
Hey, I saw Skylar yelling at Javi.
eh vi a mí a skylar increpando a Javi
about not having realized that
sobre que no se había enterado de que
had lost how burned it is by
había perdido lo ardida que está por
God is another very funny aunt
Dios es otra muy graciosa la tía
pretending that she was part of it Oh but
fingiendo que ella formaba parte Ay pero
Do you know what Mia has deleted?
sabéis lo que ha borrado Mia se me ha
forgotten it has deleted it that's why not
olvidado lo ha borrado por eso no lo
we commented Mia today, damn what
hemos comentado Mia hoy ostia qué
ridiculous or has Mia deleted it today
ridículo o lo ha borrado Mía hoy ha
put it on
puesto lo
from the capture this one that she uploads from a
de la captura esta que sube ella de un
message from Dallas that every time the
mensaje de Dallas que cada vez que la
upload has a few likes Good
sube tiene unos cuantos de likes Bueno
Well, today I uploaded it and it had 50 likes.
pues hoy lo había subido tenía 50 likes
has deleted it we have not seen it we have
la ha borrado no lo hemos visto hemos
We've been through Twitter and haven't seen it.
pasado el Twitter y no lo hemos visto
that which has it
eso que lo ha
deleted can you please remind him?
borrado se lo podéis recordar porfa que
the journalist has forgotten
se le ha olvidado a la periodista
He just took advantage of the fact that the father is not
solo se aprovechó de que el padre no es
public to make the legal trap of
público para hacer la trampa legal de
say that he had never insulted me
decir que él nunca me había insultado el
Father has insulted Dallas, eh, I mean
padre sí ha insultado a Dallas eh o sea
Yes, he has told me quite a few things.
sí le ha dicho cosas bastante yo las
I have it there
tengo por ahí
I think I have it somewhere around here.
Creo la tengo por ahí
literal In any case they have given me
literal En todo caso me han dado
content for four more videos Although
contenido para cuatro vídeos más Aunque
Maybe something else I don't know what they celebrate
capaz y algo más no sé queé celebran
because everyone is going to remember
porque todo el mundo se va a acordar de
how they have been sentenced to prison and
cómo han sido condenados a cárcel y
On top of that, they attacked a woman.
encima agredieron a una mujer está
recorded a video and are eager to have it
grabado un vídeo además son ganas de que
I answered you uncle. Sorry for taking so long.
este te conteste tío Perdón por tardar
I was busy responding to failures
en responder a fracasados estaba ocupado
while I get paid for partying for going
mientras me pagan por fiesta por ir de
party to trip with expenses
fiesta a viaje con gastos
I would pay if I were Dallas honestly
pagado yo si fuera Dallas sinceramente
If I were Dallas, honestly, I wouldn't be.
yo si fuera Dalas sinceramente yo no no
would make him
le haría
Videos are a desire for Dallas to
vídeos son ganas de que Dallas le
answer and play the victim again
conteste y hacerse la víctima de nuevo
yes or like the loop no But if I were
sí o como el bucle no Pero yo si fuera
Dallas no
Dallas no
I wouldn't make a video for him actually, eh?
le no le haría vídeo en realidad eh sa
look at me
mira que yo
I would enjoy the gossip no
me disfrutaría del chisme no
but I wouldn't have given it to him, I wouldn't have given it to him either.
pero yo no le yo no le hubiera puesto ni
This laugh, well maybe yes, no, never.
Esta rista bueno a lo mejor sí no nunca
I know it's very easy to say it from such a no
sé yo es muy fácil decirlo desde tal no
but this is
pero es que esto
Now this is not going to be commented on or
ya es que esto no lo va a comentar ni
Peter won't even remind him of it tomorrow.
Peter mañana ni se lo va a recordar más
Nobody pays him anything and he goes outside and waits for it
nadie nada págale y fuera y a esperar lo
Of the dog, in fact, I would say, well, about the
del perro de hecho yo diría Bueno lo del
dog and well, wait for the dog
perro y bueno a esperar lo del perro
but what you have to do is tell him
pero lo que tiene que hacerle es contar
always what what not
siempre lo que lo que no
they win that's what he should do
ganan eso es lo que tendría que hacer él
always uncle take out everything that every time
siempre tío sacar todo lo que cada vez
that not all the little things beat him
que no le ganan a él todas las cositas
that they have tried to put on him that they have not
que le han intentado poner que no le han
cattle, take it out and announce it
ganado irlo sacando y lo vas anunciando
Javi you're on your Prime What's up Neri
Javi estás en tu Prime Qué pasa Neri
As
Cómo
we are the twit elite mocked
estamos la élite de twit se burló de
nimmu but it's that I and given at 3 of
nimmu pero es que me and dado a las 3 de
the morning eh I don't know if I'm going to come go
la mañana eh No sé si voy a venga va
Let's see if he likes me.
Vamos a verlo ver si me cmar que n
short ones are 8 minutes long and look at
cortitos son de 8 minut encima c Mira
above This cli is mine ok with the
encima Este cli es mío vale con los
Most popular streams at the moment
Stream más populares en el momento o sea
that is, nimu
o sea nimu
eh nimu after having wanted
eh nimu después de haber querido
defeat the elite now in its
derrotar a la élite ahora ya en su
change of side new No, because of that
cambio de bando nuevo No pues por lo
seen when he arrived in Andorra he wanted to do
visto cuando llegó a andorra quiso hacer
an approach Hey I don't know if
un acercamiento Oye no sé si
I have
tengo
He wanted to call the youtubers from
eh quiso Llamar a los youtubers de
Andorra when he moved
andorra cuando se mudó
changorama if they are supporting those of the
changorama si están apoyando los de los
from Joan Plana those of Pilar Vera O
del Joan plana los de la Pilar Vera O
They are already people who are no longer part of the team.
sea ya son gente que ya el equipito no
there is
hay
you know more, there is no more
más sabes no hay más
dasas does not have to put the sentence in
dasas no tiene que poner la sentencia en
four videos Yes but it is putting the
cuatro vídeos Sí pero es poner la
sentence at the end of the video is made
sentencia al final del vídeo sea hace
any video and at the end it puts the
cualquier vídeo y al final pone la
image of the sentence and outside or me
imagen de la sentencia y fuera o sea yo
I wouldn't give the slightest attention to it
no le daría la más mínima bola la
true seg continue with the processes
verdad seg continuar con los procesos
important and out you know you think that the
importantes y fuera sabes crees que el
team can win the Champions League Yes
equipo puede ganar la Champions Sí
yes with auron and with wanted approach
sí con auron y con quiso acercamiento
but I don't know But you wanted to destroy
pero no lo sé Pero has querido destruir
to the elite And now you put yourself when you
a la élite Y ahora te pones cuando te
you move to andorra to try
mudas a andorra a intentar O sea al
In the end, I Aimo and Adelo, what I see is
final yo aimo y adelo lo que los veo es
like what
como que
Ah I don't know how to describe it because in
Ah no sé cómo describirlo porque en
Reality, nimo, yes, she has been famous. No, it's not.
realidad nimo sí ha sido famosa No lo
What's happening? It sank
que pasa que se hundió
but but in the case of Delo I that the
pero pero en el caso de delo yo que los
I see how he wants to join the
veo como que quiere juntarse a los
famous no I don't know it's something very very rare
famosos no no sé es algo muy muy raro
very Freaky for example Rubius Roblis and
muy Freaky por ejemplo Rubius roblis y
all that she wanted in the past
todo eso ella en el pasado quería
defeat or overthrow IB by whatever means
derrotar o derrocar de lo que sea a IB
from his position among the Twitch elite that
de su posición de la élite de Twitch que
wanted to make a revelation with Dallas with
quería hacer una revelión con Dallas con
deluxe and all that for what To defeat
delux y todo eso para qué Para derrotar
to the Twitch elite that seems to me a
a la élite de Twitch que me parece una
stupidity In fact I a year ago
estupidez De hecho yo hace un año atrás
I made a video for this elite that
Yo le hice un video a esta élite que
Honestly, that video was a complete
sinceramente Ese video era una completa
garbage because well it seems like a
basura porque Bueno me parece una
stupid things that everyone says
estupides que todo el mundo diga la
Twitch elite everyone drinks
élite de Twitch todo el mundo bebe
blood that I don't know what they are
sangre que no sé qué cosa que son
Illuminati and all that is basically a
illuminatis y todo eso básicamente es un
famous group and that's it, nothing more.
grupo famosos y ya está nada más no
We are in Hollywood but what happens
estamos en Hollywood pero lo que pasa
This is where she wanted to collaborate with
acá es que ella quería colaborar con
people whom she loved
personas que las cuales ella quería
defeat in the past because as I say
derrotar en el pasado porque como digo
supposedly they were illuminati and
supuestamente ellos eran illuminatis y
that are part of the Twitch Cos that
que son parte en laita de Twitch Cos que
I tell you for example I want
yo te diga por ejemplo yo quiero
defeat a president of such a country
derrotar a un presidente de tal país
For example, ripe and up to date
Como por ejemplo maduro y al día
Next I join him for a drink
siguiente me junto con él a tomarme unas
beers is like it's kind of stupid
cervezas es como que es medio estúpido
what I'm saying basically like this
lo que estoy diciendo básicamente así
That's good, I'm going to put it a little bit
que bueno lo voy a poner es un poco
stupid that wouldn't you be a little michelo
estúpido eso no serías un poco michelo
clip that which That clip was uploaded by Javi
clip que la cual Ese clip lo subió Javi
oliveira on his Twitter account that
oliveira en su cuenta de Twitter que la
which nmo threw it away for copyright But
cual nmo se lo tiró por copyright Pero
Well, our friendly neighbor here in Spain
bueno nuestro amigo vecino acá en España
kit 2 uploaded it re-uploaded it on his channel in
kit 2 lo subió lo resubi en su canal en
YouTube So I'm going to
YouTube Así que lo voy a
put Ah right luar I didn't remember it is
poner Ah verdad luar no me acordaba es
true luar is true Come on then
verdad luar es verdad Venga pues
While I wait for the script to come and go
mientras que espero el guion venga va
Would you collaborate with any new streamer?
colaborarías con algún nuevo streamer A
see I'm not closed to collaborations The
ver no estoy cerrada a colaboraciones El
The problem is that on the one hand I don't
problema es que por un lado no me
They invite collaborations because I moved away
invitan a colaboraciones porque me alejé
from the little world and well and I lost contact
del mundito y bueno y perdí el contacto
with people because no no no he doesn't like them
con la gente porque no no no le cae bien
the issue is that they don't like you
sea el tema es que no les cae bien no
They want to and on the other hand I am not
quieren y por otro lado no estoy
meeting many streamers with whom
conociendo muchos streamers con quien
Let's see, let's go for 10 seconds
colaborar A ver vamos 10 segundos de
Clip and she already told the first lie
Clip y ya dijo la primera mentira ella
was never disconnected in this
nunca estuvo desconectada en este
little world in quotes, I don't know why
mundillo entre comillas no s porque le
Mundillo says if it's literally YouTube
dice mundillo si literalmente es YouTube
Twitch eh x and kit I don't know why it says
Twitch eh x y kit no sé por qué dice
little world but well it's her thing
mundillo pero bueno es cosa de ella ella
at that time in which I was
en ese momento en la cual estaba
depressed by the massive hate that she receives
deprimida por el hate masivo que le
people threw it away because of her
tiraba la gente por la culpa de ella por
the mistakes she made
las cagadas que cometió ella se
transformed into a white thing I don't
transformó en una cosa blanca no me
I agree, what is it called here? I'll send it to you.
acuerdo cómo se le llama acá le mando
a photo so you know what it is
una foto la cual para que sepa de lo que
I am it is true He had a time like
estoy es verdad Tuvo una época como
hippi is true she speaks in that
hippi es verdad hablando ella en ese
moment when I was thinking
momento cuando estaba recapacitando
when it was becoming a new
cuando se Estaba volviendo en una nueva
animu she was not disconnected the
animu ella no estaba desconectada las
social networks she responded to the
redes sociales ella respondía a los
messages for example we have the post that
mensajes por ejemplo tenemos el post que
Sprint threw him a little bit
le tiró Sprint que le tiró un poco de
[ __ ], cheer up, saying that cheer up is good.
[__] a nimo diciendo que nimo bueno es
a heavy piece of [ __ ] that lies in the
una pesada de [__] que se miente en el
problems and everything Yes yes of course it wasn't
problemas y todo Sí sí claro no estaba
disconnected from networks, of course
desconectada de redes que claro es
It's true that he says no, it's not that he was
verdad es que dice no no es que estaba
disconnected from networks no, I wasn't
desconectada de redes no no estaba
disconnected from networks that didn't want
desconectada de redes que no querían
with you all that later I remember that
contigo todo eso después me acuerdo que
there was the fight with Dallas dasas started to
hubo la pelea con Dallas dasas empezó a
to curse a person who got involved himself
putear a una persona que mismo se metió
and he defended him with something I don't know
y lo defendió que que no sé qué cosa
Well she was never disconnected in
Bueno ella nunca estuvo desconectada en
that world just took a
ese mundo simplemente se tomó un
Twitch break only a month and
descanso de Twitch solamente un mes y lo
What she says is that she lost contacts
que dice ella es que perdió contactos
when I was disconnected in that world
cuando estaba desconectada en ese mundo
not the only way to lose those
no la única forma de perder esos
contacts is to make a tremendous mistake
contactos es hacer una [__] tremenda
Like what she has done, for example.
Como por ejemplo lo que ha hecho ella
For example, I had contact with Rickyedit.
por ejemplo con rickyedit tuve contacto
and I did a collaboration with him.
y hice una colaboración con él vos
You think he's one of the few streamers
pensás que es uno de los pocos streamers
with whom I collaborated lately is
con los que colaboré últimamente va es
the only one I believe apart from what is not
el único creo aparte de delo que no
I am very willing to collaborate with
estoy muy dispuesta a colaborar con
people I don't know I told him
gente que no conozco yo le dije a el
Deed, I don't know if he finally did that event.
deed no sé si al final hizo ese evento
I imagine not because I don't
Yo me imagino que no porque a mí no me
none arrived
llegó ninguna
invitation but I to the First and
invitación pero yo al de Primera y
last time not the first time but the
última vez no la primera no pero la
last time I asked to collaborate was at
última vez que pedí colaborar fue al
Dead I asked the Dead if he could participate
Dead le dije al Dead si podía participar
in the backshot backshot challenge
en el desafío de backshot backshot
roulette in Minecraft or something like that the point
roulet en Minecraft o algo así el punto
It's that I actually gave him Delox
es que yo le di en realidad delox
You think people like you?
ustedes creen que le cae bien a la gente
delox or rather because I believe that delo
delox o sea porque yo creo que delo
It has to be around Andorra.
tiene que ser por ahí por andorra se ha
placed there to live in Andorra and goes after
puesto allí vivir andorra y va detrás de
all the famous youtubers not in
todos los youtubers así famositos no en
plan as a Freaky fan or rather I think that
plan como Freaky fan o sea yo creo que
I don't know, except for those who are like that.
no no sé quitando a los que son así un
little like him not Ricky And I don't see that
poco como él no el Ricky Y eso no veo yo
to the others as very receptive
a los otros como muy receptivos
I didn't tell the one after not to talk to him because
no dije al de después de no hablarle por
a long time because well he is in his
mucho tiempo porque bueno él está en su
wave and I'm in mine I told him Che
onda y yo estoy en la mía le dije Che
there will be room for a funada there will be
habrá espacio para una funada habrá
space for a funada at your event
espacio para una funada en tu evento de
Back ret and he said yes without any problem
Back ret y me dijo sí sin problema
When the event is here I'll invite you or something
cuando esté el evento te invito o algo
So when I came to Andorra, all of it
así yo cuando vine a andorra toda toda
naive, I sent a message to
ingenua toda ingenua le mandé mensaje a
and I sent a message to Roble and I sent him
y le mandé mensaje a roble y le mandé
message to Rubius Yes yes ro and Rubi already
mensaje a Rubius Sí sí ro y Rubi ya
They are excited about you Yes yes but she
están contigo ilusionada Sí sí pero ella
aspiring to little aspiring to little
aspirando a poco a aspirando a poco a
Rubiu oak d me knows several streamers like this
roble rubiu d me sa varios streamers así
as if I knew they were from Andorra
como de que yo sabía que eran de andorra
to get together for a coffee or something
para para juntarnos tomar un café o algo
They hit me with more epic ignorance than you
me pegaron a ignorada más épica que te
you can imagine well I can understand No
puedas imaginar bueno puedo entender No
we have been the best friends in the world or
hemos sido los mejores panas del mundo o
I barely know them at all but I don't
sea apenas los conozco algo pero no les
I spoke to them because I was Rubius and Roble.
hablé por ser Rubius y roble les hablé
I spoke to someone else for I don't know who else
por no sé quién más le hablé a alguien
I spoke to him more but I don't remember who else
más le hablé pero no recuerdo quién más
I remember them both, that is, I spoke to them
me acuerdo de ellos dos o sea les hablé
because they were genuinely the only ones
porque genuinamente eran las únicas
people I knew who lived in
personas que conocía que vivían en
andorra and to Lauro not to Lauro not to Lauro
andorra e a Lauro no a Lauro no a Lauro
No, because I never shared it with him.
no porque a él sí que nunca compartí
words but for example with Rubius and
palabras pero por ejemplo con Rubius y
With Robl everything is always very good and we chat
con robl siempre todo muy bien y y charl
with them and such at the time and I
con ellos y tal en su momento y me
It seemed like he was pretty cool like
parecía que era bastante buena onda como
quite Not trust but enough
bastante No confianza pero suficiente
so I can send them a message
como para poder mandarles un mensaje
For me the two people who reject the
para mí las dos personas que rechazar la
nimmu invitation they realized that
invitación nimmu se dieron cuenta de que
Nimmu is a hypocrite because she joins
nimmu es una hipócrita porque se junta
with a person who, for example,
con una persona la cual por ejemplo
Dallas is a person who is a
Dallas es una persona la cual está un
a little bad in the head accuses of a crime
poco mal en la cabeza acusa de un delito
falsely serious or a person without
grave falsamente ni una persona sin
tests such as eight snow and
pruebas como por ejemplo ocho nievo y
all that word that I can't say
tod esa palabra que no lo puedo decir
apart from that as I tell you it came together
aparte de eso como te digo que se juntó
with Dallas as I say is a person who
con Dallas como digo es una persona que
which includes a lot of poetry because well
la cual se mete mucho poem porque Bueno
It's very problematic and all that aside
es muy problemática y todo eso aparte
She thinks not that good as bco
ella piensa no de que bueno como bco
Roblex like bco Rubius already like 8 years ago
roblex como bco Rubius hace ya como s 8
months almost a year now, maybe I will accept it
meses casi ya un año capaz me acepte la
invitation as I say she lost
invitación como digo ella perdió
contacts Not because he left Twitch c
contactos No porque se fue de Twitch c
months and she's already lost contact
meses y ya está ella perdió contactos
because it is a very controversial issue No
porque es problemática muy polémica No
I think that he doesn't like me.
yo Es que creo que no cae bien Yo me
I imagine there will be a kind of cordiality
imagino que habrá como una cordialidad
over there
por allí
and you know it's there living in notes
e sabes está allí viviendo en notas
It will be like super heavy and all that but
estará como super pesado y eso pero
but the little dog of the youtubers but
pero el perrillo de los youtubers pero
the stray dog ​​does silly things
el perrillo sin dueño hace tonterías
says false things, adopts arguments, does not
dice cosas falas adopta da argumentos no
valid and this has happened several times
válidos y varias veces ha pasado eso por
We have that same reason for Ray
esa misma razón la tenemos a Ray
insulting me for a while we want it
insultándome durante un rato lo queremos
see or
ver o
Ray and his girlfriend attacking each other again
qué Ray y su novia otra vez atacándose
that person from Nimu left for example
se dejó esa persona de nimu por ejemplo
to Sprint What happened to Sprint Sprint
a Sprint Qué pasó con Sprint Sprint le
He said that Nimu is a [ __ ] fake.
dijo que nimu es una falsa de [__]
because he [ __ ] with Dallas and the moment that
porque se jó con Dallas y al momento que
He [ __ ] with Dallas at that moment I don't
se jó con Dallas en ese momento no me
I agree exactly when it was made
acuerdo exactamente Cuándo fue se hizo
the grenade because I was with Dallas and
la granada porque estaba con Dallas y
cone if you Che What's up I'm living
cono si le Che Qué onda estoy viviendo
In Andorra, if you ever want to stay
en andorra eh si algún día querés quedar
or go out for a coffee or something I don't know
o o salir a tomar un café o algo no sé
to have friends in Andorra, you understand?
para tener amigos en andorra me entendés
But no, well, I understand that maybe they
Pero no bueno entiendo que Quizás ellos
In their heads they must be thinking, wow, this is it.
En su cabeza deben pensar buah está
interested I don't know what I don't know how much it is
interesada no sé qué no sé cuánto está
Well, that is a pretty thought.
bien o sea es un pensamiento bastante
Normally I think that many people will have
normal yo creo que mucha gente se habrá
wanted to take advantage of and appropriate his fame
querido aprovechar y apropiar de su fama
then XD but it seems strange to me
entonces XD pero a mí me parece raro
because at that moment I was not there
porque yo en ese momento no estaba
streame I mean he was no longer a streamer he was
streame O sea ya no era streamer estaba
yes I dear I was not streaming and they leave
sí me caro yo no estaba streame y se van
to have a coffee with you, that is, no
a poner a tomar un café contigo o sea no
eh, it seems to me that I don't feel like it, it seems to me
eh me da a mí que no eh nimo me da a mí
that's when you got a little carried away
que ahí te te te viniste un poco arriba
You got a little carried away, but trust yourself.
te viniste un poco arriba pero fíate tú
how far removed they are from reality or
lo alejado que están de la realidad o
be in what
sea en qué
moment one thing is that you once
momento una cosa es que tú una vez
Living in Andorra, well, you try it.
viviendo en andorra pues ya tú intentes
Ok, if you are there in Andorra, take it with you.
vale estando allí en andorra llevarte
good with people and you have a network of
bien con la gente y tienes una red de
contacts not because you are leaving
contactos no porque Te lo vas
finding the ladería on the street
encontrando por la calle la ladería te
you approach, you say hello, but of course from there to
acercas saludas no pero claro de ahí a
from there to you sending him a message
de ahí a que tú le mandes un mensaje
to have a coffee what did you expect?
para tomar un café qué te esperabas que
Rubius was going to tell you to go drink
El Rubius te iba a decir de ir a tomar
a
un
coffee but not only that eh But
café pero ya no solamente eso eh Sino
that comes to mind for example
que se me viene la cabeza por ejemplo
when they give them here what ghost eh or what
cuando delos aquí qué fantasma eh o sea
They are exactly like Ricky in many ways.
son son clavados el el Ricky é en muchos
aspect of it here has been hinted at that
aspecto el el delo aquí ha insinuado que
the auron was going to go to the podcast that was going to go
el auron iba ir al podcast que iba a ir
the podcast that was going to be on the agenda was scheduled
al podca que iba a ir al poca se marcaba
c triple that freaks out eh guys I'm going to the bathroom
c triple que flipa eh chicos voy al baño
one second and we'll see more gossip I have
un segundo y vemos más chisme que tengo
here three or four
aquí tres o cuatro
little things to
cosillas al
that
qué
we have This is like this This is like this is it
tenemos Esto es así Esto es así ya está
Oh wait wait wait that's it now no no
Ay espera Espera espera eso ahora no no
I know if I really want that
sé si tengo mucha ganas de eso
eh I don't know if I'm really looking forward to that eh
eh No sé si tengo muchas ganas de eso eh
I hear Javi says I saw a clip why
escho qué Javi dice vi un clip por qué
I'm with him Oh yes yes I saw a clip I saw a
estoy con él Ah sí sí vi un clip vi un
clip and eh I don't know if I'm missing something because
clip y eh No sé si me falta algo porque
nothing, I go listening to things in parts
nada me voy escuchando cosas por partes
Well, no, I don't consume that, I don't see anything.
yo pues no No Consumo eso no veo nada yo
I didn't listen much either, just me.
tampoco escuché mucho yo solamente
I heard the clip where it says it's churr but
escuché el clip donde dice es churr pero
how is it possible that even the bride
cómo es posible que hasta la novia
churra the girlfriend supports him churra and what
churra la novia lo apoya churra y qué
wants me to support him is a slander
quiere que lo apoya a él es un difama
Also, first of all, I have
además además primero que yo tengo
personality wants my girlfriend to be
personalidad quiere que mi novia se
put it next to him and Dallas or so
ponga al lado de él y de Dallas o sea
I understand the point he makes.
Entiendo entiendo el punto que dice él
I do not agree clearly I understand what
no coincido claramente entiendo lo que
It means why I endorse everything
quiere decir de de Por qué avalo todo lo
what does raed say, error, I do not endorse everything
que dice raed error yo no avalo todo lo
What Raed says is that we are two people.
que dice raed somos dos personas
different based based Mister Neon a
diferentes basada basada Mister Neón un
kiss handsome Thank you very much Not today
beso guapo Muchísimas gracias Hoy no
we have put
hemos puesto
objective Today I don't have a clear objective
objetivo Hoy no tengo el objetivo claro
to see a
a ver un
objective today's objective is going to be a
objetivo el objetivo de hoy va a ser un
little survey
poco encuesta
Ok, today's goal is going to be a little bit
vale el objetivo de hoy va a ser un poco
I'm going to put the survey on a low note
encuesta lo voy a poner flojito
Okay, I'm going to put it soft so that
vale lo voy a poner flojito para que
remain accessible Okay and it will last only
quede accesible Vale y va a durar solo
It's only going to last 30 minutes, okay?
30 minutos solamente va a durar vale
because if you want it's 30 minutes, you think
porque si queréis son 30 minutos creéis
that
que
should be in prison in prison once
ra debería estar en pris en prisión una
season for
temporada para
calm down we have opinions and together
calmarse tenemos opiniones e en conjunto
sometimes we think the same and other times
a veces pensamos lo mismo y en otras
other times we differ So that's it
otras ocasiones diferimos Así que eso es
normal as I mean I have the age
normal como o sea yo tengo la edad
enough education enough to
suficiente la educación suficiente para
have reasoning
tener un razocinio
own I don't need to have someone to
propio No necesito tener a alguien para
that is guiding me where to go, not if
que me esté guiando por dónde ir no si
At one point I think he is a
en un momento yo pienso que él es un
idiot
boludo
he was wrong, he did not say
se ha equivocado no ha dicho
we differ
diferimos
We differ on x reason I tell him or she
diferimos por x cosa se lo digo o lo
I let you know No no it's not that differing is like
hago saber No no es que diferir es como
postpone defer is not I postpone has not
aplazar diferir no es difiero no ha
I meant to say, and if I don't agree and say
querido decir y si yo no coincido y digo
For me it seems like it's closed here.
Che para mí acá me parece está cerrado
as I have done many times in life
como lo hice muchas veces en la vida
real as in Stream that's okay okay
real como en Stream eso es una vale vale
Okay, but that's what he wants.
vale pero o sea lo que está queriendo
to say is that he does not agree with
decir es que no está de acuerdo con
many network things eh but that is not it
muchas cosas de red eh pero que no lo
He says in public so as not to burn it, no, that
dice en público para no quemarlo no que
He has already humiliated himself enough, he has already humiliated himself enough.
ya bastante se humilla que ya bastante
humiliation is a thing and second There is a
se humillar é cosa y segundo Hay un
a lot of things the guy does for me
montón de cosas que el tipo para mí hace
bad and obviously I'm in favor of him and
mal y obviamente estoy a favor de él y
also yes And also the poor one
también sí Y también eh el pobre el
poor almost all eh almost all is mine
pobre casi todas eh casi todas es mi
couple and if he is my partner because I
pareja y si es mi pareja porque yo lo
I choose with all the virtues and with
elijo con todas las virtudes y con
some defects they may have
algunos defectos que puedan tener
There, well, yes, some defects, eh, some
ahí Bueno sí algún defectillos eh algún
There are little defects. What is the girl's name?
defectillos hay Cómo se llama la chica
in maja eh I like her eh What's her name
en maja eh Me cae bien eh Cómo se llama
the girl what is the girl's name No
la muchacha cómo se llama la muchacha No
I know I choose it anyway
lo sé yo de todas formas lo elijo como
that tomorrow his partner will grab and be
que mañana la pareja de él agarre y sea
the number one fan of bad haters
la número uno fan de haters malitos de
no clearly no no but based Lorena
no claramente no no pero basada Lorena
there eh or so based if you put Tina
ahí eh o sea basada si se pone a Tina
I really like Tina Tina la la
Tina a mí me cae muy bien Tina la la
lores yes the lor follows the wigs to the
lores sí la lor sigue al al pelucas al
canine and Wilson because it is that the
canino y al Wilson porque es que la
It is true that we have to see how you count
verdad es que a ver como cuentas de
humor that will never happen it will never happen
humor eso no va a pasar nunca va a pasar
And surely she must differ too
Y seguramente ella también debe diferir
on a lot of topics that are not going to be discussed either
en un montón de temas que tampoco va a
come out and say it publicly because
salir a decirlo públicamente porque
What a humiliation she's giving you.
es vaya humillada que te está pegando la
relative RAE or that is
parienta RAE o sea
Agus my friend Agus says that she has ra
Agus mi amiga Agus dice que ra tiene
some small defects are fine, they are flaws that
algún defectillos vale son taras que
They come from Vale and and Rael comes with him
vienen de Vale y y y rael le viene con
some defects but she
algún defectillos pero que ella lo
If you want it like this, it's okay that you have chosen it like this.
quiere así vale que lo ha escogido Así
that he wants it that way but that obviously
que lo quiere así pero que evidentemente
he's not going to burn it in public
no lo va a quemar en público
Vasada guys we have the Instagram of de
vasada chicos tenemos el Instagram de de
Agustina to follow her partner and is
Agustina para seguirla su pareja y es
It is also your support, it is your company
también es su sostén es su compañía
have children whatever and it's not going to
tienen hijos lo que sea y no va a
defenestrate through the networks being their
defenestrar por las redes siendo su
couple and choosing day by day PR then
pareja y eligiendo lo día a día PR luego
Once home, he calmly tells her
ya en casa pues le dice tranquilamente
Hey Ray, you might have gone too far.
Oye Ray que lo mismo te has pasado un
little threatening a baby eh RAE RAE calm
poco amenazando un bebé eh RAE RAE calma
Calm down, they might not do much for me.
calma que lo mismo no me hacen mucha
Thank you for the photos you took of your
gracia las fotos que le has hecho a tus
neighbors ra So what do you think that
vecinas ra O sea qué opinas tú que que
I also tell you really and genuinely, eh or
real y genuinamente también te digo eh o
it is about putting the relative and giving her opinion
sea lo de poner a la parienta y opinar
I did it I did it a long time ago
yo lo yo lo yo lo hice hace mucho tiempo
with the topic of the forum gossiping is worth it
con el tema del foro cotilleando vale
We're talking about 2019. But oh well.
estamos hablando de 2019 Pero bueno
mm is the worst idea You know why that is
mm es la peor idea Sabes porque es que
you are exposing her to imagine that
la estás exponiendo a que imagínate que
I'm an idiot and I put myself here
yo soy un [__] y me pong aquí a
insult Imagine that I am a raed Yes
insultar Imagínate que yo soy un raed Si
If I were Raed I would start insulting
yo fuera raed me pondría que insultar a
girl you know and now maybe the
chavala sabes y ahora a lo mejor la
girl can either stand it or she can't stand it
chavala lo soporta o no lo soporta
because he doesn't do this
porque no se dedica a esto
You know we all follow her, the girls, yes
sabes la seguimos todas las chavales si
We have the girls' Instagram Yo la
tenemos el Instagram de las chicas Yo la
I'm going to continue, okay, that is, because it's empty
voy a seguir vale o sea porque es vasada
We are not talking about that they
no estamos hablando de que de que ellos
pretend to be the good guys in the movie
simulen eh ser los buenos de la película
What do you think about them really
qué opinas tú de que ellos realmente
They believe that they are right and that
creen que ellos tienen la razón y que
They are the good guys in the movie what
ellos son los buenos de la pel qué
ask, that is, ask him about a topic
pregunta o sea pregúntale sobre un tema
So what do you think about them believing that
O sea qué opinas de que ellos crean que
They are the good guys in the movie and in
son los buenos de la película y en
reality they believe their arguments ra of
realidad se creen sus argumentos ra de
really, stop eating joints for breakfast, I mean
verdad deja de desayunar porros o sea
take joints and put them in there
[__] porros y meterlos ahí en la
toast and take a bite of that you don't
tostada y darle bocado a eso no te
feels good okay ask him Hey what do you
sienta bien vale pregúntale Oye qué te
It seems that I catch without coming to the point
parece que yo coja sin venir a cuento
a photo of the two of us and upload the photo
una foto de nosotros dos y suba la foto
from Javi and his girlfriend and say please for
de Javi y su novia y diga por favor por
Please tell me that we are more
favor decirme que nosotros somos más
handsome okay or something like that ask him a
guapos vale o sea algo así pregúntale un
specific topic Hey, what do you think?
tema en concreto Oye qué te parece que
Yesterday I made Javi a little drawing of two
ayer le hice a Javi un dibujito de dos
PCES Okay, tell him something like that, but what do you say?
pces vale dile algo así pero qué te
It seems that they think they are the
parece de que ellos piensan que son los
The good thing is that he puts on his cap very
buenos es que se pone la gorra muy
strong also that squeezes eh it puts on
fuerte también eso aprieta eh se pone la
very strong cap too
gorra muy fuerte también
eh movie So people like giving
eh película O sea que personas como dar
review And Javi Oliveira think they are
review Y Javi oliveira piensen que son
the good guys in the movie and that
los buenos de la película y que
They are really right, the worst of course
realmente tienen raz lo peor Claro que
is going to say to the girl What is going to say to
va a decir a chavala Qué va a decir a
Girl, I've already said it, it's the people who
chavala ya lo he dicho es la gente que
follows him because the people who follow him
lo sigue porque la gente que lo sigue
He applauds those things, that is, repeats them
les aplaude esas cosas o sea repetir
I constantly make a tweet and it comes out
constantemente yo hago un tweet y sale
An idiot like this, let Oliveira continue.
un idiota de esto que que siga oliveira
to tell me why I take pictures of
a decirme que por qué Yo le tomo fotos a
my neighbors, I mean, what are you talking about?
mis vecinas o sea pero qué qué hablas de
Ah, because Agustina hasn't seen the
una Ah porque Agustina no ha visto el
Twitter and doesn't know that's true Or
Twitter y no sabe que eso es verdad O
be she does not
sea ella no lo
knows doesn't know that it's true Of course because
sabe no sabe que es verdad Claro porque
how is he lying sa But why is he
cómo está mintiendo sa Pero por qué está
Why are you denying this so much?
por qué estás negando esto así con tanta
tranquility But why is it if it is
tranquilidad Pero por qué está si lo
does not know if it has been spoken in front of her
sabe No si se ha hablado delante de ella
Of course, but I don't understand it. But why?
Claro pero que no lo entiendo Pero por
why are you denying it so so so
qué lo está negando así tan tan tan
chills if the screenshots have been published
chills si se han publicado Las capturas
a lot of times Ah from a capture of
un montón de veces Ah de una captura de
screen of a group I was in
pantalla de un grupo en el que yo estaba
with with Dallas and with and with Apple and the
con con Dallas y con y con Apple y el
another when I that what was happening to him
otro cuando yo que lo que le estaba
counting at that time was neither
contando en ese momento no era ni
there is not even a squeo comment to the
siquiera hay un comentario de squeo a la
jea
jea
saying But how That there isn't even
diciendo Pero cómo Que ni siquiera hay
a comment from sadique or so then
un comentario de sadique o sea entonces
that you were commenting on the blues of the
que estabas comentando los azule de la
pool be that you are me
piscina sea qu me estás
counting but let's see RAE let's go
contando pero vamos a ver RAE vamos a
see what the [ __ ] you're doing to me
ver qué [__] me estás
saying Look, look, I have the tile
diciendo Mirad Mirad tengo el azulejo a
I have the tile, ...
tiro tengo el azulej tiro Mira azulejo
prettier and also matches my
más bonito además que hace juego con mi
bathroom is that now take a picture Look
baño es que ahora hag una foto Mirad
Look at what point, what score you give it.
Mirad qué punto qué puntuación le ponéis
to the
al
tile I can't believe it I can't believe it
azulejo no me lo puedo creer no me lo
I can believe yotin Agus that look Uy Look
puedo creer yotin Agus que mire Uy Mira
This chick is so hot, I'm not saying anything
esta tipa qué buena está no le estoy
taking I took a picture of him and said look
tomando le tomé una foto y le dije mira
These chicks are here separated they had
estas tipas están aquí separaron tenían
the entire pool building for
toda la piscina el edificio para
sit here drunk
sentarse se sentaron aquí borrachas al
in front of me That's all to say
frente mío Eso es todo para decir
theirs with friends because the
lasa de ellos con los amigos porque la
people who are like that have already shown that
gente que es así ya demostraron que
They have the morals of cardboard like
tiene tienen la moral de cartón como
he says very
dice él muy
he spends everything
se la pasa todo
elenda people is what I said the other
elenda la gente es lo que dije el otro
day the people who boast the most or the people
día la gente que más alardea o la gente
but when you when you get to
pero cuando tú cuando tú te pones a
write to jebas to be threesomes r
escribirle a jebas para ser tríos r
It means that he is spoiled with you
significa que es consentido con tu
couple you understand me one thing is that I
pareja me entiendes una cosa es que yo
I have a relationship where I have threesomes
tenga una relación en la que hago tríos
And then I write to girls to
Y entonces le escribo a chicas para
have
tener
threesomes and another thing is that you in the
tríos y otra cosa es que tú en la
pool Without your girlfriend knowing because
piscina Sin que tu novia lo sepa porque
the girl is not being seen to be
no se le está viendo a la chavala de que
I am very happy with that, you put yourself in
esté muy conforme con eso te pongas de
stalker taking pictures of you without
acosador hacerle forma fotos sin
consent to girls in bikinis
consentimiento a las muchachas en bikini
what a filthy man, how disgusting the [ __ ] there are pages
qué guarro tío qué asco [__] hay páginas
on the internet so as not to have to harass
en internet para no tener que acosar
people who say the most people who say the most
gente que más dice la gente que más
critics are the people who unfortunately
critica es la gente que lamentablemente
more so
más lo
I did tell you that Dallas and
hace yo nosotros contamos que Dallas y
Urdaneta are trying to hire
urdaneta están intentando contratar
hitmen to attack Delox, that's it.
sicarios para para siarar a delox eso es
100% true agustino was there ag
100% cierto agustino estaba ahí ag
I was there my friends know it best
estaba ahí mis amigas lo saben mi mejor
friend knows because she knows
amiga lo sabe porque se lo
She told her friends that same day
ella le contó ese mismo día a las amigas
To the parents, everyone, look at what's going on
a los papás a todos miren lo que está
doing this guy or this guy is
haciendo este tipo o sea este tipo está
talking to the other Malandro saying
hablando con el otro Malandro diciendo
that they are going to finish off another youtuber
que van a finalizar a a otro youtuber
because they don't like it or it's crazy
porque les cae mal o sea una locura
These idiots think that we
estos imbéciles creen que nosotros nos
We're going to invent that story. So I'm leaving.
vamos a inventar Ese cuento O sea me voy
to invent I don't believe that you
a inventar yo no me creo que tú te
You invented that RAE for nothing. I think that
inventes eso RAE para nada Yo creo que
you a person with such a head
tú una persona con la cabeza tan
settled like you who are denying it
asentada como tú que estás negándole
Here people are talking about the photos
aquí a la gente lo de las fotos a las
neighbors saying that it is a tile
vecinas diciendo que es a un azulejo me
You can please make a point of being here.
podéis hacer porfi luar estás por aquí
Can you send me the following tweet?
me podéis hacer el siguiente tweet de
RAE
RAE
Please, I don't know if this is the place
porfa no sé si está lugar por
Here you can see how he tries
aquí se nota se nota como intenta
drive the girl's argument even so
conducir el argumento de la chica aú así
falla starts to put on his crazy face
falla empieza a poner su cara de loco de
He always raises his voice. Greetings, Javi
siempre y hasta sube la voz Saludos Javi
red heart the
corazón rojo el
of ra is worth with the image of ra with the
de ra vale con la imagen de ra con el
sandwich above with the tweet you remember
bocadillo arriba con el tweet acuerdas
not the one that he burns so much Because I have
no el que él se arde tanto Pues tengo
a new version in which I want you to
una nueva versión en la que quiero que
I put it that I didn't take pictures of girls without their
ponga yo no hice fotos a chicas sin su
consent in the pool we were
consentimiento en la piscina estábamos
scoring the
puntuando los
tiles Please make me believe that
azulejos Porfa me ese que lo crean que
I believe it But where In what head does it fit
lo cre Pero de dónde En qué cabeza cabe
that I'm going to go out and say this
que yo voy a salir y voy a decir esta
people wanted to contact hitmen from where
gente quería contactar sicarios de dónde
from where tell me from where it can be
de dónde díganme de dónde que se puede
invent a movie about someone like that
inventar una película de alguien así
I could if I wanted to throw it at him
podría si es que yo quería tirarle
[ __ ] the guy could have me
[__] al tipo me hubiese podido
invent anything and because it was
inventar cualquier cosa y porque s era
a person who is capable of doing
una persona que es capaz de hacer
anything and to deny anything
cualquier cosa y de desmentir cualquier
thing like saying that a woman was with
cosa como decir que una mujer estuvo con
a [ __ ] short shy or so that's it already already
un fucking shor shy o sea eso es ya ya
when you realize that people have arrived
cuando te das cuenta que la gente llegó
to believe something like that you already realize that
a creer algo así ya te das cuenta que
that type of society is totally
ese tipo de sociedad está totalmente
lost to believe such a tremendous atrocity or
perdida para creer tremenda atrocidad o
be it never or be it physically it is impossible
sea nunca o sea físicamente es imposible
Well, I'm not going to comment on this topic.
bueno no voy a opinar de este tema
Because honestly that was something that
Porque sinceramente eso fue algo que
Well, Dallas gave it publicity and everything.
bueno el Dallas le dio difusión y todo
the roll no Or he commented it But because it is
el rollo no O lo comentó Pero porque se
Nimu's ex said it, no, in any case no.
lo dijo el ex de nimu no En todo caso no
Nimu's ex And then Nimu's ex
el ex de nimu Y luego el ex de nimu se
He started saying that the delos paid him no
puso a decir que que el delos le pagó no
So the delos paid him to do it.
O sea que el delos le pagó para para que
delete or something like that I don't remember how
borrara o algo así no me acuerdo cómo
That's what they said that I don't know who
fue lo que dijeron que yo no sé quién
you would be right in the end there because
tendría la razón al final ahí porque
Since they have not debated in the end it has been
como no han debatido al final se ha
things have been left like this, it is going to be
quedado la cosa como ahí que se va a
eat a criminal complaint for
comer una denuncia penal por
and a criminal complaint will be filed against the baby for
y va caer una denuncia penal al bebé por
to be saying that a woman is that she is
estar diciendo que una muj Yo es que es
a real penalty, in any case,
un penal de verdad yo en to caso un
civil Well maybe you say Well
civil Pues a lo mejor dices tú Bueno
I could have no but a civilian is a
Podría tener no pero un civil sea un
criminal that is not an accusation of a
penal eso no es una imputación de un
crime no I mean it depends No maybe
delito no O sea depende No a lo mejor
No, that is an accusation of a crime that
no eso es una imputación de delito que
not these
no estos
No, I've never been that interested, to be honest.
No no me ha dado nunca por ahí la verdad
woman without any proof only the
mujer sin prueba ninguna solamente el
testimony only the testimony of a
testimonio solamente el testimonio de un
sophilia is
sofilia Es
crime that was trolling him apart And
delito que lo estaba troleando aparte Y
who also has the nerve to not even
que aparte tenga el descaro de ni
not even download the video on YouTube bro
siquiera bajar el video YouTube hermano
you are blatantly lying about
estás mintiendo descaradamente acerca a
You are defaming this woman in the worst way
esta mujer estás difam de la peor manera
possible saying that he has relations
posible diciendo que tiene relaciónes
with a spotted dog
con un perro manchás
her privacy no no because she does have
su intimidad no no porque ella sí tiene
many things against him the times that the
muchas cosas contra él las veces que la
who insulted her with defamation when
que la insultó las difamaciones cuando
told where they lived when he contacted the
contó dónde vivían cuando contactó a la
Andorran police to go to her
policía de andorra para que la vaya a
search that it was illegal when he said that
buscar que era ilegal cuando contó que
what they lived on when he revealed the address
de qué vivían cuando reveló la dirección
from the place where he worked or had one
de del lugar donde trabajaba o tenía una
company has many things
empresa del tiene muchísimas cosas
against him there is much defamation
contra él muchísimas la difamación
clearly the greatest do not denounce
claramente la más grande no denuncies a
the review my love you are hitting me ha
las review mi amor me estás pegando ha
that prop no don't do it Hey guys
esa prop no no lo hagas Oy chicos se
been a bad temper no but you are me
estado un mal genio no pero me estás
trando is putting a video of mine of de
trando está poniendo un vídeo mío de de
Javiel Wigs are watching Javiel
javiel pelucas están viendo javiel
wigs seriously I can't stand the raed By
pelucas en serio no soporto al raed Por
what the [ __ ] is very cute that he pored it but
qué [__] es muy lindo que lo poró pero
Of course, you have to answer when
claro n tú tienes que responder cuando
you are going to put the crella that you are going to
tú vayas a poner la crella que tú vas a
other creators and you tell them they are no more
otros creadores y le dices no son más
idiot, because they don't pay you, stop
[__] porque no te pagan deja de
defame and go chase your tail and
difamar y anda a perseguirte la cola y
smell ass where I came from
oler culo ahí donde venía yo
D's [ __ ] knows that for sure.
sabe la pija de D eso sí que te lo
you have studied Clear you are a
tienes estudiado Claro tú eres una
person who will tell you Well I have guard
persona que te dir Bueno tengo guard
person
person
Well Agustina says that's great.
bueno Agustina dice que es genial esa
Mine, I'm putting on screen a t
mina estoy poniendo yo en pantalla un t
of encouragement insulting me here in these in
de nimo insultándome aquí en estos en
specifically the two that are mine eh A
concreto los dos que puesto es a mí eh A
what does Dallas's [ __ ] know moves the
qué sabe la [__] de Dallas mueve la
tail doggy I don't know what and and he says that
cola perrito No sé qué y y dice que
Hahaha, that girl is great, I mean she is.
Jajaja Ja es genial esa mina o sea está
like super offended because Dallas
como super ofendida porque el Dallas
insult the animu is worth it
insulte al animu vale
Suddenly Oh, but it's that Nim has
de repente Ay pero es que nim tiene
many things against but ah see nim
muchas cosas contra pero ah ve nim
insulting other people and chilling
insultando a otra gente y chill es
that's great
genial esa
Mina we no longer follow her We no longer follow her
Mina ya no la seguimos Ya no la seguimos
what he tells you is what that thing is
qué es lo que le dice es lo que eso que
You have studied what it is that
te lo tienes estudiado qué es lo que le
says
dice
He explains what he knows
va explicando lo que sabe
nothing to do I just wanted his
la nada que ver Solo quería su
channel with the new series of the club of
canal con la nueva serie del club de
Nimu fans is that it has because the
fans de nimu es que tiene porque los
old videos were outdated and
videos viejos estaban obsoletos y lo
has been announcing for a long time that
viene anunciando hace mucho antes que
this news in your Stream better than the
esta noticia en sus Stream mejor que el
next video is what explaining what
próximo video sea qué explicando A qué
The Dallas girl knows that's true.
sabe la pija de Dallas que eso sí lo
You have studied it well, I will explain it to you
tiene bien estudiado os voy a explicar
one thing now
una cosa ahora
God explaining what the dick knows God
Dios explicando qu sabe la pija Dios
holy RAE You know what is happening to me
santo RAE Tú sabes lo que me está
answering there nimu pintam mona that
contestando ahí nimu pintam mona que
are
eres
silly You know what's happening to me
tonto Tú sabes lo que me está
Nimu responding to the crypto thing
respondiendo nimu ahí a lo de crypto
Spain or so There nimu answering me to a
Spain o sea Ahí nimu me contestando a un
tweet where I put your screenshot
tweet donde yo pongo la captura tuya
buffoon, trust me if you're stupid and don't
mamarracho fíate si eres tonto y no
you have a beginning or anything or that is to say you
tienes principio ni ni nada o sea te
You simply base it on whether I will tomorrow
basas simplemente en si yo mañana me
I fight with you, you support the opposite
peleo contigo apoyas todo lo contrario
Right there he is answering me to yours
ahí mismo Me está respondiendo a lo tuyo
of Christ Spain that you said that of them
de Cristo Spain que tú dijiste que delos
He was a scammer, another line for
era un estafador otra raya más para
tiger Search for a tweet look this is yours
tigre Busca un tweet mira este es tu
tweet is that you are stupid uncle is that you are
tweet es que eres tonto tío es que eres
really stupid And you're leaving your
tonto de verdad Y estás dejando í a tu
Bad girlfriend, [ __ ], get her out of there, humiliate yourself
novia mal [__] quítala de ahí humíllate
you alone sun
tú sol solo
Look, do you remember this?
Mira te acuerdas de este
tweet Look at another stripe for the tiger
tweet Mira otra raya más para el tigre
Okay, eh, they were wondering why the maximum
vale eh se preguntaban Por qué el máximo
Crypto criminal Delox deleted
delincuente del mundo crypto delox borró
from now on more than 1000 videos of
de momento a otro más de 1000 vídeos de
your channel Okay, so from this I got a
su canal Vale pues de esto yo saqué un
tweet And then that's what I'm talking about
tweet Y entonces a eso a lo que me está
Nimu answering me telling me that that is
contestando nimu diciéndome que eso es
lie that he deleted the videos because of the
mentira que borró los vídeos por la
miniature and what better than to suck it
miniatura y que mejor que le chupe la
polla dala or how many sheets does it have
[__] dala o cuántos pliegos tiene la
[ __ ] dala
[__] dala
eh No but it makes me a bit dog
eh No pero me pone algo de perro
don't go and wag your tail and smell
no anda a menearte la cola y a oler
asses like the dog you are or something like that
culos como el perro que eres o algo así
not that it was for me to do If I were
no que era para yo hacer Si yo fuera
like like you Well I would answer him
como como ustedes Pues yo le contestaría
nmo with a dog joke Not now that
nmo con un chiste de perros No ahora que
You make it so easy for me now that we are
me lo ponéis tan fácil ahora que estamos
talking about dogs No, well it happens that no
hablando de perros No pues pasa que no
I fall for that because well because I don't
caigo en eso Porque bueno porque no me
I mess with couples like you who are
meto yo con las parejas como tú que eres
one thing
una cosa
You understand me. See if you're stupid, RAE.
me entiendes Fíjate si eres tonto RAE
Look how stupid you are. Look at the face that
Fíjate si eres tonto Mira la cara que se
the one whoa The poor guy Look how stupid you are
la quea Al pobre Fíjate si eres tonto
RAE that the other day we have already told you
RAE que que el otro día Ya te hemos
caught with the divai The other day you
pillado con lo divai El otro día te
we caught you with the divai that you
hemos pillado con lo divai que te
you started to invent that you defended
pusiste a inventarte que tú defendiste a
and when Dala got into him in front
i cuando dala se metió con él delante
yours Look how stupid you are that you became
tuya Fíjate si eres tonto que te pusiste
to say eh that we have to see those who
a decir eh que hay que ver los que le
They donated to Fran Cuesta, we have a tea from you
donaron a Fran cuesta tenemos un t tuyo
sucking his [ __ ] Fran Here I am to
chupándole la [__] Fran Aquí estoy para
What I need I give you And see if
lo que necesit yo te dono Y fíjate si
You're a fool who's clapping now
eres tonto que Estás aplaudiendo ahora
a tweet that this is from September here
un tweet que esto es de septiembre aquí
you were still eating my balls, okay? And
todavía tú me comías los [__] vale Y
In this tweet I am echoing
en este twit Yo me estoy haciendo eco de
a news that you give what happens that
una noticia que das tú lo que pasa que
Now then, how did you fight with D?
ahora luego como te peleaste con el D te
you went to talk to him
fuiste hablarte con el
delox, that is, you are completely stupid.
delox o sea eres completamente lelo es
that
que
I think you should take off your forelock.
tonto Yo opino que te quites el copete
this one you have here because I guess that
este que tienes aquí porque Supongo que
when you're sucking him off
cuando le estás chupando
tickle the navel then
da cosquillas en el ombligo entonces
So recommend that I put on the cap
pues recomiéndame que me ponga la gorra
so tight like you that then to the
así apretadita como tú que luego a lo
I better keep the signal when I get it
mejor se me queda la señal cuando me la
But well, recommend that I take it
quite Pero bueno recomiéndame que me la
put it like this and it doesn't move at all
ponga así y así no se me mueve ni un
hair that tuft because surely
pelo el copete ese Porque seguramente
starts laughing when you touch this
empieza a reírse cuando tú le rozas esta
[ __ ] in the navel criminal clown I don't
[__] en el ombligo payaso penal yo no
I know if this type is a penalty, it disgusts me
sé si una penal este tipo qué asco me da
the complaint how disgusting that idiot is
la denuncia qué asco que da imbécil una
Report how disgusting it is to me, I swear that
denuncia qué asco me da se los juro que
It disgusts me, it disgusts me to see his face
me da un asco un asco me da ver la cara
If I see this lazy guy, I get
a este tipo huevón s yo lo veo me dan
I feel like throwing up, dude.
ganas de vomitar huevón a mí me dan
I feel like vomiting the guys who harass
ganas de vomitar los tipos que acosan a
RAE women the types that threaten
las mujeres RAE los tipos que amenazan a
under 5 years old, those give me a lot
menores de 5 años a mí esos me dan mucho
disgust I think they should be in the
asco Creo que deberían estar en la
jail, guys really disgust me
cárcel a mí me dan mucho asco los tipos
that they put in the pool to do it
que se ponen en la piscina a hacerle
photography without consent to the
fotografía sin consentimiento a las
women, that's what disgusts me and
mujeres eso es que me dan un asco y una
fatigue to you no, the same thing happens to us
fatiga a ustedes no noos pasa lo mismo a
I am a guy who starts to do it
mí es que un tipo que se pone a hacerle
photos of an aunt without consent
fotos a una tía sin consentimiento las
girls in the pool, imagine, I mean
chavalas en la piscina imagínate o sea
Imagine that you buy your house
tú Imagínate que te compras tu casa
calm down your private urbanization is
tranquila tu Urbanización privada estás
you in the pool and a pig comes to you
tú en piscina y te viene un cerdo de
This is something to do at 40 and something years old.
esto con 40 y pico años hacerle
photo how disgusting kid how disgusting for
foto qué asco chaval qué asco para
put him in jail
meterlo preso
Hey, how can you have a character in
eh que cómo puedes haber personaje en
The internet is so pathetic that it's vomit-inducing.
internet tan patético es que es vomitivo
This guy is disgusting at what he does.
este tipo es un asco a lo que se dedica
shameful what he dedicates his [ __ ] life to
vergonzoso a lo que dedica su [__] vida
Brother, what a disgusting person, what disgusting, what
brother un asco de persona qué asco qué
I hate everything, the guy, the accent disgusts me.
asco todo me da asco el tipo el acento
the form goes from a pimp there to throwing one
la forma va de chulo ahí a tirarse una
that he is from
de que él es de
too too funny Oh how funny
demasiado demasiado cómico Ah Qué cómico
I am the one who threw a mi at him
soy le tiró una mi quién le tiró una mi
be with me and she's Dallas's ex and she was
estar con mi y es la ex de Dallas y era
your friend you Why do you think he now
su amigo tú Por qué crees que él ahora
It's from the Dallas Review side, you don't.
es del bando de Dallas review tú no
You knew because he changed sides, you didn't.
sabías por él se cambió de bando tú no
You knew he was the main hater of
sabías que él era el principal hater de
Dallas you didn't know Ah well he was the
Dallas no sabías Ah bueno él era el
main hater of Dallas so hater of
principal hater de Dallas tan hater de
Dallas was telling him he made tweets of
Dallas era que le decía hacía tweets de
This Caliber look at the tweets the caliber
este Calibre miren los tweets el calibre
the tweets that Jolas made this
los tweets que hacía las jolas este
Before I bounce it I'm going to tell you
Antes de que lo rebotara ya les voy a
searching for the tweet is a It seems to me that
buscar el tweet es una Me parece que
He dedicated some tweets to insulting me, I don't
dedicó algunos tweets a insultarme no me
I agree very well that he is saying no
acuerdo muy bien está diciendo que no
that the woman I got involved with
que la mujer con la que yo me metí
supposedly he is a little angel of the
supuestamente que es un angelito del
Sir, they are going to beatify her right now.
señor que la van a beatificar ahorita
even though Oliveira's wife is the one
mismo siendo la mujer de oliveira lo
I doubt it very much but he is saying that the
dudo mucho pero está diciendo que la
His wife is tweeting him but
mujer de él le está poniendo tweets pero
look at the quality of tweets he posted
vean la calidad de tweets que le ponía
jav oliveira Now dog of this By
jav oliveira Ahora perro de este Por
true there is one thing that r does not answer
cierto hay una cosa la que r no contesta
Let's see if we can all ask him.
a ver si se lo podemos preguntar todos
because he hasn't answered me
porque a mí no me ha contestado ra
get rid of the gear get rid of the gear that
quítate del avío quítate del avío que
You are a Crypto.com Partner because I
eres Partner de cripto.com porque yo
I have here the captures in which they
tengo aquí Las capturas en las que ellos
They deny you, they know that you are a
reniegan de ti saben que eres una
person who has just been released from prison
persona que acaba de salir de la cárcel
They know what you do with it
saben que a lo que te dedicas con el
harassment is worth it and they say they don't have
acoso vale Y ellos dicen que no tienen
absolutely nothing to do with you that
absolutamente nada que ver contigo que
if you have created a referral link
si te has creado un enlace de referidos
something like that but don't wear it
algo por el estilo pero que no te pongas
in the avio that you are a Partner of
en la avío que eres Partner de
cristo.com because they don't want to know
cristo.com porque ellos no quieren saber
nothing of
nada de
you of this sock with the woman see the
ti de este soquete con la mujer vean la
quality of tweets and the qualities of
calidad de tweets y las calidades de
offense that I did to him before my
ofensa que le hacía antes de que mi lo
will bounce retweet if you think so
rebotara retweet si piensas que si
you were the mother of dasas, it's not that you look
fueses la madre de dasas no es que mira
You see, if you don't know this debate
Es que fíjate tú si no sabes Este debate
Mine with Dallas the conversations are of
mío con Dallas las conversaciones son de
My conversations with my son are very
mucho las conversaciones mías con mi son
a night of fun in which she doesn't
una noche de cachondeo en la que ella no
is uncomfortable in conversation a lot
está incómoda en la conversación mucho
before this debate two years before
antes que este debate dos años antes de
This debate, that is, look at the spite
este debate o sea fíjate tú el despecho
that I had because the other one that night didn't
que yo tenía porque la otra esa noche no
He slept with me for two years.
se acostó conmigo que esto es dos años
then you trust the logic but of course
después fíate tú la lógica pero claro
as you are using an argument of
como está utilizando un argumento de
Antonia, well that's what's happening to you.
Antonia pues eso es lo que te pasa ra
which is a bit like those people
que queda un poco como esa gente
guys t
chavales t
ok scoring wait I'm going to do it
vale puntuando espérate lo voy a
I write the text luare
escribir yo el texto luare
That night I hooked up with Cristina
esa noche mi se enrollo con la Cristina
Bernard exactly, that is, it is an exit
bernald exactamente o sea es una salida
as a fun friend and little more but he is
de amigo de cachondeo y poco más pero es
It doesn't matter because it has nothing to do with
que da igual es que no tiene nada que
see or even if it were real Although my
ver o sea aunque fuera real Aunque mi
intention was real I was not with my
intención fuera real yo no estaba con mi
woman then after two or three weeks
mujer luego a las dos o tres semanas
we came back and continued our normal friendship
volvimos continuamos la amistad normal
That was in 2016, so I continued the
Eso fue en 2016 o sea yo continué la
friendship with them until January 2019
amistad con ellos hasta enero de 2019 me
you understand or so That is the argument that
entiendes o sea Ese es el argumento que
The lady at the school has ordered them to
la señora la escuela les ha ordenado al
army this to the little team
ejército este al equipito
and but it's like it doesn't have much
e pero es como que no tiene mucho
sense either not because the spite you
sentido tampoco no porque el despecho te
enters at the moment, not at 3 years old
entra al momento no a los 3 años
you would leave your 10-year-old sister alone
dejarías a su hermana de 10 años a solas
with him for fear that he will look at her with others
con él por miedo a que la mire con otros
eyes that [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] the
ojos eso te [__] [__] [__] el
offended because I told him
ofendidito porque le dije
but I don't understand what it is that I
pero es que no entiendo que es lo que me
This is what I'm not understanding. I mean
está es que no estoy entendiendo O sea
What do you think about my strong tweets?
que te parece fuerte los tweets que yo
I put Dallas in
le ponía a Dallas en
2017 and you know that we are in 2025 and you
2017 y sabes que estamos en el 2025 y tú
you do it
lo haces
now it is that it does not make sense what it is
ahora sea es que no tiene sentido qué es
what you want that you are doing to yourself
lo que quieres que te estás haciendo el
indignant when you came to eat my
indignado cuando venías a comerme los
balls in private you didn't know
[__] por privado no conocías
This is what you think Dallas's mom doesn't do.
esto crees que la mamá de Dallas no
I should leave the little sister alone with him
debería dejar a la hermanita sola con él
for fear that he will see her with different eyes
por miedo a que la vea con otros ojos el
offended This is the offended a tweet yes
ofendido Este es el ofendido un tweet sí
a chill tweet a chill tweet that's it
un tweet de chill un twit chill eso es
a tacit cry that was thrown
un tcito chill que se lanzaba el
This is a slanderous slanderer.
difamador calumniador este un tiito
chill that this one threw at him Now they are the
chill que le lanzaba este Ahora son los
best friends because they are the same
mejores amigos porque son igual de
scumbags both of us are not best friends or
lacras ambos no somos mejores amigos o
We are colleagues, they are both scumbags.
sea somos colegas son ambos unas lacras
some scourges that completely affect people who
unas lacras que interamente personas que
They made so much [ __ ] that they can get to
se hicieron tanta [__] pueden llegar a
join What is the reason for them to be
unirse Qué es la razón de que sean
the same as when they saw each other like this
iguales que cuando se vieron así se
They recognized themselves in a mirror because they are
reconocieron en un espejo porque son
exactly the same
exactamente la misma
[ __ ] wait, let's see something cool
[__] espérate Vamos a ver una cosa ra
because I think you forgot
porque es que creo que que se te olvid a
You, the truth is, I think you're forgetting one.
ti la verdad creo que se te olvida una
something you do not know the human quality
cosa ustedes no saben la calidad humana
the quality of person that Dallas has
la calidad de persona que tiene Dallas
has no idea what it's like to have a
no tiene ni idea lo que es tener un
friend like Dallas is one thing
amigo como Dallas es una cosa
It's amazing how happy I am in
impresionante lo feliz que yo soy en
This moment of being able to be friends with someone
este momento de poder ser amigo de una
person like that I mean what transparency What
persona así O sea qué transparencia Qué
person is incredible, my brother is awesome
persona es increíble de pana mi brother
I love you very much and you have given me a
te quiero mucho y me has dado una
opportunity that the la well I appreciate it
oportunidad que la la bueno la aprecio
like nothing in the world all those who you
como nada en el mundo todos los que te
They want to harm you, they will regret it.
quieren dañar se van a arrepentir de
having tried to hurt you like that
haberte intentado hacer daño De esa
way of telling lies and slander because
manera diciendo mentiras y calume porque
They are professional slanderers
son calumniadores de oficio los
slanderers were
calumniadores eran
others Because they live by slandering
otros Porque viven de calumniar a
people because they have no proof of what
personas porque no tienen pruebas de lo
what they say and and everything that we go
que dicen y y todo lo que nosotros vamos
to do is to keep the project going
a hacer es para que el proyecto siga
forward and so that your name never
adelante y para que tu nombre nunca
Nobody ever tries to stain him here Lu me
nadie intente mancharlo nunca aquí Lu me
You can send that clip via WhatsApp by
puedes mandar ese clip por WhatsApp por
end to tarlo
fin para tarlo
being disgustingly united them hatred
ser asquerosamente los unió el odio la
frustration towards a woman who is miare
frustración hacia una mujer que es miare
why Why look poor mine what
por qué Por qué miare pobre mina qué
condemns being with a guy and then that
condena estar con un tipo y después que
don't leave you alone, don't leave you alone
no te deje en paz que no te deje en paz
that wherever it [ __ ] you, that it [ __ ] you
que por donde sea que te joda que te
I put this in and I will name what sentence he should
meta esto que te nombre qué condena debe
be for the mine the worst thing you could have done
ser para la mina lo peor que hizo puedes
say good ally my Antonia Échale
decir buena aliada mi Antonia Échale
tell everyone who is with you
cuenta a toos dos que te están
tagging Hey good Defenders eh
etiquetando Oye buenos Defensores eh
good support good
buen apoyo buenos
I support this guy as well, because he is
apoyo este igual este tipo pues se
changes sides the moment he
cambia de bando en el momento en que
Miare handed him a truckload of beer.
miare le entregó un camión de cerveza le
He said take it go take it take it here you
dijo tome vaya Tómese Tómese aquí usted
This beer crate, sir, is going to happen
esta gavera de cerveza señor vaya
Get me drunk will be able to play Not a hair
emborráchame va a poder tocar Ni un pelo
They gave him What the
le dieron What the
Fu But at what point if here there was already
Fu Pero en qué momento si aquí ya había
after that, that is, at what point did RAE announce a
pasado eso o sea en qué momento RAE una
little box of beer on top is he has a woman
cajita de cerveza encima é é ten mujer
since then obviously I was
desde ese entonces obviamente estaba
married when he was flirting are
casado cuando estaba de coquetín están
the tweets eye This is not is not a
los tweets ojo Esto no es no es un
invention like the twe inventions where you
invento como los inventos twe donde le
It says a few things there How beautiful
dice un poco de cosas ahí Que hermosa
that you are not going to tell your mommy and a
que no le vayas a decir a tu mami y un
a few things of course that you are not going to
poco de cosas claro que no le vayas a
say no Ray or literally no dude
decir que no Ray o sea literal no tío
Neon a literal kiss just denied with
Neón un beso literal acaba de negar con
all his [ __ ] that he doesn't get to do to her
toda su [__] que no se pone a hacerle
photos of the women in the pool at
fotos a las mujeres en la piscina a las
girls in the pool are worth it
chavalas en la piscina vale el
and now he starts complaining that if I
y ahora se pone a quejarse que si yo
I do or don't do whatever I want.
hago o no hago lo que me de la gana me
you're telling uncle Don't tell him
estás contando tío No le vayas a contar
to your mother
a tu mamá sea
me telling miare not to go to him
mi diciéndole a miare que no le fuera a
tell mom anything because obviously
contar nada a la mamá porque obviamente
Je was 16 17 years old and 16 17 years old
la Je tenía que 16 17 años y 16 17 años
no, he has no [ __ ] idea what
no no tiene ni [__] idea de lo que
good luck with your mouth, man, that is, you speak
suerta por la boca tío o sea habla
because he has a mouth and that's it, eh, my mre
porque tiene boca y punto eh que mi mre
Jeeva was 16, 17 years old, no, no, no
tenía la jeeva tenía 16 17 años no no no
no but it is completely stupid or rather it is
no pero es completamente lelo o sea es
that the support of these people is that the
que los apoyos de esta gente es que el
little team But who is the dumbest of all
equipito Pero quién es el más tonto de
all family Who is the dumbest of
todos familia Quién es el más tonto de
all the
todo el
little team could be ra no ra is like a
equipito podría ser ra no ra es como un
crazy
loquito
not this type because obviously we already know
no este tipo pues obviamente ya sabemos
what is eh And I would like to know why
lo que es eh Y me gustaría saber por qué
dasas lives so burned perhaps Dallas lives
dasas vive tan ardido quizás Dallas vive
angry because they discovered what he had
ardido porque le descubrieron lo que
made with olive and from
hizo con olivita Y a partir
[Laughs]
[Risas]
that what he did with olivita became
que lo que hizo con olivita se convirtió
in verer mode to denounce everyone
en modo verer a funar a todo el mundo a
call everyone a pedophile and
decirle pedófilo a todo el mundo y a
mess with everyone, that is, he messes with everyone
meterse con todo el mundo o sea le le
I farted on everyone, everyone, why? Because
hice pedo a todos a todos por qué Porque
He was the one who was accused of that. Then
él fue que lo acusaron de eso Entonces
he makes sense makes sense eh based
él tiene sentido tiene sentido eh basado
ra eh based the herald has suffered a lot
ra eh basado sufrió mucho el herdal ha
suffered a lot since he was
sufrió muchísimo desde que le
They discovered that Sad was one of 13
descubrieron que estaba Sad una de 13
Churra How that boy has suffered
churra Cómo ha sufrido ese muchacho
churra is like in some
churra es como que en algún
God bless me, I have to find Ray.
momento Dios tengo que buscar a Ray
eating my balls eh that too
comiéndome los [__] eh que también
There's mine like this eating my balls
hay cl mío así comiéndome los huevos
but a lot eh Neither r nor Ricky are the
pero un montón eh Ni r ni Ricky son los
sharper pencils But who is the a
lápices más afilados Pero quién es el a
See, I think the smartest of
ver yo creo que el más listo de
everyone let's see there are several there are two in
todos a ver hay varios hay dos en
I'm not going to mention them specifically, but there are
concreto no voy a mencionarlos Pero hay
two in particular that do seem clever to me
dos en concreto que sí me parecen listos
What happens is that they are very bad at it.
Lo que pasa que son muy malos del
I think there are two teams that do
equipillo yo creo que hay dos que sí que
They are quite clever, they are not stupid. But
son listos bastante no son tontos Pero
They are very bad, they are very bad and evil
son muy malos son muy malos y la maldad
It can make them look foolish.
les puede Y les hace quedar como tontos
But they are very clever
Pero son muy listo
[Music]
[Música]
m must have gone crazy and there as
m tuvo que haber ido la olla y ahí como
that has already shown its true self and
que ya está mostró su verdadero ser y
never now is quiet quiet with
nunca ahora está calladito calladito con
all quiet with everything only
todo calladito con todo solamente
attacking people on tiktok hello why
atacando a gente de tiktok hola porque
needs new viewers then for
necesita viewers nuevos entonces para
In order to have new viewers, I
para poder tener viewers nuevos a mí me
I like the excuses that Javi says for
gustan las excusas que dice Javi para
When wings lose a trial it is that
cuando alas pierde un juicio es que
elurra the Ju the night before the
elurra el Ju la noche anterior del
trial saw him around in a bar and
juicio lo vieron por ahí en un bar y
I was drunk
estaba tomado churra
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Oh my God Oh my God and says the bride
Ay Dios mío Ay Dios mío y dice la novia
No, I disagree with him on some things.
no yo discrepo con él en alguna cosilla
I disagree with him on some things.
eh discrepo con él en alguna
thing the mouth idiot studies
cosilla la boca papanatas estudia
graduate from something please you're 40
gradúate de algo por favor tienes 40
years brother 40 years please you left
años brother 40 años por favor te fuiste
soft God It seems I was soft he said
suave Dios Parece que fui suave dijo
It seems that I was gentle, he says, I don't understand.
parece que fui suave dice yo no entiendo
What's wrong with these people?
qué le pasa a esta gente por
This one will never dare to say to me, "No, no, that's it."
este a m nunca se atr deir No no ya va
RAE neither Agus RAE is not given either
RAE tampoco Agus A RAE tampoco se le
I wouldn't even think of saying something like that.
ocurriría decir algo así ni de coña ra
Chill who really is a super person
chill que de verdad es una persona super
rec counterintelligence and it is and it is
rec contrainteligente y está y está
every day on the Stream surely
todos los días en el Stream seguramente
is reacting to this because now his
está reaccionando a esto porque ahora su
Hobby is to come and react to this
Hobby es venir a reaccionar a este
Stream then for tomorrow yes me
Stream entonces para mañana sí me
I love it, I don't care if you like this one
encanta me da igual que os guste este
content eh maximum a kiss Hey by
contenido eh máximo un beso Oye por
true I have set a goal that is going
cierto he puesto un objetivo que se va
finish in seconds I just realized
acabar en segundos me acabo de dar
account I had forgotten uncle javid
cuenta Se me había olvidado tío javid
you are with some sick people that I am staying with
dasas con unos enfermos que me quedo
I'm freaking out when I see this content
flipando a ver a mí este contenido me
enchants is the character that
encanta es es el personaje que
we needed it I'm not going to let it go
necesitábamos no lo voy a soltar lo
you know no Z Z more not being able in total
sabéis no Z Z más no poder en total
disagreement what the [ __ ] are you telling me
desacuerdo qué [__] estás contándome
What do you mean ZZ What do you mean ZZ
Cómo que ZZ Cómo que ZZ
Dude, I already saw the live, delete it, but whatever.
tío ya vi el directo borrarlo pero o sea
It doesn't seem like one of the best, I'm not going to give it to me
no parece de los mejores no voy a me da
I don't care, I'm not going to stop, eh? No
igual me da igual no voy a parar eh No
I'm going to stop this content, we're going to
voy a parar este contenido lo vamos a
always react to make all clips
reaccionar siempre hacer todos los clips
go cutting him off so I don't know who he will be
ir cortando a él para no sé quién será
worst of the little soccer team but the one that
peor del equipito de fútbol pero el que
He is selecting them, he has poor eyesight
los está seleccionando tiene mala vista
For the players, better alone than bad
para los jugadores mejor solo que mal
accompanied me, he or she who
acompañado a yo el él o la que
select the team I don't know if it has
selecciona el equipo yo no sé si tiene
good bad eyesight But I think so
buena mala vista Pero yo creo que lo
does with all his good intentions
hace con toda su buena intención de
win this match Okay and the battle
ganar este partido Vale y la batalla
Above all, his struggle, his cause is worth it, but
sobre todo su lucha su causa vale pero
I think that we will also see what
yo creo que a ver también tir de lo que
can
puede
have a kiss
tener un beso
maximum I think this morning Hey but
máximo creo que esta mañana Oye pero
We found that judge brutal.
noos ha parecido brutal eso el juez que
I every time a trial fails
yo cada vez que da la pier de un juicio
I say for him at night that he
digo por el por la noche que el que el
judge has gone over there to to to
juez se ha ido por ahí a a a
drink that what I say has no
beber que lo que yo diga no tiene ningún
type does not have any type of
tipo no tenga ningún ningún tipo de
sense then he makes all the cuts
sentido entonces é hace todos los cortes
perfect so that what I say does not
perfectos para que lo que yo diga no
There is no logic to this whatsoever.
teng tenga ningún tipo de lógica este
[ __ ], I mean like it's really hard
[__] o sea como si fuera muy difícil
that is to say that we actually do it
eso o sea que nosotros en realidad lo
that he is saying yes he has a lot
que él está diciendo sí tiene mucha
Logically, what happens is that I am
lógica lo que pasa es que yo lo estoy
cutting and I'm manipulating it a lot
cortando y lo estoy manipulando mucho
to make it look like it has no
para que parezca que no tiene ningún
type of logic
tipo de lógica
eh or so this is what you are
eh o sea esto que estáis ustedes
listening really makes a lot of sense
escuchando en verdad tiene mucha lógica
It's me who makes it seem like no And
soy yo que lo hago parecer que no Y
you guys because I'm a crazy [ __ ]
ustedes porque soy unos cabrones loco un
kiss
beso
eh it looks like it looks like that clip
eh parece como parece como el clip ese
what they do to Homer in the chapter in
que le hacen a Homero en el capítulo en
the chapter that he is accused of
el capítulo que lo que lo acusan de de
grab the babysitter's ass
agarrarle el culo a la a la niñera se
They agree that it is going to be a program
acuerdan que va para un programa
deceived and in the program they do some
engañado y en el programa hacen unos
Cuts and only cut it when it is
Cortes y solamente lo cortan cuando está
doing and such the one of the the one of the
haciendo y tal el de la el de la
candy Aha that's what jav does
golosina Ajá es eso es lo que hace jav
oliveira every day on his Stream
oliveira todos los días en su Stream
Every day on the Stream he grabs short
todos los días en el Stream agarra corta
here that is not it that cannot be that is not it
aquí eso no lo eso no puede ser eso no
You can say it because for example you are
lo puede decir porque por ejemplo se le
a reaction escaped to the Stream where I
escapó una reacción al Stream donde yo
I tell him if I have all the evidence in
le digo si yo tengo todas las pruebas en
the blockchain that the scammer
la blockchain de que el estafador de
pambi is Dallas and Fernando Urdaneta and
pambi es Dallas y Fernando urdaneta y
They are all on my YouTube channel and the
están todas en mi canal de YouTube y el
fast guy if you see him
tipo rápido se sea ustedes lo vieran
How the guy hits the bar quickly
Como el tipo le da rápido a la barra
to move forward because he says damn how
para adelantar porque dice [__] Cómo
[ __ ], I'm not going to justify this. No, this isn't
[__] voy a justificar esto esto no
Do you remember that great day when you
lo os acordáis de ese gran día cuando ra
He showed that and I ran and hit the
demostró eso y yo corriendo le di a la
man, what a rush, eh, what a rush
barra [__] tío qué apuro eh qué apuro
That day I had to take it off running.
ese día eh lo tuve que quitar corriendo
because it's really quite a mess, eh?
porque es que vaya tela eh
I can justify if it is in the
puedo justificar si está en la
blockchain and cannot be edited How
blockchain y no se puede editar Cómo
I justify this no no on the blockchain in
justifico esto no no en la blockchain en
bmar was fast ahead there there is that
bmar estaba rápido adelante hay hay que
cut here so you can see what
cortar aquí para que se vea que lo que
is saying that there is no logic in it
está diciendo no tiene nada de lógica la
another strategy of this fool that
otra estrategia del papanata este que
He thinks that one graduated for free than me.
cree que uno se graduó de gratis que yo
I got my law degree, I got it
me saqué el título mío de abogado me lo
I took it out of a box of
saqué de una caja de
conf has not said that he has the title of
conf no ha dicho que tiene el título de
lawyer
abogado
Don't imagine hiring RAE to help you.
no imagínate contratar a RAE para que te
defend themselves in a trial and is put to
defiendan en un juicio y se pone a
banging his head on the table and starts to
pegarle un cabezazo a la mesa se pone a
hit the opponent What the hell, son of a [ __ ]
pegarle al contrario Cómo queé hijo [__]
that you threaten that you don't put it in like that
que tú amenazas que tú no te meto así
you know and he starts saying, imagine
sabes y se pone a decir sea imagínate a
defending yourself
ra defendiéndote
making up any story or whatever
inventándose cualquier historia o sea
tremendous lawyer eh No no but I have
tremendo abogado eh No no pero lo he
Seriously, this is the guy I'm going out with.
dicho en serio eh este el tipo yo salgo
and I say for example let's put a
y digo por ejemplo vamos a poner un
For example, I say the tests of the
ejemplo yo digo las pruebas de las
Daras scams review Fernando
estafas de daras review Fernando
Urdaneta are absolutely all in
urdaneta están a absolutamente todas en
the blockchain guy comes out and says but
la blockchain sale el tipo y dice pero
churra if this has been From 7 years ago
churra si esto ha sido Del de hace 7
months that he is going to talk about this right now
meses que va a hablar de esto ahorita no
See how stupid it is to talk about this
ven lo idiota que queda hablando de esto
Now, 7 months later, everything that one
ahorita 7 meses después todo lo que uno
say he tries to discredit him and
diga lo trata de desprestigiar y lo
tries to take away his value
trata le trata de quitar valor él
saying but churra if this this this
diciendo pero churra si esto esto esto
Here's what he said to do to her
acá Esto fue lo que dijo la hacerle hace
two years churra and now it's so what
dos años churra y ahora está y qué
It doesn't matter, you piece of [ __ ], if it's true.
importa pedazo imbécil si es verdad Qué
It doesn't matter if it was two days ago, if it was two days ago.
importa si fue hace dos días si fue hace
months if it was years ago or if he gave it or if
meses si fue hace años o si lo dio o si
his [ __ ] mother said it, what does it matter what?
lo dijo su [__] madre Qué importa qué
It matters at the moment they have it
importa en momento lo hayan
said it doesn't matter it doesn't matter eh or so
dicho no importa no importa eh o sea que
Suddenly Che the laser with his
de repente Che el laseren con su
history of the tweet I posted in 2022
historia del tweet que le puse en 2022
Antonia with her conversations
la Antonia con sus conversaciones
2016 Win michu I think he's saying
2016 Win michu creo que está diciendo
still that has changed that really
todavía que ha cambiado que de verdad
that we believe that it has
que lo creamos que ha
changed who more who more the gorgon
cambiado quién más quién más la gorgona
with the son
con lo del hijo
and each one with his own story that does not
e cada uno con su historia que no
It matters that it was a decade ago, eh?
importa que haya sido hace una década eh
Nothing happens, nothing happens, it's based
No pasa nada no pasa nada es basado
based raed is true bastard acting
basado raed es verdad cabrón accionando
Here is the thing about Joan Plana and what do I do?
acá lo de Joan plana y las a mí qué me
It matters if I'm reacting Joan
importa si estoy reaccionando Joan
flat I don't even know who Joan is
planas no sé ni siquiera Quién es Joan
flat if there is a clip of him telling her
planas si hay un clip de él diciéndole
fat, useless hick to a bunch of
cateta gorda inútiles a un montón de
women I say look you know what you don't
mujeres digo mira sabes qué tú no te
You can offend because I offend your
puedes ofender porque yo ofendo a tu
woman because you are the first one who of
mujer porque tú eres el primero que of
Grandpa already found me a new toy
abuelito ya encontró juguete nuevo me
remembered another season with the toy
recordó otra temporada con el juguete
Previously we already needed another jsj and
anterior ya necesitábamos a otro jsj y
This one with less lights, it would only be missing
este con menos luces Ya solo faltaría
that you raise the haters who defend him
que subas a los haters que lo defienden
to laugh XD but that's what happens
para reírnos XD pero es que lo que pasa
It's that not even one defends him, eh, that is, him
es que no lo defiende ni uno eh o sea el
delo He still had bad ones the delo
delo Todavía tenía malillos el delo
I still had bad ones You know why with
Todavía tenía malillos Sabes porque con
that is against D as that
eso que es en contra de D como que
Someone always joins you And such But it is
siempre alguien se te suma Y tal Pero es
that the ra is not even the ra lo
que el ra ni siquiera eh sea el ra lo
The poor man tries to put some faith some
intenta el pobre pone Alguna fese algún
tweet all that stuff but it's just not
tweet todo el rollo ese pero es que no
Hey, nobody, you don't even find a tweet.
eh nadie no te encuentras ni un tweet
to support it Here is your clip
que lo apoye Aquí está el clip tuyo
offending women churra that is
ofendiendo mujeres churra que está
reacting to when I got hot
reaccionando a cuando yo me calenté
churrita with these fatties that have
churrita con estas gordas que se han
messed with me, I do have it clear
metido conmigo yo sí tengo claro
churra justification because I am the one
justificación churra porque yo soy el
churra and because I'm very late
churra y porque tengo mucho [__]
who follows me, go suck the truth is
que me sigue anda a mamar la verdad es
the truth is, little brother, very well surpassed
la verdad hermanito muy bien rebasado
based on RAE based on the truth is the truth
basado RAE basado la verdad es la verdad
but if churra this is too much it is the
pero si churra esto es demasiado es la
true little brother the truth is the
verdad hermanito la verdad es la
See, what happened there? I want to see.
ver Ay qué ha pasado ahí que quiero ver
what has happened there that I have not
lo que ha pasado ahí que no lo he
caught wait what happened there
pillado espérate qué ha pasado ahí
luare is the
luare es la
verd What has he done
verd Qué ha hecho
There is the truth
Ahí la verda
eh eh listen listen this one is scratching
eh eh escucha escucha que este se raya
Hey, listen to me, listen to me, this one is getting scratched.
eh escúchame escúchame que este se raya
Hey, they're here in this
eh que están aquí en este
I miss you directly when you were throwing yourself at
directo extraño cuando te tirabas a
roll on the floor when you bumped into
rodar en el piso cuando te topaba con
absurdity like this you have gold for
absurdez como esta tienes oro para
do it you have earned it kneel down
hacerlo se lo ha ganado arrodillate a
pray like before I'm older I'm older
rezar como antes estoy mayor estoy mayor
eh For that eh I'm too old for that
eh Para eso eh estoy mayor para eso la
knees damn If I had how they hurt me
rodillas [__] Si tuviera cómo me dolan
knees from walking so much
las rodillas de de andar tantísimo en
New
Nueva
York this is too old this is from
York esto es demasiado viejo esto es de
when I didn't talk to you guys Ah
cuando yo no me hablaba con erdas Ah
when he wasn't talking to herdas he was
cuando no se hablaba con erdas estaba
fought with D then it means
peleado con el D entonces quiere decir
that he set the dogs on me is
que él le haya echado los perros a mi es
lie is lie The captures are
mentira es mentira Las capturas es
Lie that Bot gets into YouTube
mentira queas se mete Bot en YouTube
churra But if those captures were made
churra Pero si esas capturas fueron hace
Vasado Badía I can't no we can't
vasado badía no puedo no no podemos
replicate nothing eh it's been 6 months and what
replicar nada eh es 6 meses y qué
It doesn't matter, idiot. What does it matter that The
importa idiota Qué importa que Las
captures are months ago What does it matter
capturas sean hace se meses Qué importa
It has nothing to do with the truth is the
no tiene nada que ver la verdad es la
It is true that the theme of Christ is Ay el
verdad que ya el tema de la Cristo Ay el
frame that place the frame that I just
frame ese luar el frame que acabo de
stopping is nice for the thumbnail
parar está guapo para la miniatura
man the frame is ideal for the
tío el frame está ideal para la
miniature coins not the subject of the
miniatura monedas no el tema de las
Cryptocurrencies are not the topic: the 11 scams
criptomonedas no el tema las 11 estafas
from Pambi that goes out of fashion and is no longer
de pambi que pasa de moda y ya no es
trending on Twitter doesn't mean that
trending en Twitter no quiere decir que
They stopped doing scams that people already
dejaron de hacer estafas que ya la gente
Don't talk about ETA and DALA roaring
no hable de que de que rugan eta y dala
They released for example S Days to Rock and they
sacaron por ejemplo s days to Rock y se
0,000 raisins were stolen from Twitter
robaron 0,000 pasa de moda en Twitter
but it doesn't mean that people
pero no quiere decir que la gente
recovered the 0,000 that that pair of
recuperó los 0,000 que Ese par de
thieves took that away, that's still
ladrones se llevaron eso sigue siendo
One truth applies all the time
una verdad todo el tiempo aplica la
Same strategy, oh churra, but look
misma estrategia Ay churra pero mira
churra aside aside he thinks he's the comedian
churra aparte aparte se cree El Cómico
He doesn't believe he's the comedian making memes.
él no se cree El Cómico haciendo memes
of 15-year-old Mexican children and he believes
de niños mexicanos de 15 años y él cree
that he is the comedian here
que es que él es el cómico él que aquí
He's responding to me with memes, look here.
está respondiéndome con memes miren Aquí
He answered me.
está me respondió yo le
I sent his I'm not burned telesalseo and no
mandé su no estoy ardido telesalseo y no
she got angry
se enfadó la
The baby got angry because she didn't
guagüita se enfadó la guagüita porque no
I liked your
me gustó su
drawing you can't like it
dibujo no le podéis dar like al al
drawing you can all go to the drawing and
dibujo podéis iros todos al dibujito y
give it a like and tell me to put this
darle like y decirle r me ponerle esto
Please so they don't say that we are
por favor para que no digan que somos
a community of hate is worth it, you all go to
una comunidad de odio vale vais todos a
this drawing and you give it a like
este dibujo y le ponéis ra me gusta
It's very cool, eh, one of the best
mucho está mu chuli eh de los mejores
montages how you did it man
montajes cómo lo has hecho tío
how how how did you manage to put it here
cómo cómo cómo has conseguido poner aquí
Teresa's logo to the CEO What
el logo de Teresa al ceo Qué
[Laughs]
[Risas]
handsome
guapo
Oh how how you did it man How good
Ay cómo cómo lo has hecho tío Qué bien
brought eh what I have not caught the thing about the
traído eh lo que no he pillado lo de la
You know about the Ho What?
ustedes sabéis lo de de la Ho Qué
means the Ho here in the Ah Es
significa lo de la Ho aquí en la Ah Es
de oliveira No oh what is the o of
de oliveira No oh que es la o de
Oliveira has worked hard, go No, no, it's not
oliveira se le ha currado iros No no es
from oliveira eh the o instead of wario
de oliveira eh la o en vez de wario
olive tree
oliveira
oligario Well please go to this one
oligario Pues iros por favor a este
tweet that has no like is ok And me and him
tweet que no tiene like vale Y me y le
says how cool ra heart heart
pone qué chulo ra corazón corazón
Heart heart heart smiley face
Corazón corazón corazón carita sonriente
how well done
qué bien hecho
Uncle Haha eh How did you manage to put the
tío Jaja eh Cómo has conseguido poner el
pepper here that looks like it is
pimiento aquí que parece que está
really floating here
flotando de verdad aquí
back the idiot thinks it's because I kiss
atrás el idiota cree que es que yo beso
Alexis I'm sending Waluigi because
Alexis estoy mandándole a waluigi porque
He commands Wario, no, we are not commanding him.
él manda wario no no estamos mandándole
to wuigi because yesterday in the Stream one of
a wuigi porque ayer en el Stream uno de
You who don't know what it was, RAE told me
ustedes que no sé cuál fue me dijo RAE
that doesn't look like Wario, he's exactly the same
que no se parece a wario que Es igualito
to waluigi and really yes the churra
a waluigi y realmente sí el churra
telesalseo I'm not burned every time
telesalseo no estoy ardido cada vez que
I make a tweet or something comes out here
yo hago un tweet o una cosa sale aquí
Look here he came to his master's defense. Oh
mira aquí salió en defensa de su amo Oh
no Dallas has insulted well brought well
no Dallas ha insultado bien traído bien
Someone brought the meme very cool
traído el meme ra muy chuli alguien
Thank goodness that justice is good
Menos mal que menos mal que la justicia
put it in its place now yes, yes
lo pone en su sitio ahora sí que sí
Thanks for letting us know tonight.
gracias por avisar esta noche lo
I will comment after acknowledging that
comentaré después de reconocer que
I parked in the second row the other day because
aparqué en segunda fila el otro día por
A certain Oliveira talking about parking and
cierto oliveira hablando de aparcar y de
drive more there are clips out there of yours
conducir más hay clips por ahí tuyos
where you are driving reading chats and
donde estás manejando leyendo chats y
talking to your phone while you are
hablándole a tu teléfono mientras estás
driving without a seat belt
manejando sin cinturón de
safety without seat belt no
seguridad sin cinturón de seguridad no
I don't think the car beeps when you don't have it
no creo el coche Pita cuando no tienes
the belt of
el cinturón de
security with this fat girl who got involved
seguridad con esta gorda que se meti
with me not without a belt it would not be without
conmigo no sin cinturón no sería sin
belt of the pants That's right, huh
cinturón de los pantalones Eso sí eh
but without any sense of security by not speaking to him
pero sin ón de seguridad no hablándole
to the mobile phone maybe also That's what you do
al móvil puede que también Eso sí te lo
I will recognize RAE But you know what happens RAE
vo reconocer RAE Pero sabes qué pasa RAE
that you can talk to the cell phone, okay?
que al móvil se le puede hablar vale
because on the other side of the connection there is
porque al otro lado de la conexión Hay
people who speak I know that you the
personas que hablan Yo sé que tú el
you use your phone to harass
teléfono lo utilizas para acosar a
women are worth it and take pictures like that
mujeres vale Y hacerle fotografías así
I don't know about thongs, but the phone has one.
de tanga no sé pero el móvil tiene una
something called hands-free or what
cosa que se llama manos libres o lo
you can put it on the stand and you can
puedes poner en el soporte y te puedes
record without problem you know but yes yes yes
grabar sin problema sabes pero sí sí sí
That's what you said there, a factor I have
eso ahí has dicho un factor le he
spoken to the mobile a lot of times
hablado al móvil un montón de veces lo
I recognize
reconozco
a kiss
un beso
friend A kiss Bravo Wait a moment
amigo Un beso Bravo Espérate un momento
uncle
tío
Oh
Oh
No
no
[ __ ] [ __ ]
[__] [__]
[Music]
[Música]
have m in
ten m en
we have in this
tenem en es
sun sun
sol sol
[Music]
[Música]
based based r driving and dancing
basado basado r conduciendo y bailando
based raay driving and
basado raay conduciendo y
dancing and
bailando an
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Look you see the reflection driving and
Mira ves el reflejo conduciendo y
looking at the phone
mirando el teléfono
[Music]
[Música]
m Ai
m Ai
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
driving and doing those stories of
conduciendo y haciendo esas historias de
Instagram now sees and criticizes Brunenger
Instagram ahora ve y critica a brunenger
when you are a [ __ ] brunenger the same
cuando eres un [__] brunenger la misma
[ __ ] and it's not just one clip a bunch of
[__] y no es un solo clip un montón de
clips with this guy with the phone
clips con el trolo este con el teléfono
sitting there talking on the phone like this
puesto ahí hablándole al teléfono así
without a seat belt and driving
sin cinturón de seguridad y conduciendo
Then the whole thing is projected.
Entonces se proyecta se proyecta todo el
time is projected a lot eh
tiempo se proyecta muchísimo eh se
projects a lot
proyecta much
Simon For more than healthy people and
Simón Por más que gente sanita y
exemplary like you on the internet or me in
ejemplar como tú en internet o sea yo en
I'm much better than you on the internet.
internet soy muchísimo mejor que tú
because I teach on the internet
porque yo en internet Le enseño a la
people something and people go to this
gente algo y la gente se va a este
Stream with something on your mind people
Stream con algo en la cabeza la gente se
She leaves here happy because she is leaving with
va de aquí contenta porque se va con
something else to sleep the people who leave
algo más a dormir la gente que se va de
your stream is filled with head
tu Stream se va llena de con la cabeza
full of hatred and resentment for people
llena de odio de resentimiento por gente
that they don't know with full of lies and
que no conocen con llena de mentiras y
of slander about people they don't know
de calumnias sobre gente que no conocen
based on that, repeating the lies
basado eh ahí eh repitiendo las mentiras
From an alumni ador that is what he
de un alumni ador eso es lo que él le
he sows in the heads of his followers that
siembra en la cabeza a sus segidores que
They are very stupid, my post has 610 likes
son muy tontos mi post tiene 610 likes
610 likes comes the [ __ ] one with his
610 likes viene el [__] con sus
other retards tweet and he has
otros retrasados twitea y él tiene
779 likes What's the first thing they do?
779 likes Qué es lo primero que hacen
the [ __ ] ones who follow him Well
los retrasados que lo siguen a él Bueno
There they have given you a like on that post yet
ahí te han dado like en ese post todavía
The ratio is not so humiliated
no es tanta la humillada del ratio
Normally Maybe I have it every time
normalmente A lo mejor tengo yo cada vez
I answer you 1000 likes and your 10
que te respondo 1000 likes y tus 10
Likes Maybe they will be yours and yours
likes A lo mejor que serán tuyos y de tu
girlfriend but in that particular one it is that
novia pero en ese en concreto es que
you were putting the Dallas conviction
estabas poniendo la condena de Dallas
So when I answer you, people who
Entonces al yo contestarte la gente que
come see my tweets that are my haters I give you
ven mis twit que son mis hater te doy
more diffusion you know So you're welcome what
más difusión sabes O sea que de nada qué
ratio what ratio made you Wow what ratio
ratio qué ratio te hizo Wow qué ratio
such an impressive ratio we are more
tan impresionante ratio somos más los
We are [ __ ], more do you believe me?
retrasados somos más os creen a me
It matters, but what does it have to do with it?
importa pero es que qué tiene que ver
that he has more likes than he has all
que tenga más likes él que él tiene toda
his life on YouTube has 123,000
su vida en YouTube tiene 123000
followers of that idiot I have
seguidores el el papanatas ese yo tengo
13000 I have 13000 I have 610 likes
13000 yo tengo 13000 yo tengo 610 likes
and also because he is unemployed and has 700
y además porque parado y él tiene 700
Also, if you don't wipe it with a cloth and have
además sí no vos le pasas el trapo y ten
keep in mind that it's you who happens to him, RAE you
en cuenta que es vos le pas sí RAE tú le
you wipe the poor bride has to
pasas el trapo la pobre novia tiene que
be saying yes RAE Yes yes you him
estar diciéndole sí RAE Sí sí tú le
you wipe the RAE with a rag and we know
pasas el trapo RAE hace salseo y sabemos
that the term "salseo" moves masses
que que el término salseo mueve masas
guys because people like it
chicos porque a la gente le gusta el
quilombo a crypto content a
quilombo un contenido cripto un
quality gossip content and
contenido de calidad salseo y
defamations a had quality is more
difamaciones un tenido calidad es más
difficult that the controversy will always go
difícil que la la polémica siempre va a
having more was going to put some phrase of the
tener más iba a poner alguna frase de la
girlfriend from the beginning but now as she has
novia del principio pero ya como se ha
has been put against me
puesto en contra se me ha
I was going to forget to put
olvidado iba a poner de
title: r me's girlfriend
título la novia de r me
defends but I was going to add some phrase
defiende pero iba a poner alguna frase
I have forgotten the beginning of it
el principio de ella se me ha olvidado
uncle for the thumbnail
tío para la miniatura
I say even if it's [ __ ] and that
digo aunque sea una [__] y que
really don't do anything good for the
realmente no haga nada bueno para la
society because it is based on
sociedad porque es la basado basada
bay
badía
One will not earn more money knowing if
uno no va a ganar más plata Sabiendo si
Gita cheated on him or not?
gita le metió los cuernos o no aur
clearly not me based based but
claramente No yo basada basada pero
we want
queremos
know it but we want
saberlo pero queremos
know it Ah but but I don't remember something
saberlo Ah pero pero no me acuerdo algo
positive that he told me before at the beginning
positivo que me dijo antes al principio
Hey, he's already beaten you. Accept it. Yes.
ehay ya te venció Ja Acéptalo si lo
I accepted the principle
acepté principio
I don't remember, could I put it on the
no me acuerdo podría ponerle la
miniature as well as I am a fan of Javi or
miniatura así como soy fan de Javi o
Something like that is what the [ __ ] Venezuelan says
algo así dice el [__] venezolano tiene
like 40 years Look at the level please
como 40 años Miren el nivel por favor el
level of hate no no the level of hate
nivel de odio no no el nivel de odio
Agustina the level the level of delay
Agustina el nivel el nivel de retraso
mentally the [ __ ] Venezuelan is like 40
mental el [__] venezolano tiene como 40
old years
añosos años
has been messing with you for 40 years RAE
tiene te metiendo contigo 40 años RAE te
you're messing with yourself because you're 40
estás metiendo contigo porque tienes 40
years old and you are
años y eres
stupid, I mean it's not because you're 40 years old
tonto o sea no es porque tengas 40 años
He's not telling you, "Ah, you're 40, aren't you?"
no te está diciendo Ah tienes 40 años no
You can be 40 years old, people turn 40.
puedes tener 40 años la gente cumple
years the problem is that you are 40 years old and
años el problema es que tengas 40 años y
you are
seas
so 40 years old imbecile is 40 years old me
así 40 años imbécil tiene 40 años me
I put it on me, the [ __ ] guy is 40 years old
puse me pone el putoz tiene 40 años se
behaves like he's 20 I'm
comporta como si tuviera 20 yo me
I behave as if I were 20 years old, I who
comporto como si tuviera 20 años yo que
I'm looking at coins and cryptos here or the
estoy viendo aquí monedas y criptos o el
idiot who is reacting to Juan
idiota que está reaccionando a Juan
guard to wescol who is the one who has
guarniz a wescol quién es el que tiene
20 mental years Ah, the one who knows, the one who knows
20 años mentales Ah el que se el que se
you're going to get rich with a cryptocurrency
va a hacer rico con una criptomoneda
like Unicorn farts or the idiot who
como Unicorn fardos o el idiota que
He has to be watching what he's doing
tiene que estar viendo que está haciendo
wescol smelling the farts of the
wescol oliéndole los pedos a los
influencer Who is the one who behaves
influencer Quién es el que se comporta
as if it is so Why is it so
como si está tan Por qué está tan
angry 43 has the baby at that age
enfadado 43 tiene la guagüita a esa edad
they are tremendous
son tremendo
But why is he so angry?
Pero por qué está tan enfadado la
baby, that was known for a long time
guagüita eso se sabía desde hace tiempo
Update yourself, poor thing, how much you want
actualízate Pobrecito cuántas ganas
has to attract attention and I tell him
tiene de llamar la atención y yo le digo
oliveras is older, he is 40 years old
oliveras es más viejo tiene 40 años de
human that in dog life is 240 years
humano eso en vida de perro Son 240 años
The dog is two and a half centuries old
dos siglos y medio tiene el can le
I put and boast of his
puse y presume de su
answer and boast about his answer year
respuesta y presume de su respuesta año
40 years of dog is a lot, it's a lot
de perro 40 años es muchísimo es un
old dog an ancient dog
perro anciano un perro de ancient de
ancient dog what what what the [ __ ] is wrong with him
ancient dog qué qué qué [__] le pasa
How is the [ __ ] Venezuela going to turn out 40 years ago?
Cómo va a salir el [__] venezola 40 años
How old is the idiot?
Cuántos años tiene al idiota Al que
you are defending but you have
estás defendiendo pero es que tienes
delay or what? I mean, do you really have
retraso o qué O sea de verdad tienes
They are mentally [ __ ] and very losers.
retraso mental Son son muy losers son
very losers Then the idiot comes out here
muy losers Entonces el idiota sale aquí
and says, Oh, it seems that you can't do it.
y dice Ay como que no a ti no te sale
love yourself a little bit I do take it love yourself
quiérete un poquito Yo sí toma quiérete
t a little bit go sleep there with your
t un poquito vete a dormir ahí con tu
grab your catfish grab your catfish God grab
agarra tu bagre coge tu bagre Dios coge
You and the poor girlfriend laughing at the
tu y la novia la pobre riéndose de las
nonsense that Ray says. Look, take your
tonterías que dice el Ray Mira coge tu
catfish your bagasse There give him your kiss
bagre tu bagazo Ahí dale tu beso
It's hard to sleep because every time you put
cuestate a dormir que cada vez que pones
the little face like that on the pillow
la carita así en la almohadita te
Do you remember what I tell you every time?
acuerdas de lo que te digo cada vez que
He makes his face like this and says damn it
pone la carita así así dice [__] sea
Damn I'm going to sleep
[__] sea que me estoy yendo a dormir
and this son of a [ __ ] told me that while
y este hijo de [__] me dijo eso mientras
that I don't sleep like this watching the
que yo no yo duermo así viendo los
simson like this eating some gummies
simson así comiéndome unas gomitas de
those of Agustina stolen and already hidden
las de Agustina robada y ya escondido
because he says he says he doesn't burn
porque él dice él dice que él no se arde
That's why I look, I don't even know him.
Por esto yo mira yo no ni siquiera le
I write nothing to you, it doesn't come out because he
escribo nada a ti no te sale porque él
He's the funny one. Oh yeah. Ah, I'm not.
es el chistoso Ah sí Ah yo no soy
funny Ah well here here let's see if not
chistoso Ah bueno toma toma a ver si no
It's a joke, let's see if it doesn't make you laugh, clown.
es chiste a ver si no da risa payaso se
sleeping there with his friend is angry
dormir allá con su agre está enfadado
No, but why does it go like this?
no Pero por qué va así
Take it out of the river that is very
la sáquelo ahí del río que está muy
funny what your answer
gracioso ra tu respuesta qué
chuli agre del río lie down to sleep and
chuli agre del río acuéstese a dormir y
and to be setting the dogs on the
tal y estarle echando los perros a las
girls on instagram are throwing them
niñas en instagram estle echando los
dogs to Dallas's ex-girlfriends go
perros a las exnovias de Dallas vaya
lie down even if you sleep there with
acuéstese usted así duerma ahí con
its this tomorrow tomorrow when I leave
su este mañana mañana cuando salga
to act like a fool and to act like Ah
hacerse el vasado y hacerse el que Ah
How do I know? Oh, I am the king of gossip.
cómo sé yo Ay yo soy el rey del salseo
the king of gossip tomorrow any tweet
el rey del salseo mañana cualquier tweet
there out there any video clip that
ahí por ahí cualquier videoclip que
I took it out and put it here, Luigi.
saque el lo vo a poner aquí Luigi
Luigi is going to give me an answer in
Luigi me lo va a poner de respuesta en
the twi that
el twi que
position
puesto
no Ah well I put this one that this one I put the
no Ah bueno puse este que este puse el
Click on Dallas from sucking [ __ ] to
click de Dallas del chupándosela al
Dallas is going to appear here Ray in
Dallas por aquí va a aparecer ray en
any time eh
cualquier momento eh
but I think this is what he's going to put in
pero lo yo creo que lo va a poner este
uncle this is
tío este es
Great, Dallas and you have principles.
buenísimo Dallas y tú tienen principios
They even become good people with
Incluso se pasan de buena gente con
many always kick them out afterwards
muchos siempre les da la patada después
of scratching fame that when they no longer
de rascar fama que cuando ya no les
interested become sick until
interesa se vuelven enfermos hasta que
They end up sunk and without relevance but
terminan hundidos y sin relevancia pero
This guy is really, really crazy.
lo de este tío está muy muy loco
No, this guy is very crazy.
no lo de este tío está muy loco
eh, I mean, it also goes like s it goes like a
eh o sea además va como s va como una
super crazy motorcycle looking bad bad
moto super desquiciado quedando mal mal
bad bad doing the pathetic eh I mean
mal mal haciendo el patético eh o sea
but I don't know if you act like that
pero yo no sé es que si te pones así
Uncle I don't know, maybe if you answer it's more
tío No sé a lo mejor si contestas es más
calmer, more chill than you weren't
calmadito más chill que no estuvieras
burned you know but it's that it's super
ardido sabes pero es que está super
burned
ardido
[Music]
[Música]
eh it's looking terrible but apart
eh está quedando fatal pero aparte
insulting children insulting women
insultando a niños insultando a mujeres
the poor bride next door with me I imagine
la pobre novia al lado con me imagino
afraid of not saying no to anything
con miedo a no decirle de que no a nada
Of course, you are obviously a tremendous madman.
Claro evidentemente tremendo loco tienes
next door but good for a laugh
al lado pero bueno para echar las risas
this
está
well no no we are not going to stop
bien no no nosotros no vamos a dejar de
reacting to this series seems like cinema to me
reaccionar a esta serie me parece cine
eh Nothing, no tomorrow we'll see
eh Nada no mañana vemos
That place we see tomorrow is that
ese que mañana vemos ese lugar es que
I have to record for him
tengo que grabar para el
main tomorrow we see that total It is
principal mañana lo vemos ese total Está
Good morning Good morning Good morning
bien Mañana Bueno mañana Bueno mañana
past
pasado
or in the extensible what we do
o en el extensible qué hacemos
family I understand habi you can't
familia entiendo habi tú no puedes
tell you nothing, I remind you that you don't
decirle nada ra te recuerdo que no te
you put on your seatbelt in the car
pones cinturón en el coche
Ah I would love to be live but it is
Ah Me encantaría está en directo pero es
that I am not going to invite you to debate
que no vo no voy a invitar a debatir a
a guy who insults my wife
un tipo que insulta a mi mujer
garlic me
aijo me
you understand But if not if if there weren't
entiendes Pero si no si si no hubiera
crossed that
traspasado esa
even line
línea incluso
We could invite him to debate and
lo lo podríamos invitar a a debatir y
it cracks us up
nos descojona
eh what I don't understand is how he doesn't
eh lo que yo no entiendo es Cómo no le
They ban no No man Of course not
banean no No hombre Claro que no lo
we're going to invite But what I don't
vamos a invitar Pero lo que yo no
I understand this is how he doesn't get banned from Twitch.
entiendo es cómo no lo banean del Twitch
You can't be insulting people like that.
no puedes estar insultando a gente de
that way you were a zen person with Mili
esa forma raed una persona zen con Mili
a hug face throwing a kiss Thank you
un abrazo cara lanzando un beso Gracias
heart I love you so much family
corazón Te quiero mucho familia
How could I know that you want a
Cómo cómo podría yo saber que queréis un
extensible I mean if I knew that
extensible O sea si yo supiera que
you want the
queréis el
extensible, that is, how could we measure if
extensible o sea cómo podríamos medir si
Do you want the extendable one or not? And then
queréis el extensible o no Y entonces ya
chill tomorrow I don't work tomorrow it's up
chill mañana no trabajo mañana se sube
the video that is being recorded now on the channel
el vídeo que se grabe ahora en el canal
main thing that I'm waiting for
principal que lo estoy esperando que me
finish the compilation
terminen la recopilación
in
em
How do I know you want the extendable one?
Cómo sé que queréis el extensible pues
Okay, okay, tomorrow I won't, won't, won't work, okay?
ya ya mañana yo no no no trabajo vale
I am fully involved with my son and he
estoy a tope con con mi hijo y y el
Sunday we could
domingo podríamos
do it But how do we do it grandpa you
hacerlo Pero cómo lo hacemos abuelo te
I want you love me and I do love you
quiero tú me quieres y yo sí te quiero
handsome, how could it not be
guapo cómo no
but extensible without limit mouse but it is
pero extensible sin límite ratón pero es
that without limits I cannot, I cannot, I have
que sin límite no puedo no puedo tengo
children who go to school and my wife studies
hijos que van al Cole y mi mujer estudia
So now I can stay from now on.
O sea ya el el el puedo quedarme desde
Sunday at 12
el domingo a las 12
put on and I can even put on men
ponte y me puedo poner hasta las hombre
as always Look from the
como a la hora de siempre Mira desde las
12 until 12 is 12
12 hasta las 12 son 12
hours until 3 are 15 hours I can
horas hasta las 3 son 15 horas me puedo
set a limit of 15 hours
poner un límite de 15 horas
and besides, you are already telling me
y aparte me estáis ya me estáis diciendo
that you are going to spend the
que Vais a pasar el
12 hour limit is fine man Karime
límite 12 horas está bien hombre Karime
If you tell me we're going to arrive at 12
si me dices que vamos a llegar a las 12
hours I do it from
horas lo hago del
pull but of course I don't know I think
tirón pero claro es que no lo sé yo creo
that we are in a very bad month already
que estamos en un mes muy malo ya la
People have also donated a lot to the
gente ha donado mucho también para la
box I think it's ready I think so
caja yo creo que ya está yo creo que si
perhaps it would be to do it the next time
acaso sería hacerlo a la siguiente
week
semana
eh, you can't do it 24 hours, man, 24 hours
eh No se puede 24 horas hombre 24 horas
The truth is that I think it is complicated.
la verdad es que complicado yo creo que
It would be better to do it next time
sería mejor hacerlo la siguiente
week and people are going to c
semana y y va a c la gente
better not not the box the box has been
mejor no no la caja la caja se le ha
stuck in a big squeeze the box already
pegado en apreto gordo la caja ya la
the answer to the complaint is paid
contestación a la demanda está pagada
Okay, and that's it.
vale Y ya
[Music]
[Música]
600 euros more or so 600 700 euros more already known
600 eur más o así 600 700 eur más ya se
the attorney pays and now for Joan Hasta
paga el procurador y ya lo de Joan Hasta
then it would be time to start suing
luego ya sería empezar a demandar a
Peña but I'm not going to say who In
Peña pero no voy a decir A quiénes En
what order But we would be you already know the
qué orden Pero seríamos ya conocéis la
list and we are going to and we are going to sue
lista y vamos a y vamos demandando a
all the little characters
todos los personajillos
I don't know, man, I'll think about it tomorrow, but of course
no sé tío lo meditaré mañana pero claro
I would like How could we do it by
me gustaría Cómo podríamos hacerlo por
For example
por ejemplo
eh By
eh Por
likes I mean if this live has many
likes O sea si este directo tiene muchos
likes I don't know 3000
likes yo que sé 3000
likes tomorrow I announce the extensible. That is
likes mañana anuncio el extensible O sea
Yes, yes, for likes something is worth free, yes.
si si por likes vale algo gratuito si
This live stream has 3000 likes tomorrow
este directo tiene 3000 likes mañana
I do I do
hago hago
I do the extension on Sunday because
el hago el extensible el domingo porque
I know that people want it and then, well,
sé que la gente quiere y ya luego pues
We will be there for 4 hours, we will be there for five
estaremos 4 horas estaremos cinco
we will be six it will depend on
estaremos seis dependerá de
You guys OK, well, if this live has
ustedes Vale pues si este directo tiene
3000 likes it
3000 likes lo
Let's go guys, I'm going, okay, I have to
hacemos chicos me voy vale que tengo que
record the video for the main
grabar el el videito para el principal
Have a nice Saturday and see you
que paséis un bonito sábado y nos vemos
Sunday extendable or non-extendable yes
el domingo extensible o no extensible si
There is no extension because we will see each other in the
no hay extensible pues nos vemos por la
night Tomorrow Frank at 12 okay tomorrow
noche Mañana Frank a las 12 vale mañana
Frank is on the flight, come on, let's give him one.
Frank está el vuelo venga le hacemos una
Ray on the fly tomorrow Frank is at 12
ray al vuelo mañana Frank está a las 12
ok a kiss poncito Thank you very much
vale un beso poncito Muchas gracias
very handsome we do ra on the fly Give it to
guapísimo hacemos ra al vuelo Dale al
ra button
botón de la ra